<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>



     <string name="bardOverview">
        Humming as she traces her fingers over an ancient
        monument in a long-forgotten ruin, a half-elf in rugged
        leathers finds knowledge springing into her mind,
        conjured forth by the magic of her song — knowledge
        of the people who constructed the monument and the
        mythic saga it depicts.
        \n\nA stern human warrior bangs his sword rhythmically
        against his scale mail, setting the tempo for his war chant
        and exhorting his companions to bravery and heroism.
        The magic of his song fortifies and emboldens them.
        \n\nLaughing as she tunes her cittern, a gnome weaves
        her subtle magic over the assembled nobles, ensuring
        that her companions’ words will be well received.
        \n\nWhether scholar, skald, or scoundrel, a bard weaves
        magic through words and music to inspire allies,
        demoralize foes, manipulate minds, create
        illusions, and even heal w ounds.
    </string>

    <string name="bardCreating">
        Bards thrive on stories, whether those stories are true
        or not. Your character’s background and motivations
        are not as important as the stories that he or she tells
        about them. Perhaps you hada secure and mundane
        childhood. There’s no good story to be told about that,
        so you might paint yourself as an orphan raised by a hag
        in a dismal swamp. Or your childhood might be worthy
        of a story. Some bards acquire their magical music
        through extraordinary means, including the inspiration
        of fey or other supernatural creatures.
        \n\nDid you serve an apprenticeship, studying under a
        master, following the more experienced bard until you
        were ready to strike out on your own? Or did you attend
        a college where you studied bardic lore and practiced
        your musical magic? Perhaps you were a young runaway
        or orphan, befriended by a wandering bard who became
        your mentor. Or you might have been a spoiled noble
        child tutored by a master. Perhaps you stumbled into the
        clutches of a hag, making a bargain for a musical gift in
        addition to your life and freedom, but at what cost?
    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="bard_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Spellcasting,
        \nBardic Inspiration (d6)
    </string>

    <string name="bard_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Jack of All Trades,
        \nSong of Rest (d6)
    </string>

    <string name="bard_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        Bard College,
        \nExpertise
    </string>

    <string name="bard_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="bard_5th_lvl_abilities">
        Bardic Inspiration (d8),
        \nFont of Inspiration
    </string>

    <string name="bard_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Countercharm,
        \nBard College Feature
    </string>

    <string name="bard_7th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="bard_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="bard_9th_lvl_abilities">
        Song of Rest (d8)
    </string>

    <string name="bard_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Bardic Inspiration(d10),
        \nExpertise,
        \nMagical Secrets
    </string>

    <string name="bard_11th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="bard_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="bard_13th_lvl_abilities">
        Song of Rest (d10)
    </string>

    <string name="bard_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Magical Secrets,
        \nBard College Feature
    </string>

    <string name="bard_15th_lvl_abilities">
        Bardic Inspiration (d12)
    </string>

    <string name="bard_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="bard_17th_lvl_abilities">
        Song of Rest (d12)
    </string>

    <string name="bard_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Magical Secrets
    </string>

    <string name="bard_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="bard_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Superior Inspiration
    </string>

    //---------------------------------------------------------Spell Table---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="bard_table2_label">
        Spells Table
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value2_label">
        Cantrips Known
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_label">
        Spells Known
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value2_1to3_values">
        2
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value2_4to9_values">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value2_10to20_values">
        4
    </string>


    <string name="bard_table2_value3_1values">
        4
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_2values">
        5
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_3values">
        6
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_4values">
        7
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_5values">
        8
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_6values">
        9
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_7values">
        10
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_8values">
        11
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_9values">
        12
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_10values">
        14
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_11to12values">
        15
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_13values">
        16
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_14values">
        18
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_15to16values">
        19
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_17values">
        20
    </string>

    <string name="bard_table2_value3_18to20values">
        22
    </string>


    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="bardFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a bard, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="bardHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d8 per bardn lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 8 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d8(or 5) + Constitution Modifier per bard level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="bardProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> Light Armor
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Simple Weapons, hand crossbows, longswords, rapiers, shortswords
        \n<b>Tools:</b> Three musical instruments of your choice
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Dexterity, Charisma
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose any three
    </string>

    <string name="bardEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background
        \n\n- (a) a rapier or (b) a longsword or (c) any simple weapon
        \n- (a) a diplomats pack or (b) an entertainers pack
        \n- (a) a lute or (b) any other musical instrument
        \n- Leather armor and a dagger
    </string>


    //------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    //------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//







    <string name="bardSpellSlots">
        The table below shows how many spell slots you have to
        cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of
        these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell’s level
        or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you
        finish a long rest.
        \n\nFor example, if you know the 1st-level spell cure
        wounds and have a 1st-level and a 2nd-level spell slot
        available, you can cast cure wounds using either slot.
    </string>

    <string name="BardSpellKnownForFirstLevelAndHigher">
        You know four 1st-level spells of your choice from the
        bard spell list.
        \n\nThe Spells Known column of the Bard table shows
        when you learn more bard spells of your choice. Each of
        these spells must be of a level for which you have spell
        slots, as shown on the table above. For instance, when you
        reach 3rd level in this class, you can learn one new spell
        of 1st or 2nd level.
        \n\nAdditionally, w hen you gain a level in this class, you
        can choose one of the bard spells you know and replace
        it with another spell from the bard spell list, which also
        must be of a level for which you have spell slots.
    </string>

    <string name="BardSpelLCastingAbility">
        Charisma is your spellcasting ability for your bard
        spells. Your magic comes from the heart and soul you
        pour into the performance of your music or oration.
        You use your Charisma whenever a spell refers to your
        spellcasting ability. In addition, you use your Charisma
        modifier when setting the saving throw DC for a bard
        spell you cast and when making an attack roll with one.
    </string>

    <string name="BardSpellSave">
        <b>Spell Save DC</b> = 8 + your proficiency bonus + your charisma modifier
        \n\n
        <b>Spell Attack Modifier</b> = your proficiency bonus + your charisma modifier
    </string>

    <string name="BardRitualCasting">
        You can cast any bard spell you know as a ritual if that
        spell has the ritual tag.
    </string>

    <string name="BardSpelLCastingFocus">
        You can use a musical instrument (found in chapter 5)
        as a spellcasting focus for your bard spells.
    </string>

    <string name="BardBardicInspiration">
        You can inspire others through stirring words or music.
        To do so, you use a bonus action on your turn to choose
        one creature other than yourself within 60 feet of you
        who can hear you. That creature gains one Bardic
        Inspiration die, a d6.
        \n\nOnce within the next 10 minutes, the creature can roll
        the die and add the number rolled to one ability check,
        attack roll, or saving throw it makes. The creature can
        wait until after it rolls the d20 before deciding to use the
        Bardic Inspiration die, but must decide before the DM
        says whether the roll succeeds or fails. Once the Bardic
        Inspiration die is rolled, it is lost. A creature can have
        only on e Bardic Inspiration die at a time.
        \n\nYou can use this feature a number of times equal
        to your Charisma modifier (a minimum of once). You
        regain any expended uses when you finish a long rest.
        \n\nYour Bardic Inspiration die changes when you reach
        certain levels in this class. The die becomes a d8 at 5th
        level, a d10 at 10th level, and a d12 at 15th level.
    </string>

    <string name="BardJackOfAllTrades">
        Starting at 2nd level, you can add half your proficiency
        bonus, rounded down, to any ability check you make that
        doesn’t already include your proficiency bonus.
    </string>

    <string name="BardSongOfRest">
        Beginning at 2nd level, you can use soothing music or
        oration to help revitalize your wounded allies during
        a short rest. If you or any friendly creatures who can
        hear your performance regain hit points at the end of
        the short rest, each of those creatures regains an extra
        1d6 hit points.
        \n\nThe extra hit points increase when you reach certain
        levels in this class: to 1d8 at 9th level, to 1d10 at 13th
        level, and to 1d12 at 17th level.
    </string>

    <string name="BardBardCollege">
        At 3rd level, you delve into the advanced techniques of
        a bard college of your choice: the College of Lore or the
        College of Valor. Your choice grants you features at 3rd level
        and again at 6th and 14th level.
    </string>

    <string name="BardExperise">
        At 3rd level, choose two of your skill proficiencies. Your
        proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check you
        make that uses either of the chosen proficiencies.
        \n\nAt 10th level, you can choose another two skill
        proficiencies to gain this benefit.
    </string>

    <string name="BardFontOfInspiration">
        Beginning when you reach 5th level, you regain all of
        your expended uses of Bardic Inspiration w hen you
        finish a short or long rest.
    </string>

    <string name="BardCounterCharm">
        At 6th level, you gain the ability to use musical notes or
        words of power to disrupt mind-influencing effects. As
        an action, you can start a performance that lasts until
        the end of your next turn. During that time, you and any
        friendly creatures within 30 feet of you have advantage
        on saving throws against being frightened or charmed.
        A creature must be able to hear you to gain this benefit.
        The performance ends early if you are incapacitated or
        silenced or if you voluntarily end it (no action required).
    </string>

    <string name="BardMagicalSecrets">
        By 10th level, you have plundered magical knowledge
        from a wide spectrum of disciplines. Choose two spells
        from any class, including this one. A spell you choose
        must be of a level you can cast, as shown on the Bard
        table, or a cantrip.
        \n\nThe chosen spells count as bard spells for you and are
        included in the number in the Spells Known column of
        the Bard table.
        \n\nYou learn two additional spells from any class at 14th
        level and again at 18th level.
    </string>

    <string name="BardSuperiorInspiration">
        At 20th level, when you roll initiative and have no uses
        of Bardic Inspiration left, you regain one use.
    </string>

    <string name="BardCollegesDescription">
        The way of a bard is gregarious. Bards seek each
        other out to swap songs and stories, boast of their
        accomplishments, and share their knowledge. Bards
        form loose associations, which they call colleges, to
        facilitate their gatherings and preserve their traditions.
    </string>

    <string name="BardCollageOfLore">
        Bards of the College of Lore know something about
        most things, collecting bits of knowledge from sources
        as diverse as scholarly tomes and peasant tales.
        \n\nWhether singing folk ballads in taverns or elaborate
        compositions in royal courts, these bards use their gifts
        to hold audiences spellbound. When the applause dies
        down, the audience members might find them selves
        questioning everything they held to be true, from their
        faith in the priesthood of the local temple to their
        loyalty to the king.
        \n\nThe loyalty of these bards lies in the pursuit of beauty
        and truth, not in fealty to a monarch or following the
        tenets of a deity. A noble who keeps such a bard as a
        herald or advisor knows that the bard would rather be
        honest than politic.
        \n\nThe college`s members gather in libraries and
        sometimes in actual colleges, complete with classrooms
        and dormitories, to share their lore with one another.
        They also meet at festivals or affairs of state, where they
        can expose corruption, unravel lies, and poke fun at self-
        important figures of authority.
    </string>

    <string name="BardBonusProfitiences">
        When you join the College of Lore at 3rd level, you gain
        proficiency with three skills of your choice.
    </string>

    <string name="BardCuttingWords">
        Also at 3rd level, you learn how to use your wit to
        distract, confuse, and otherwise sap the confidence and
        competence of others. When a creature that you can
        see within 60 feet of you makes an attack roll, an ability
        check, or a damage roll, you can use your reaction to
        expend one of your uses of Bardic Inspiration, rolling
        a Bardic Inspiration die and subtracting the number
        rolled from the creature’s roll. You can choose to use
        this feature after the creature makes its roll, but before
        the DM determines whether the attack roll or ability
        check succeeds or fails, or before the creature deals its
        damage. The creature is immune if it can’t hear you or if
        it’s immune to being charmed.
    </string>

    <string name="BardAdditionalMagicSecrets">
        At 6th level, you learn two spells of your choice from any
        class. A spell you choose must be of a level you can cast,
        as shown on the Bard table, or a cantrip. The chosen
        spells count as bard spells for you but don’t count
        against the number of bard spells you know.
    </string>

    <string name="BardPeerlessSkill">
        Starting at 14th level, when you make an ability check,
        you can expend one use of Bardic Inspiration. Roll a
        Bardic Inspiration die and add the number rolled to
        your ability check. You can choose to do so after you roll
        the die for the ability check, but before the DM tells you
        whether you succeed or fail.
    </string>

    <string name="BardCollegeOfValor">
        Bards of the College of Valor are daring skalds whose
        tales keep alive the memory of the great heroes of the
        past, and thereby inspire a new generation of heroes.
        These bards gather in mead halls or around great
        bonfires to sing the deeds of the mighty, both past
        and present. They travel the land to witness great
        events firsthand and to ensure that the memory of
        those events doesn’t pass from the world. With their
        songs, they inspire others to reach the same heights of
        accomplishment as the heroes of old.
    </string>

    <string name="BardValorBonusBrofitiency">
        When you join the College of Valor at 3rd level, you
        gain proficiency with medium armor, shields, and
        martial weapons.
    </string>

    <string name="BardCombatInspiration">
        Also at 3rd level, you learn to inspire others in battle.
        A creature that has a Bardic Inspiration die from you
        can roll that die and add the number rolled to a weapon
        damage roll it just made.
        \n\nAlternatively, when an attack
        roll is made against the creature, it can use its reaction
        to roll the Bardic Inspiration die and add the number
        rolled to its AC against that attack, after seeing the roll
        but before knowing whether it hits or misses.
    </string>

    <string name="BardExtraAttack">
        Starting at 6th level, you can attack twice, instead of
        once, whenever you take the Attack action on your turn.
    </string>

    <string name="BardBattleMagic">
        At 14th level, you have mastered the art of weaving
        spellcasting and weapon use into a single harmonious
        act. When you use your action to cast a bard spell, you
        can make one weap on attack as a bonus action.
    </string>

</resources>