<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

     <string name="clericOverview">
        Arms and eyes upraised toward the sun and a prayer
        on his lips, an elf begins to glow with an inner light that
        spills out to heal his battle-worn companions.
        \n\nChanting a song of glory, a dwarf swings his axe
        in wide swaths to cut through the ranks of orcs
        arrayed against him, shouting praise to the gods with
        every foe’s fall.
        \n\nCalling down a curse upon the forces of undeath, a
        human lifts her holy symbol as light pours from it to
        drive back the zombies crowding in on her companions.
        Clerics are intermediaries between the mortal world
        and the distant planes of the gods. As varied as the gods
        they serve, clerics strive to embody the handiwork of
        their deities. No ordinary priest, a cleric is imbued with
        divine magic.
    </string>

    <string name="clericCreating">
        As you create a cleric, the most important question to
        consider is which deity to serve and what principles you
        want your character to embody. Check with
        your DM to learn which deities are in your campaign.
        Once you’ve chosen a deity, consider your cleric’s
        relationship to that god. Did you enter this service
        willingly? Or did the god choose you, impelling you into
        service with no regard for your w ishes? How do the
        temple priests of your faith regard you: as a champion
        or a troublemaker? What are your ultimate goals? Does
        your deity have a special task in mind for you? Or are
        you striving to prove yourself worthy of a great quest?
    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="cleric_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Spellcasting,
        \nDivine Domain
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Channel Divinity (1/rest)
        \nDivine Domain Feature
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_5th_lvl_abilities">
        Destroy Undead (CR 1/2)
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Channel Divinity (2/rest)
        \nDivine Domain Feature
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_7th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement,
        \nDestroy Undead (CR 1),
        \nDivine Domain Feature
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_9th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Divine Intervention
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_11th_lvl_abilities">
        Destroy Undead(CR 2)
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_13th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Destroy Undead (CR 3)
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_15th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_17th_lvl_abilities">
        Destroy Undead (CR 4),
        \nDivine Domain Feature
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Channel Divinity (3/rest)
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Divine Intervention \nimprovement
    </string>

    //---------------------------------------------------------Spell Table---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="cleric_table2_label">
        Spells Table
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_table2_value2_label">
        Cantrips Known
    </string>


    <string name="cleric_table2_value2_1to3_values">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_table2_value2_4to9_values">
        4
    </string>

    <string name="cleric_table2_value2_10to20_values">
        5
    </string>



    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="clericFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a cleric, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="clericHp">
         <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d8 per cleric lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 8 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d8(or 5) + Constitution Modifier per cleric level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="clericProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> Light Armor, medium armor, shields
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> All simple weapons
        \n<b>Tools:</b> None
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Wisdom, Charisma
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose two from History, Insight, Medicine, Persuation and Religion
    </string>

    <string name="clericEquipment">
        You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background
        \n\n- (a) a mace or (b) a warhammer (if proficient)
        \n- (a) scale mail or (b) leather armor or (c) chain mail (if proficient)
        \n- (a) a light crossbow and 20 bolts or (b) any simple weapon
        \n- (a) a priests pack or (b) an explorers pack
        \n- (a) a shield and holy symbol
    </string>


    //------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//





    <string name="clericCantrips">
        At 1st level, you know three cantrips of your choice from
        the cleric spell list. You learn additional cleric cantrips
        of your choice at higher levels, as shown in the Cantrips
        Known column of the Cleric table.
    </string>

    <string name="ClericPreparingAndCastingSpells">
        The Cleric table shows how many spell slots you have
        to cast your spells of 1st level and higher. To cast one of
        these spells, you must expend a slot of the spell’s level
        or higher. You regain all expended spell slots when you
        finish a long rest.
        \n\nYou prepare the list of cleric spells that are available
        for you to cast, choosing from the cleric spell list. When
        you do so, choosea number of cleric spells equal to
        your <b>Wisdom modifier + your cleric level (minimum of
        one spell).</b> The spells must be of a level for which you
        have spell slots.
        \n\nFor example, if you are a 3rd-level cleric, you have four
        1st-level and two 2nd-level spell slots. With a Wisdom
        of 16, your list of prepared spells can include six spells
        of 1st or 2nd level, in any combination. If you prepare
        the 1st-level spell cure wounds, you can cast it using
        a 1st-level or 2nd-level slot. Casting the spell doesn’t
        remove it from your list of prepared spells.
        \n\nYou can change your list of prepared spells when you
        finish a long rest. Preparing a new list o f cleric spells
        requires time spent in prayer and meditation: at least 1
        minute per spell level for each spell on your list.
    </string>


    <string name="clericSpelLCastingAbility">
        Wisdom is your spellcasting ability for your cleric spells.
        The power of your spells comes from your devotion to
        your deity. You use your Wisdom whenever a cleric spell
        refers to your spellcasting ability. In addition, you use
        your Wisdom modifier when setting the saving throw
        DC for a cleric spell you cast and when making an
        attack roll w ith one.
    </string>

    <string name="clericSpellSave">
        <b>Spell Save DC</b> = 8 + your proficiency bonus + your wisdom modifier
        \n\n
        <b>Spell Attack Modifier</b> = your proficiency bonus + your wisdom modifier
    </string>

    <string name="clericRitualCasting">
        You can cast a cleric spell as a ritual if that spell has the
        ritual tag and you have the spell prepared.
    </string>

    <string name="clericSpellcastingFocus">
        You can use a holy sym bol (found in chapter 5 of Players Handbook) as a
        spellcasting focus for your cleric spells.
    </string>

    <string name="clericDivineDomain">
        Choose one domain related to your deity: Knowledge,
        Life, Light, Nature, Tempest, Trickery, or War. Each
        domain is detailed at the end of the class description,
        and each one provides examples of gods associated
        with it. Your choice grants you domain spells and other
        features when you choose it at 1st level. It also grants
        you additional ways to use Channel Divinity when you
        gain that feature at 2nd level, and additional benefits at
        6th, 8th, and 17th levels.
    </string>

    <string name="clericDomainSpells">
        Each domain has a list of spells—its domain spells—
        that you gain at the cleric levels noted in the domain
        description. Once you gain a domain spell, you always
        have it prepared, and it doesn’t count against the
        number of spells you can prepare each day.
        If you have a domain spell that doesn’t appear on the
        cleric spell list, the spell is nonetheless a cleric spell for you.
    </string>

    <string name="clericChannelDivinity">
        At 2nd level, you gain the ability to channel divine
        energy directly from your deity, using that energy to fuel
        magical effects. You start with two such effects: Turn
        Undead and an effect determined by your domain. Some
        domains grant you additional effects as you advance in
        levels, as noted in the domain description.
        \n\nWhen you use your Channel Divinity, you choose
        which effect to create. You must then finish a short or
        long rest to use your Channel Divinity again.
        \n\nSome Channel Divinity effects require saving throws.
        When you use such an effect from this class, the DC
        equals your cleric spell save DC.
        \n\nBeginning at 6th level, you can use your Channel
        Divinity twice between rests, and beginning at 18th level.
        you can use it three times between rests. When you finish
        a short or long rest, you regain your expended uses.
    </string>

    <string name="clericTurnUndead">
        As an action, you present your holy symbol and speak a
        prayer censuring the undead. Each undead that can see
        or hear you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom
        saving throw. If the creature fails its saving throw, it is
        turned for 1 minute or until it takes any damage.
        \n\nA turned creature must spend its turns trying to move
        as far away from you as it can, and it can’t willingly
        move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can’t take
        reactions. For its action, it can use only the Dash action
        or try to escape from an effect that prevents it from
        moving. If there’s nowhere to move, the creature can use
        the Dodge action.
   </string>

    <string name="clericDestroyUndead">
        Starting at 5th level, when an undead fails its saving
        throw against your Turn Undead feature, the creature is
        instantly destroyed if its challenge rating is at or below a
        certain threshold, as shown in the table below.
        \n\n
        <b>\t\tLvl \t\t\t\tDestroy Undead of Cr</b>
        \n\t\t5th\t\t\t\t1/2 or lower
        \n\t\t8th\t\t\t\t1 or lower
        \n\t\t11th\t\t\t\t2 or lower
        \n\t\t14th\t\t\t\t3 or lower
        \n\t\t17th\t\t\t\t4 or lower
    </string>

    <string name="clericDivineIntervention">
        Beginning at 10th level, you can call on your deity to
        intervene on your behalf when your need is great.
        \n\nImploring your deity’s aid requires you to use your
        action. Describe the assistance you seek, and roll
        percentile dice. If you roll a number equal to or lower
        than your cleric level, your deity intervenes. The DM
        chooses the nature of the intervention; the effect of any
        cleric spell or cleric domain spell would be appropriate.
        \n\nIf your deity intervenes, you can’t use this feature
        again for 7 days. Otherwise, you can use it again after
        you finish a long rest.
        \n\nAt 20th level, your call for intervention succeeds
        automatically, no roll required.
    </string>

    <string name="clericDivineDomains">
        In a pantheon, every deity has influence over different
        aspects of mortal life and civilization, called a deity’s
        domain. All the domains over which a deity has
        influence are called the deity’s portfolio. For example,
        the portfolio of the Greek god Apollo includes the
        domains of Know ledge, Life, and Light. As a cleric, you
        choose one aspect of your deity’s portfolio to emphasize,
        and you are granted p ow ers related to that dom ain.
        \n\nYour choice might correspond to a particular sect
        dedicated to your deity. Apollo, for example, could be
        worshiped in one region as Phoebus(“radiant”) Apollo,
        emphasizing his influence over the Light domain,
        and in a different place as Apollo Acesius(“healing”),
        emphasizing his association with the Life domain.
        Alternatively, your choice of domain could simply be a
        matter of personal preference, the aspect of the deity
        that appeals to you most.
        \n\nEach domain’s description gives examples of deities
        who have influence over that domain. Gods are included
        from the worlds of the Forgotten Realms, Greyhawk,
        Dragon lance, and Eberron campaign settings, as well as
        from the Celtic, Greek, Norse, and Egyptian pantheons
        of antiquity.
    </string>


    <string name="clericKnowledgeDomain">
        The gods of knowledge—including Oghma, Boccob ,
        Gilean, Aureon, and Thoth —value learning and
        understanding above all. Some teach that knowledge is
        to be gathered and shared in libraries and universities,
        or promote the practical knowledge of craft and
        invention. Some deities hoard knowledge and keep its
        secrets to themselves. And some promise their followers
        that they will gain tremendous power if they unlock the
        secrets of the multiverse. Followers of these gods study
        esoteric lore, collect old tomes, delve into the secret
        places of the earth, and learn all they can. Some gods
        of knowledge promote the practical knowledge of craft
        and invention, including smith deities like Gond, Reorx,
        Onatar, Moradin, Hephaestus, and Goibhniu.
    </string>

    <string name="clericKnowledgeDomainSpells">
        <b>\t\tLvl \t\t\t\tSpells</b>
        \n\t\t1st \t\t\t\tcommand,identify
        \n\t\t3rd \t\t\t\taugury, suggestion
        \n\t\t5th \t\t\t\tnondetection, speak with dead
        \n\t\t7th \t\t\t\tarcane eye, confusion
        \n\t\t9th \t\t\t\tlegend lore, scrying
    </string>

    <string name="clericBlessingofKnowledge">
        At 1st level, you learn two languages of your choice.
        You also become proficient in your choice of two of the
        follow in gskills: Arcana, History, Nature, or Religion.
        \n\nYour proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check
        you make that uses either of those skills.
    </string>

    <string name="clericKnowledgeOfTheAges">
        Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity
        to tap into a divine well of knowledge. As an action,
        you choose one skill or tool. For 10 minutes, you have
        proficiency with the chosen skill or tool.
    </string>

    <string name="clericReadThoughs">
        At 6th level, you can use your Channel Divinity to read a
        creature’s thoughts. You can then use your access to the
        creature’s mind to command it.
        \n\nAs an action, choose one creature that you can see
        within 60 feet of you. That creature must make a
        Wisdom saving throw. If the creature succeeds on the
        saving throw, you can’t use this feature on it again until
        you finish a long rest.
        \n\nIf the creature fails its save, you can read its surface
        thoughts (those foremost in its mind, reflecting its
        current emotions and what it is actively thinking
        about) when it is within 60 feet of you. This effect lasts
        for 1 minute.
        \n\nDuring that time, you can use your action to end this
        effect and cast the suggestion spell on the creature
        without expending a spell slot. The target automatically
        fails its saving throw against the spell.
    </string>

    <string name="clericPotentSpellcasting">
        Starting at 8th level, you add your Wisdom modifier to
        the damage you deal with any cleric cantrip.
    </string>

    <string name="clericVisionOfThePast">
        Starting at 17th level, you can call up visions of the
        past that relate to an object you hold or your immediate
        surroundings. You spend at least 1 minute in meditation
        and prayer, then receive dream like, shadowy glimpses
        of recent events. You can meditate in this way for a
        number of minutes equal to your Wisdom score and
        must maintain concentration during that time, as if you
        were casting a spell.
        \n\nOnce you use this feature, you can’t use it again until
        you finish a short or long rest.
        \n\n<b>Object Reading.</b> Holding an object as you meditate,
        you can see visions of the object’s previous owner.
        After meditating for 1 minute, you learn how the owner
        acquired and lost the object, as well as the most recent
        significant event involving the object and that owner.
        If the object was owned by another creature in the
        recent past (within a number of days equal to your
        Wisdom score), you can spend 1 additional minute
        for each owner to learn the same information about
        that creature.
        \n\n<b>Area Reading.</b> As you meditate, you see visions
        of recent events in your immediate vicinity (a room ,
        street, tunnel, clearing, or the like, up to a 50-foot cube),
        going back a number of days equal to your Wisdom
        score. For each minute you meditate, you learn about
        one significant event, beginning with the most recent.
        Significant events typically involve powerful emotions,
        such as battles and betrayals, marriages and murders,
        births and funerals. However, they might also include
        more mundane events that are nevertheless important
        in your current situation.
    </string>

    <string name="clericLifeDomain">
        The Life domain focuses on the vibrant positive
        energy—one of the fundamental forces of the universe—
        that sustains all life. The gods of life promote vitality
        and health through healing the sick and wounded,
        caring for those in need, and driving away the forces of
        death and undeath. Almost any non-evil deity can claim
        influence over this domain, particularly agricultural
        deities (such as Chauntea, Arawai, and Demeter), sun
        gods (such as Lathander, Pelor, and Re-Horakhty), gods
        of healing or endurance (such as Ilmater, Mishakal,
        Apollo, and Diancecht), and gods of home and
        community (such as Hestia, Hathor, and Boldrei).
    </string>

    <string name="clericLifeDomainSpells">
        \t\tCleric Level \t\t\t\tSpells
        \t\t1st \t\t\t\tbless, cure wounds
        \t\t3rd \t\t\t\tlesser restoration, spiritual weapon
        \t\t5th \t\t\t\tbeacon of hope, revivify
        \t\t7th \t\t\t\tdeath ward, guardian of faith
        \t\t9th \t\t\t\tmass cure wounds, raise dead
    </string>

    <string name="lericBonusProficiency">
        When you choose this domain at 1st level, you gain
        proficiency with heavy armor.
    </string>

    <string name="clericDiscipleOfLight">
        Also starting at 1st level, your healing spells are more
        effective. Whenever you use a spell of 1st level or higher
        to restore hit points to a creature, the creature regains
        additional hit points equal to 2+ the spell’s level.
    </string>

    <string name="clericPreserveLife">
        Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity
        to heal the badly injured.
        \n\nAs an action, you present your holy symbol and
        evoke healing energy that can restore a number of hit
        points equal to five times your cleric level. Choose any
        creatures within 30 feet of you, and divide those hit
        points among them. This feature can restore a creature
        to no more than half of its hit point maximum . You can’t
        use this feature on an undead or a construct.
    </string>

    <string name="clericBlessedHealer">
        Beginning at 6th level, the healing spells you cast on
        others heal you as well. When you cast a spell of 1st
        level or higher that restores hit points to a creature
        other than you, you regain hit points equal to 2+ the
        spell’s level.
    </string>

    <string name="clericDivineStrike">
        At 8th level, you gain the ability to infuse your weapon
        strikes with divine energy. Once on each of your turns
        when you hit a creature with a weapon attack, you can
        cause the attack to deal an extra 1d8 radiant damage to
        the target. When you reach 14th level, the extra damage
        in creases to 2d8.
    </string>

    <string name="clericSupremeHealing">
        Starting at 17th level, when you would normally roll
        one or more dice to restore hit points with a spell, you
        instead use the highest number possible for each die.
        For example, instead of restoring 2d6 hit points to a
        creature, you restore 12.
    </string>

    <string name="clericLightDomain">
        Gods of light—including Helm, Lathander, Pholtus,
        Branchala, the Silver Flame, Belenus, Apollo, and
        Re-Horakhty — promote the ideals of rebirth and
        renewal, truth, vigilance, and beauty, often using the
        symbol of the sun. Some of these gods are portrayed
        as the sun itself or as a charioteer who guides the sun
        across the sky. Others are tireless sentinels whose eyes
        pierce every shadow and see through every deception.
        Some are deities of beauty and artistry, who teach that
        art is a vehicle for the soul's improvement. Clerics of a
        god of light are enlightened souls infused with radiance
        and the power of their gods’ discerning vision, charged
        with chasing away lies and burning away darkness.
    </string>

    <string name="clericLightDomainSpells">
        \t\tCleric Level \t\t\t\tSpells
        \t\t1st \t\t\t\tburning hands, faerie fire
        \t\t3rd \t\t\t\tflaming sphere, scorching ray
        \t\t5th \t\t\t\tdaylight, fireball
        \t\t7th \t\t\t\tguardian of faith, wall of fire
        \t\t9th \t\t\t\tflame strike, scrying
    </string>

    <string name="clericBonusCantrip">
        When you choose this domain at 1st level, you gain the
        light cantrip if you don’t already know it.
    </string>

    <string name="clericWardingFlare">
        Also at 1st level, you can interpose divine light between
        yourself and an attacking enemy. When you are attacked
        by a creature within 30 feet of you that you can see,
        you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on
        the attack roll, causing light to flare before the attacker
        before it hits or misses. An attacker that can’t be blinded
        is immune to this feature.
        \n\nYou can use this feature a number of times equal to
        your Wisdom modifier (a minim um of once). You regain
        all expended uses when you finish a long rest.
    </string>

    <string name="clericRadiantOfTheDawn">
        Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity
        to harness sunlight, banishing darkness and dealing
        radiant damage to your foes.
        \n\nAs an action, you present your holy symbol, and any
        magical darkness within 30 feet of you is dispelled.
        Additionally, each hostile creature within 30 feet of
        you must make a Constitution saving throw. A creature
        takes radiant damage equal to 2d10 + your cleric level
        on a failed saving throw, and half as much damage on a
        successful one. A creature that has total cover from you
        is not affected.
    </string>

    <string name="clericImprovedFlare">
        Starting at 6th level, you can also use your Warding
        Flare feature when a creature that you can see within
        30 feet of you attacks a creature other than you.
    </string>

    <string name="clericCoronaOfLight">
        Starting at 17th level, you can use your action to activate
        an aura of sunlight that lasts for 1 minute or until you
        dismiss it using another action. You emit bright light in
        a 60-foot radius and dim light 30 feet beyond that. Your
        enemies in the bright light have disadvantage on saving
        throws against any spell that deals fire or radiant damage.
    </string>

    <string name="clericNatureDomain">
        Gods of nature are as varied as the natural world
        itself, from inscrutable gods of the deep forests (such
        as Silvanus, Obad-Hai, Chislev, Balinor, and Pan) to
        friendly deities associated with particular springs and
        groves (such as Eldath). Druids revere nature as a
        whole and might serve one of these deities, practicing
        mysterious rites and reciting all-but-forgotten prayers in
        their own secret tongue. But many of these gods have
        clerics as well, champions  who take a more active role
        in advancing the interests of a particular nature god.
        These clerics might hunt the evil monstrosities that
        despoil the woodlands, bless the harvest of the faithful,
        or wither the crops of those who anger their gods.
    </string>

    <string name="clericNatureDomainSpells">
        \t\tCleric Level \t\t\t\tSpells
        \t\t1st \t\t\t\tanimal friendship, speak with animals
        \t\t3rd \t\t\t\tbarskin, spikegrow
        \t\t5th \t\t\t\tplant growth, wind wall
        \t\t7th \t\t\t\tdominate beast, grasping vine
        \t\t9th \t\t\t\tinspect plague, tree stride
    </string>

    <string name="clericAcolyteOfNature">
        At 1st level, you learn one druid cantrip of your choice.
        You also gain proficiency in one of the following skills of
        your choice: Animal Handling, Nature, or Survival.
    </string>

    <string name="clericCharmAnimals">
        Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity
        to charm animals and plants.
        \n\nAs an action, you present your holy symbol and invoke
        the name of your deity. Each beast or plant creature that
        can see you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom
        saving throw. If the creature fails its saving throw, it is
        charmed by you for 1 minute or until it takes damage.
        While it is charmed by you, it is friendly to you and other
        creatures you designate.
    </string>

    <string name="clericDampenElements">
        Starting at 6th level, w hen you or a creature within 30
        feet of you takes acid, cold, fire, lightning, or thunder
        damage, you can use your reaction to grant resistance to
        the creature against that instance of the damage.
    </string>

    <string name="clericMasterOfNature">
        At 17th level, you gain the ability to command animals
        and plant creatures. While creatures are charmed by
        your Charm Animals and Plants feature, you can take
        a bonus action on your turn to verbally command what
        each of those creatures will do on its next turn.
    </string>

    <string name="clericTempestDomain">
        Gods whose portfolios include the Tempest domain -
        including Talos, Umberlee, Kord, Zeboim , the
        Devourer, Zeus, and Thor—govern storms, sea, and
        sky. They include gods of lightning and thunder, gods
        of earthquakes, some fire gods, and certain gods of
        violence, physical strength, and courage. In some
        pantheons, a god of this domain rules over other deities
        and is known for swift justice delivered by thunderbolts.
        In the pantheons of seafaring people, gods of this
        domain are ocean deities and the patrons of sailors.
        Tempest gods send their clerics to inspire fear in the
        common folk, either to keep those folk on the path of
        righteousness or to encourage them to offers a crifices of
        propitiation to ward off divine wrath.
    </string>

    <string name="clericTempestDomainSpells">
        \t\tCleric Level \t\t\t\tSpells
        \t\t1st \t\t\t\tanimal friendship, speak with animals
        \t\t3rd \t\t\t\tbarskin, spikegrow
        \t\t5th \t\t\t\tplant growth, wind wall
        \t\t7th \t\t\t\tdominate beast, grasping vine
        \t\t9th \t\t\t\tinspect plague, tree stride
    </string>

    <string name="clericTempestBonusProfitiency">
        At 1st level, you gain proficiency with martial weapons
        and heavy armor.
    </string>

    <string name="clericWrathOfTheStorm">
        Also at 1st level, you can thunderously rebuke attackers.
        When a creature within 5 feet of you that you can see
        hits you with an attack, you can use your reaction to
        cause the creature to make a Dexterity saving throw.
        The creature takes 2d8 lightning or thunder damage
        (your choice) on a failed saving throw, and half as much
        damage on a successful one.
        \n\nYou can use this feature a number of times equal to
        your Wisdom modifier (a minimum of once). You regain
        all expended uses when you finish a long rest.
    </string>

    <string name="clericDestructiveWrath">
        Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity
        to wield the power of the storm with unchecked ferocity.
        \n\nWhen you roll lightning or thunder damage, you can
        use your Channel Divinity to deal maximum damage,
        instead of rolling.
    </string>

    <string name="clericThunderboltStrike">
        At 6th level, when you deal lightning damage to a Large
        or smaller creature, you can also push it up to 10 feet
        away from you.
    </string>

    <string name="clericStormborn">
        At 17th level, you have a flying speed equal to
        your current walking speed whenever you are not
        underground or indoors.
    </string>

    <string name="clericTrickerDomain">
        Gods of trickery—such as Tymora, Beshaba,
        Olidammara, the Traveler, Garl Glittergold, and
        Loki — are mischief-makers and instigators who stand
        as a constant challenge to the accepted order among
        both gods and mortals. They’re patrons of thieves,
        scoundrels, gamblers, rebels, and liberators. Their
        clerics are a disruptive force in the world, puncturing
        pride, mocking tyrants, stealing from the rich, freeing
        captives, and flouting hollow traditions. They prefer
        subterfuge, pranks, deception, and theft rather than
        direct confrontation.
    </string>

    <string name="clericTricksterDomainSpells">
        \t\tCleric Level \t\t\t\tSpells
        \t\t1st \t\t\t\tcharm person, disguise self
        \t\t3rd \t\t\t\tmirror image, pass without a trace
        \t\t5th \t\t\t\tblink, dispel magic
        \t\t7th \t\t\t\tdimension door, polymorph
        \t\t9th \t\t\t\tdominate person, modify memory
    </string>

    <string name="clericBessingOfTrickster">
        Starting when you choose this domain at 1st level, you
        can use your action to touch a willing creature other
        than yourself to give it advantage on Dexterity (Stealth)
        checks. This blessing lasts for 1 hour or until you use
        this feature again.
    </string>

    <string name="clericInvokeDuplicity">
        Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity
        to create an illusory duplicate of yourself.
        \n\nAs an action, you create a perfect illusion of
        yourself that lasts for 1 minute, or until you lose your
        concentration (as if you were concentrating on a spell).
        The illusion appears in an unoccupied space that you
        can see within 30 feet of you. As a bonus action on your
        turn, you can move the illusion up to 30 feet to a space
        you can see, but it must remain within 120 feet of you.
        \n\nFor the duration, you can cast spells as though you
        were in the illusion’s space, but you must use your own
        senses. Additionally, when both you and your illusion
        are within 5 feet of a creature that can see the illusion,
        you have advantage on attack rolls against that creature,
        given how distracting the illusion is to the target.
    </string>

    <string name="clericCloakOfShadow">
        Starting at 6th level, you can u se your Channel
        Divinity to vanish.
        As an action, you become invisible until the end of your
        next turn. You become visible if you attack or cast a spell.
    </string>

    <string name="clericImproveDuplicity">
        At 17th level, you can create up to four duplicates
        of yourself, instead of one, w hen you use Invoke
        Duplicity. As a bonus action on your turn, you can
        move any number of them up to 30 feet, to a maximum
        range of 120 feet.
    </string>

    <string name="clericWarDomain">
        War has many manifestations. It can make heroes of
        ordinary people. It can be desperate and horrific, with
        acts of cruelty and cowardice eclipsing instances of
        excellence and courage. In either case, the gods of war
        watch over warriors and reward them for their great
        deeds. The clerics of such gods excel in battle, inspiring
        others to fight the good fight or offering acts of violence
        as prayers. Gods of war include champions of honor
        and chivalry (such as Torm, Heironeous, and Kiri-
        Jolith) as well as gods of destruction and pillage (such
        as Erythnul, the Fury, Gruumsh, and Ares) and gods of
        conquest and domination (such as Bane, Hextor, and
        Maglubiyet). Other wargods (such as Tempus, Nike,
        and Nuada) take a more neutral stance, promoting war
        in all its manifestations and supporting warriors in any
        circumstance.
    </string>

    <string name="clericWarDomainSpells">
        \t\tCleric Level \t\t\t\tSpells
        \t\t1st \t\t\t\tdivine favor, shield of faith
        \t\t3rd \t\t\t\tmagic weapon, spiritual weapon
        \t\t5th \t\t\t\tcrusaders mantle, spirit guardian
        \t\t7th \t\t\t\tfreedom of movement, stoneskin
        \t\t9th \t\t\t\tflame strike, hold monster
    </string>

    <string name="clericWarPriest">
        From 1st level, your god delivers bolts of inspiration to
        you while you are engaged in battle. When you use the
        Attack action, you can make one weapon attack as a
        bonus action.
        \n\nYou can use this feature a number of times equal to
        your Wisdom modifier (a minimum of once). You regain
        all expended uses when you finish a long rest.
    </string>

    <string name="clericGuidedStrike">
        Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Channel Divinity
        to strike with supernatural accuracy. When you make
        an attack roll, you can use your Channel Divinity to gain
        a +10 bonus to the roll. You make this choice after you
        see the roll, but before the DM says whether the attack
        hits or misses.
    </string>

    <string name="clericWarGodsBlessing">
        At 6th level, when a creature within 30 feet of you
        makes an attack roll, you can use your reaction to grant
        that creature a +10 bonus to the roll, using your Channel
        Divinity. You make this choice after you see the roll, but
        before the DM says whether the attack hits or misses.
    </string>

    <string name="clericAvatarOfBattle">
        At 17th level, you gain resistance to bludgeoning, piercing,
        and slashing damage from non magical weapons.
    </string>

</resources>