<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="druid_introduction">
        Holding high a gnarled staff wreathed with holly, an elf
        summons the fury of the storm and calls down explosive
        bolts of lightning to smite the torch-carrying orcs who
        threaten her forest.

        \n\nCrouching out of sight on a high tree branch in the
        form of a leopard, a human peers out of the jungle at the
        strange construction of a temple of Evil Elemental Air,
        keeping a close eye on the cultists’ activities.

        \n\nSwinging a blade formed of pure fire, a half-elf
        charges into a mass of skeletal soldiers, sundering
        the unnatural magic that gives the foul creatures the
        mocking semblance of life.

        \n\nWhether calling on the elemental forces of nature or
        emulating the creatures of the animal world, druids are
        an embodiment of nature’s resilience, cunning, and fury.
        They claim no mastery over nature. Instead, they see
        them selves as extensions of nature’s indomitable will.
    </string>

    <string name="creating_druid_string">
        When making a druid, consider why your character has
        such a close bond with nature. Perhaps your character
        lives in a society where the Old Faith still thrives, or was
        raised by a druid after being abandoned in the depths
        of a forest. Perhaps your character had a dramatic
        encounter with the spirits of nature, coming face to
        face with a giant eagle or dire wolf and surviving the
        experience. Maybe your character was born during an
        epic storm or a volcanic eruption, which was interpreted as a sign that becoming a druid
        was part of your character’s destiny.
        \n\nHave you always been an adventurer
        as part o f your druidic calling, or did you
        first spend time as a caretaker of a sacred
        grove or spring? Perhaps your homeland was
        befouled by evil, and you took up an adventuring life in
        hopes of finding a new home or purpose.
    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="druid_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Druidic,
        \nSpellcasting
    </string>

    <string name="druid_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Wild Shape,
        \nDruid Circle
    </string>

    <string name="druid_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Wild Shape Improvement
        \nAbility Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_5th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Druid Circle Feature
    </string>

    <string name="druid_7th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Wild Shape Improvement,
        \nAbility Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_9th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Druid Circle Feature
    </string>

    <string name="druid_11th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_13th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Druid Circle Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_15th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_17th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Timeless Body,
        \nBeast Spells
    </string>

    <string name="druid_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Archdruid
    </string>

    //---------------------------------------------------------Spell Table---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="druid_table2_label">
        Spells Table
    </string>

    <string name="druid_table2_value2_label">
        Cantrips Known
    </string>


    <string name="druid_table2_value2_1to3_values">
        2
    </string>

    <string name="druid_table2_value2_4to9_values">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="druid_table2_value2_10to20_values">
        4
    </string>



    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="druidFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a druid, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="druidHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d8 per druid lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 8 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d8(or 5) + Constitution Modifier per druid level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="druidProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> Light Armor, Medium Armor, Shields (druids will not wear armor or use shields made of metal)
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Clubs, Daggers, Darts, Javelins, Maces, Quarterstaffs, Scimitar, Sickles, Slings, Spears
        \n<b>Tools:</b> Herbalism Kit
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Intelligence, Wisdom
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose two from Arcana, Animal Handling, Insight, Medicine, Nature, Perception, Religion, Survival
    </string>

    <string name="druidEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background:
        \n\n- (a) a wooden shield or (b) any simple weapon
        \n- (a) a scimitar or (b) any simple melee weapon
        \n- Leather Armor, an Explorers Pack and a Druidic Focus
    </string>



    //------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

</resources>