<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="druid_introduction">
        Holding high a gnarled staff wreathed with holly, an elf
        summons the fury of the storm and calls down explosive
        bolts of lightning to smite the torch-carrying orcs who
        threaten her forest.

        \n\nCrouching out of sight on a high tree branch in the
        form of a leopard, a human peers out of the jungle at the
        strange construction of a temple of Evil Elemental Air,
        keeping a close eye on the cultists’ activities.

        \n\nSwinging a blade formed of pure fire, a half-elf
        charges into a mass of skeletal soldiers, sundering
        the unnatural magic that gives the foul creatures the
        mocking semblance of life.

        \n\nWhether calling on the elemental forces of nature or
        emulating the creatures of the animal world, druids are
        an embodiment of nature’s resilience, cunning, and fury.
        They claim no mastery over nature. Instead, they see
        them selves as extensions of nature’s indomitable will.
    </string>

    <string name="creating_druid_string">
        When making a druid, consider why your character has
        such a close bond with nature. Perhaps your character
        lives in a society where the Old Faith still thrives, or was
        raised by a druid after being abandoned in the depths
        of a forest. Perhaps your character had a dramatic
        encounter with the spirits of nature, coming face to
        face with a giant eagle or dire wolf and surviving the
        experience. Maybe your character was born during an
        epic storm or a volcanic eruption, which was interpreted as a sign that becoming a druid
        was part of your character’s destiny.
        \n\nHave you always been an adventurer
        as part o f your druidic calling, or did you
        first spend time as a caretaker of a sacred
        grove or spring? Perhaps your homeland was
        befouled by evil, and you took up an adventuring life in
        hopes of finding a new home or purpose.
    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="druid_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Druidic,
        \nSpellcasting
    </string>

    <string name="druid_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Wild Shape,
        \nDruid Circle
    </string>

    <string name="druid_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Wild Shape Improvement
        \nAbility Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_5th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Druid Circle Feature
    </string>

    <string name="druid_7th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Wild Shape Improvement,
        \nAbility Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_9th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Druid Circle Feature
    </string>

    <string name="druid_11th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_13th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Druid Circle Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_15th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_17th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="druid_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Timeless Body,
        \nBeast Spells
    </string>

    <string name="druid_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="druid_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Archdruid
    </string>

    //---------------------------------------------------------Spell Table---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="druid_table2_label">
        Spells Table
    </string>

    <string name="druid_table2_value2_label">
        Cantrips Known
    </string>


    <string name="druid_table2_value2_1to3_values">
        2
    </string>

    <string name="druid_table2_value2_4to9_values">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="druid_table2_value2_10to20_values">
        4
    </string>



    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="druidFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a druid, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="druidHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d8 per druid lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 8 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d8(or 5) + Constitution Modifier per druid level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="druidProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> Light Armor, Medium Armor, Shields (druids will not wear armor or use shields made of metal)
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Clubs, Daggers, Darts, Javelins, Maces, Quarterstaffs, Scimitar, Sickles, Slings, Spears
        \n<b>Tools:</b> Herbalism Kit
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Intelligence, Wisdom
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose two from Arcana, Animal Handling, Insight, Medicine, Nature, Perception, Religion, Survival
    </string>

    <string name="druidEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background:
        \n\n- (a) a wooden shield or (b) any simple weapon
        \n- (a) a scimitar or (b) any simple melee weapon
        \n- Leather Armor, an Explorers Pack and a Druidic Focus
    </string>
    
    //--------------------------------------------------ABILITIES----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="druidDruidicTitle">
        Druidic
    </string>
    <string name="druidDruidic">
        You know Druidic, the secret language of druids. You can speak the language and use it to leave hidden messages.
        You and others who know this language automatically spot such a message. 
        Others spot the message’s presence with a successful DC  15 Wisdom (Perception) 
        check but can’t decipher it without magic.
    </string>
    
    <string name="druidWildShapeTitle">
        Wild Shape
    </string>
    <string name="druidWIldShape">
        Starting at 2nd level, you can use your action to magically assume the shape of a beast that you have seen before.
        You can use this feature twice. You regain expended uses when you finish a short or long rest.

        \n\nYour druid level determines the beasts you can transform into,
        as shown in the Beast Shapes table. At 2nd level, for example,
        you can transform into any beast that has a challenge rating of 1/4 or lower
        that doesn’t have a flying or swimming speed

        \n\n
        <b>Beast Shapes</b>
        \n\nLevel   \t\t\tMax Cr.   \t\t\tLimitations       \t\t\tExample
        \n2nd   \t\t\t1/4   \t\t\tNo flying/swimming speed   \t\t\tWolf
        \n4th   \t\t\t1/2   \t\t\tNo flying speed             \t\t\tCrocodile
        \n8th   \t\t\t1   \t\t\t-                               \t\t\tGiant Eagle

        \n\n
        You can stay in a beast shape for a number of hours equal
        to half your druid level (rounded down). You then revert to your
        normal form unless you expend another use of this feature. You can
        revert to your normal form earlier by using a bonus action on your
        turn. You automatically revert if you fall unconscious, drop to 0 hit points, or die

        \n\n<b>While you are transformed, the following rules apply:</b>
        \n\n
        Your game statistics are replaced by the statistics of the beast,
        but you retain your alignment, personality, and Intelligence,
        Wisdom, and Charisma scores. You also retain all of your skill
        and saving throw proficiencies, in addition to gaining those of the creature.
        If the creature has the same proficiency as you and the bonus in its stat block
        is higher than yours, use the creature’s bonus instead of yours. If the creature
        has any legendary or lair actions, you can't use them

        \n\n
        When you transform, you assume the beast’s hit points and Hit Dice.
        When you revert to your normal form, you return to the number of hit points
        you had before you transformed. However, if you revert as a result of dropping
        to 0 hit points, any excess damage carries over to your normal form. For example,
        if you take  10 damage in animal form and have only 1 hit point left, you revert
        and take 9 damage. As long as the excess damage doesn’t
        reduce your normal form to 0 hit points, you aren’t knocked unconscious

        \n\n
        You can’t cast spells, and your ability to speak or take any action that
        requires hands is limited to the capabilities of your beast form.
        Transforming doesn’t break your concentration on a spell you’ve already cast,
        however, or prevent you from taking actions that are part of a spell,
        such as call lightning, that you’ve already cast

        \n\n
        You retain the benefit of any features from your class, race,
        or other source and can use them if the new form is physically capable of doing so.
        However, you can’t use any of your special senses, such as darkvision,
        unless your new form also has that sense

        \n\n
        You choose whether your equipment falls to the ground in your space,
        merges into your new form, or is worn by it. Worn equipment functions as normal,
        but the DM decides whether it is practical for the new form to wear a piece of equipment,
        based on the creature’s shape and size. Your equipment doesn’t
        change size or shape to match the new form, and any equipment
        that the new form can’t wear must either fall to the ground or merge with it.
        Equipment that merges with the form has no effect until you leave the form.
    </string>

    <string name="druidTimelessBodyTitle">
        Timeless Body
    </string>
    <string name="druidTimelessBody">
        Starting at 18th level, the primal magic that you wield 
        causes you to age more slowly. For every 10 years that pass, your body ages only 1 year
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="druidBeastSpellsTitle">
        Beast Spells
    </string>
    <string name="druidBeastSpells">
        Beginning at 18th level, you can cast many of your druid spells 
        in any shape you assume using W ild Shape. You can perform the somatic 
        and verbal components of a druid spell while in a beast shape, 
        but you aren’t able to provide material components
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="druidArchdruidTitle">
        Archdruid
    </string>
    <string name="druidArchdruid">
        At 20th level, you can use your Wild Shape an unlimited number of times.
        \n\nAdditionally, you can ignore the verbal and somatic components of your druid spells,
        as well as any material components that lack a cost and aren’t consumed by a spell.
        You gain this benefit in both your normal shape and your beast shape from Wild Shape.
    </string>

    //--------------------------------------------------CLASS SCHOOLS----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="druidDruidCircleTitle">
        Druid Circles
    </string>
    <string name="druidDruidCircle">
        Though their organization is invisible to most outsiders,
        druids are part of a society that spans the land, ignoring
        political borders. All druids are nominally members of this
        druidic society, though som e individuals are so isolated that
        they have never seen any high-ranking members of the society or participated
        in druidic gatherings. Druids recognize each other as brothers and sisters.
        Like creatures of the wilderness, however, druids sometimes compete with or even prey on each other.

        \n\n
        At a local scale, druids are organized into circles that share certain perspectives on nature, balance, and the way of the druid.

        \n\n
        At 2nd level, you choose to identify with a circle of druids: the Circle of the Land or the Circle of the Moon, 
        both detailed at the end of the class description. Your choice grants you features at 2nd level and again at 6th,  10th, and  14th level.
    </string>

    
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandTitle">
        Circle of the Land
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLand">
        The Circle of the Land is made up of mystics and sages who safeguard ancient
        knowledge and rites through a vast oral tradition. These druids meet within sacred
        circles of trees or standing stones to whisper primal secrets in Druidic.
        The circle’s wisest members preside as the chief priests of communities that hold to
        the Old Faith and serve as advisors to the rulers of those folk.As a member of this
        circle, your magic is influenced by the land where you were initiated into the circle’s mysterious rites.
    </string>

    
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandBonusCantripTitle">
        Bonus Cantrip
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandBonusCantrip">
        When you choose this circle at 2nd level, you learn one additional druid cantrip of your choice.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandNaturalRecoveryTitle">
        Natural Recovery
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandNaturalRecovery">
        Starting at 2nd level, you can regain som e of your magical energy by
        sitting in meditation and communing with nature. During a short rest,
        you choose expended spell slots to recover. The spell slots can have a
        combined level that is equal to or less than half your druid level (rounded up),
        and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher. You can’t use this feature
        again until you finish a long rest.
        
        \n\n
        For example, when you are a 4th-level druid, you can recover up to two levels
        worth of spell slots. You can recover either a 2nd-level slot or two  1st-level slots.
    </string>
    
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandCircleSpellsTitle">
        Circle Spells
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandCircleSpells">
        Your mystical connection to the land infuses you with the
        ability to cast certain spells. At 3rd, 5th, 7th, and 9th
        level you gain access to circle spells connected to the
        land where you became a druid. Choose that land—arctic,
        coast, desert, forest, grassland, mountain, swamp, or
        Underdark—and consult the associated list of spells.

        \n\n
        Once you gain access to a circle spell,
        you always have it prepared, and it doesn’t
        count against the number of spells you can prepare each day.
        If you gain access to a spell that doesn’t appear on the druid
        spell list, the spell is nonetheless a druid spell for you

        \n\n
        <b>Arctic</b>
        \n\n
        Level \t\t\t Circle Spells
        \n 3rd \t\t\t hold person, spike growth
        \n 5th \t\t\t sleet storm, slow
        \n 7th \t\t\t freedom of movement, ice storm
        \n 9th \t\t\t commune with nature, cone of cold

         \n\n
        <b>Coast</b>
        \n\n
        Level \t\t\t Circle Spells
        \n 3rd \t\t\t mirror image, misty step
        \n 5th \t\t\t water breathing, water walk
        \n 7th \t\t\t control water, freedom of movement
        \n 9th \t\t\t conjure elemental, scrying

         \n\n
        <b>Desert</b>
        \n\n
        Level \t\t\t Circle Spells
        \n 3rd \t\t\t blur, silence
        \n 5th \t\t\t create food and water, protection from energy
        \n 7th \t\t\t blight, hallucinatory terrain
        \n 9th \t\t\t insect plague, wall of stone

         \n\n
        <b>Forest</b>
        \n\n
        Level \t\t\t Circle Spells
        \n 3rd \t\t\t barskin, spider climb
        \n 5th \t\t\t call lightning, plant growth
        \n 7th \t\t\t divination, freedom of movement
        \n 9th \t\t\t commune with nature, tree stride

         \n\n
        <b>Grassland</b>
        \n\n
        Level \t\t\t Circle Spells
        \n 3rd \t\t\t invisibility, pass without a trace
        \n 5th \t\t\t daylight, haste
        \n 7th \t\t\t freedom of movement, divination
        \n 9th \t\t\t dream, insect plague

         \n\n
        <b>Mountain</b>
        \n\n
        Level \t\t\t Circle Spells
        \n 3rd \t\t\t spider climb, spike growth
        \n 5th \t\t\t lightning bolt, meld into stone
        \n 7th \t\t\t stone shape, stoneskin
        \n 9th \t\t\t passwall, wall of stone

         \n\n
        <b>Swamp</b>
        \n\n
        Level \t\t\t Circle Spells
        \n 3rd \t\t\t darkness, Melfs acid arrow
        \n 5th \t\t\t water walk, stinking cloud
        \n 7th \t\t\t freedom of movement, locate creature
        \n 9th \t\t\t insect plague, scrying

         \n\n
        <b>Underdark</b>
        \n\n
        Level \t\t\t Circle Spells
        \n 3rd \t\t\t spider climb, web
        \n 5th \t\t\t gaseous form, stinking cloud
        \n 7th \t\t\t greater invisibility, stone shape
        \n 9th \t\t\t cloudkill, insect plague
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandLandsStrideTitle">
        Lands Stride
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandLandsStride">
        Starting at 6th level, moving through nonmagical
        difficult terrain costs you no extra movement.
        You can also pass through nonmagical plants without
        being slowed by them and without taking damage from them
        if they have thorns, spines, or a similar hazard.

        \n\n
        In addition, you have advantage on saving throws 
        against plants that are magically created or manipulated to 
        impede movement, such those created by the entangle spell
    </string>
    
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandNaturesWardTitle">
        Natures Ward
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandNaturesWard">
        When you reach  10th level, you can’t be 
        charmed or frightened by elementals or fey, 
        and you are immune to poison and disease.
    </string>

    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandNaturesSanctuaryTitle">
        Natures Sanctuary
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheLandNaturesSanctuary">
        When you reach  14th level, creatures of the natural world sense
        your connection to nature and become hesitant to attack you.
        When a beast or plant creature attacks you, that creature must
        make a Wisdom saving throw against your druid spell save DC.
        On a failed save, the creature must choose a different target,
        or the attack automatically misses. On a successful save, the
        creature is immune to this effect for 24 hours.

        \n\nThe creature is aware of this effect before it makes its attack against you.
    </string>


    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoonTitle">
        Circle of the Moon
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoon">
        Druids of the Circle of the M oon are fierce guardians of the wilds.
        Their order gathers under the full m oon to share news and trade warnings.
        They haunt the deepest parts of the wilderness, where they might go for weeks
        on end before crossing paths with another humanoid creature, let alone another druid.

        \n\n
        Changeable as the moon, a druid of this circle might prowl 
        as a great cat one night, soar over the treetops as an eagle 
        the next day, and crash through the undergrowth in bear form 
        to drive off a trespassing monster. The wild is in the druid's blood.
    </string>
    
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoonCombatWildShapeTitle">
        Combat Wild Shape
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoonCombatWildShape">
        W hen you choose this circle at 2nd level,
        you gain the ability to use Wild Shape on your
        turn as a bonus action, rather than as an action.

        \n\n
        Additionally, while you are transformed by 
        Wild Shape, you can use a bonus action to 
        expend one spell slot to regain  1d8 hit points per level of the spell slot expended.
    </string>

    
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoonCircleFormsTitle">
        Circle Forms
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoonCircleForms">
        The rites of your circle grant you the ability to transform into more
        dangerous animal forms. Starting at 2nd level, you can use your Wild
        Shape to transform into a beast with a challenge rating as high as
        1 (you ignore the Max. CR column of the Beast Shapes table, but must abide by the other limitations there).

        \n\n
        Starting at 6th level, you can transform into a beast with a challenge rating as high as your druid level divided by 3, rounded down.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoonPrimalStrikeTitle">
        primal Strike
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoonPrimalStrike">
        Starting at 6th level, your attacks in beast form count as magical 
        for the purpose of overcoming resistance and immunity to nonmagical attacks and damage.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoonElementalWildshapeTitle">
        Elemental Wild Shape
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoonElementalWldShape">
        At  10th level, you can expend two uses of Wild Shape 
        at the same time to transform into an air elemental, 
        an earth elemental, a fire elemental, or a water elemental.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoonThousandFormsTitle">
        Thousand Forms
    </string>
    <string name="druidCircleOfTheMoonThousandForms">
        By 14th level, you have learned to use magic to alter your physical
        form in more subtle ways. You can cast the alter self spell at will.
    </string>



</resources>