<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="fighter_introduction">
        A human in clanging plate armor holds her shield
        before her as she runs toward the massed goblins. An
        elf behind her, clad in studded leather armor, peppers
        the goblins with arrows loosed from his exquisite
        bow. The half-orc nearby shouts orders, helping
        the two combatants coordinate their assault to the
        best advantage.

        \n\nA dwarf in chain mail interposes his shield between
        the ogre’s club and his companion, knocking the deadly
        blow aside. His companion, a half-elf in scale armor,
        swings two scimitars in a blinding whirl as she circles
        the ogre, looking for a blind spot in its defenses.

        \n\nA gladiator fights for sport in an arena, a master with
        his trident and net, skilled at toppling foes and moving
        them around for the crowd’s delight—and his own
        tactical advantage. His opponent’s sword flares with
        blue light an instant before she sends lightning flashing
        forth to smite him.

        \n\nAll of these heroes are fighters, perhaps the most
        diverse class of characters in the worlds of Dungeons and
        Dragons. Questing knights, conquering overlords, royal
        champions, elite foot soldiers, hardened mercenaries,
        and bandit kings — as fighters, they all share an
        unparalleled mastery with weapons and armor, and a
        thorough knowledge of the skills of combat. And they
        are well acquainted with death, both meting it out and
        staring it defiantly in the face.
    </string>

    <string name="creating_fighter_string">
        As you build your fighter, think about two related
        elements of your characters background: Where did
        you get your combat training, and what set you apart
        from the mundane warriors around you? Were you
        particularly ruthless? Did you get extra help from a
        mentor, perhaps because of your exceptional dedication?
        What drove you to this training in the first place? A
        threat to your homeland, a thirst for revenge, or a need
        to prove yourself might all have been factors.

        \n\nYou might have enjoyed formal training in an oble’s
        army or in a local militia. Perhaps you trained in a war
        academy, learning strategy, tactics, and military history.
        Or you might be self-taught—unpolished but well tested.
        Did you take up the sword as a way to escape the limits
        of life on a farm, or are you following a proud family
        tradition? Where did you acquire your weapons and
        armor? They might have been military issue or family
        heirlooms, or perhaps you scrimped and saved for years
        to buy them. Your armaments are now among your
        most important possessions—the only things that stand
        between you and death’s embrace.
    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="fighter_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Fighting style,
        \nSecond Wind
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Action Surge (one use)
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        Martial Archetype
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_5th_lvl_abilities">
        Extra Attack
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_7th_lvl_abilities">
        Martial Archetype feature
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_9th_lvl_abilities">
        Indomitable (one use)
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Martial Archetype Feature
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_11th_lvl_abilities">
        Extra Attack (2)
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_13th_lvl_abilities">
        Indomitable (two uses)
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_15th_lvl_abilities">
        Martial Archetype Feature
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_17th_lvl_abilities">
        Action Surge (two uses),
        \nIndomitable (three uses)
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Martial Archetype Feature
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="fighter_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Extra Attack (3)
    </string>


    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="fighterFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a fighter, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="fighterHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d10 per fighter lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 10 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d10(or 6) + Constitution Modifier per fighter level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="fighterProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> All Armors, Shields
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Simple Weapons, Martial Weapons
        \n<b>Tools:</b> None
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Strength, Constitution
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose two from Acrobatics, Animal Handling, Athletics, History, Insight, Intimidation, Perception, Survival
    </string>

    <string name="fighterEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background:
        \n\n- (a) Chain Mail or (b) Leather, Longbow with 20 arrows
        \n- (a) a Martial Weapon and Shield or (b) two Martial Weapons
        \n- (a) a Light Crossbow and 20 Bolts or (b) two Handaxes
        \n- (a) a Dungeoners Pack or (b) an Explorers Pack
    </string>



    //------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
</resources>