<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="monk_introduction">
        Her fists a blur as they deflect an incoming hail of arrows,
        a half-elf springs over a barricade and throws herself
        into the massed ranks of hobgoblins on the other side.
        She whirls among them, knocking their blows aside and
        sending them reeling, until at last she stands alone.

        \n\nTaking a deep breath, a human covered in tattoos
        settles into a battle stance. As the first charging orcs
        reach him, he exhales and a blast of fire roars from his
        mouth, engulfing his foes.
        \n\nMoving with the silence of the night, a black-clad
        halfling steps into a shadow beneath an arch and
        emerges from another inky shadow on a balcony a
        stone’s throw away. She slides her blade free of its cloth-
        wrapped scabbard and peers through the open window
        at the tyrant prince, so vulnerable in the grip of sleep.

        \n\nWhatever their discipline, monks are united in their
        ability to magically harness the energy that flows in
        their bodies. Whether channeled as a striking display
        of combat prowess or a subtler focus of defensive ability
        and speed, this energy infuses all that a monk does.
    </string>

    <string name="creating_monk_string">
        As you make your monk character, think about your
        connection to the monastery where you learned your
        skills and spent your formative years. Were you an
        orphan or a child left on the monastery’s threshold? Did
        your parents promise you to the monastery in gratitude
        for aservice perform ed by the monks? Did you enter
        this secluded life to hide from a crime you committed?
        Or did you choose the monastic life for yourself?

        \n\nConsider why you left. Did the head of your monastery
        choose you for a particularly important mission beyond
        the cloister? Perhaps you were cast out because of
        some violation of the community’s rules. Did you dread
        leaving, or were you happy to go? Is there something
        you hope to accomplish outside the monastery? Are you
        eager to return to your home?

        \n\nAs a result of the structured life of a monastic
        community and the discipline required to harness ki,
        monks are almost always lawful in alignment.

    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="monk_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Unarmored Defense,
        \nMartial Arts
    </string>

    <string name="monk_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Ki,
        \nUnarmored Movement
    </string>

    <string name="monk_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        Monastic Tradition,
        \nDeflect Missiles
    </string>

    <string name="monk_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="monk_5th_lvl_abilities">
        Extra Attack,
        \nStunning Strike
    </string>

    <string name="monk_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Ki-empowered Strikes,
        \nMonastic Tradition Feature
    </string>

    <string name="monk_7th_lvl_abilities">
        Evasion,
        \nStillness of Mind
    </string>

    <string name="monk_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="monk_9th_lvl_abilities">
        Unarmored Movement Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="monk_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Purity of Body,
    </string>

    <string name="monk_11th_lvl_abilities">
        Monastic Tradition Feature
    </string>

    <string name="monk_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="monk_13th_lvl_abilities">
        Tongue of the Sun and Moon
    </string>

    <string name="monk_14th_lvl_abilities">
       Diamond Soul
    </string>

    <string name="monk_15th_lvl_abilities">
        Timeless Body
    </string>

    <string name="monk_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="monk_17th_lvl_abilities">
        Monastic Tradition Feature
    </string>

    <string name="monk_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Empty Body
    </string>

    <string name="monk_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="monk_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Perfect Self
    </string>

    //---------------------------------------------------------Spell Table---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="monk_table2_label">
        Monk Table
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value2_label">
        Martial Arts
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_label">
        Ki Points
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value2_1to4_values">
        1d4
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value2_5to10_values">
        1d6
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value2_11to16_values">
        1d8
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value2_17to20_values">
        1d10
    </string>



    <string name="monk_table2_value3_1values">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_2values">
        2
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_3values">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_4values">
        4
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_5values">
        5
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_6values">
        6
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_7values">
        7
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_8values">
        8
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_9values">
        9
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_10values">
        10
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_11values">
        11
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_12values">
        12
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_13values">
        13
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_14values">
        14
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_15values">
        15
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_16values">
        16
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_17values">
        17
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_18values">
        18
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_19values">
        19
    </string>

    <string name="monk_table2_value3_20values">
        20
    </string>

    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="monkFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a monk, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="monkHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d8 per monk lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 8 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d8(or 5) + Constitution Modifier per monk level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="monkProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> None
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Simple Weapons, Shortswords
        \n<b>Tools:</b> Choose one type of artisian's tools or one musical instrument
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Strength, Dexterity
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose two from Acrobatics, Athletics, History, Insight, Religion, Strength
    </string>

    <string name="monkEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background:
        \n\n- (a) a shortsword or (b) any simple weapon
        \n- (a) a dungeoners pack or (b) an explorers pack
        \n- 10 darts
    </string>



    //------------------------------------------------ABILITIES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="monkUnarmoredDefenceTitle">
        Unarmored Defence
    </string>
    <string name="monkUnarmoredDefense">
        Beginning at  1st level, while you are wearing no armor and not wielding a shield, your AC equals  10 + your Dexterity modifier + your W isdom  modifier.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkMartialArtstitle">
        Martial Arts
    </string>
    <string name="monkMartialArts">
        At 1st level, your practice of martial arts gives you mastery of combat styles that use unarmed strikes and monk weapons,
        which are shortswords and any simple melee weapons that don’t have the two-handed or heavy property.
        \n\n
        You gain the following benefits while you are unarmed or wielding only monk weapons and you aren’t wearing armor or wielding a shield:
        \n\n
        -You can use Dexterity instead of Strength for the attack and damage rolls of your unarmed strikes and monk weapons.
        \n\n
        -You can roll a d4 in place of the normal damage of your unarmed strike or monk weapon.
        This die changes as you gain monk levels, as shown in the Martial Arts column of the Monk table.
        \n\n
        -When you use the Attack action with an unarmed strike or a monk weapon on your turn, you can make one unarmed
        strike as a bonus action. For example, if you take the Attack action and attack with a
        quarter-staff, you can also make an unarmed strike as a bonus action, assuming you haven't already taken a bonus action this turn.

        \n\n
        Certain monasteries use specialized forms of the monk weapons. For example, you might use a club
        that is two lengths of w ood connected by a short chain (called a nunchaku) or a sickle with a
        shorter, straighter blade (called a kama). Whatever name you use for a monk weapon, you can use
        the game statistics provided for the weapon in chapter 5.
    </string>


    <string name="monkKiTitle">
        KI
    </string>
    <string name="monkKi">
        Starting at 2nd level, your training allows you to harness the mystic energy of ki. Your access to this energy is represented by a number of ki points.
        Your monk level determines the number of points you have, as shown in the Ki Points column of the Monk table.
        \n\n
        You can spend these points to fuel various ki features. You start knowing three such features: Flurry of Blows, Patient Defense,
        and Step of the Wind. You learn more ki features as you gain levels in this class.
        \n\n
        When you spend a ki point, it is unavailable until you finish a short or long rest, at the end of which you draw all of your expended ki back
        into yourself. You must spend at least 30 minutes of the rest meditating to regain your ki points.
        \n\n
        Some of your ki features require your target to make a saving throw to resist the feature’s effects. The saving throw DC is calculated as follows:
        \n\n
        <b>Ki save DC:</b>> 8 + your profitiency bonus + your Wisdom modifier

        \n\n
        <b>Flurry Blows</b>
        \n
        Immediately after you take the Attack action on your turn, you can spend  1  ki point to make two unarmed strikes as a bonus action.
        \n\n
        <b>Patient Defense</b>
        \nou can spend  1  ki point to take the Dodge action as a bonus action on your turn.
        \n\n
        <b>Step of the Wind</b>
        \n
        You can spend  1 ki point to take the Disengage or Dash action as a bonus action on your turn, and your jump distance is doubled for the turn.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkUnarmoredMovementTitle">
        Unarmored Movement
    </string>
    <string name="monkUnarmoredMovement">
        Starting at 2nd level, your speed increases by 10 feet while you are not wearing armor or wielding a 
        shield. This bonus increases when you reach certain monk levels, as shown in the Monk table.
        \n\n
        At 9th level, you gain the ability to move along vertical surfaces and across liquids on your turn without falling during the move.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkDeflectMissilesTille">
        Deflect Missiles
    </string>
    <string name="monkDeflectMissiles">
        Starting at 3rd level, you can use your reaction to deflect or catch the missile when you are hit by a ranged weapon attack.
        When you do so, the damage you take from the attack is reduced by 1d10 + your Dexterity modifier + your monk level.
        \n\n
        If you reduce the damage to 0, you can catch the missile if it is small enough for you to hold in one hand and you have at least one hand free. If you catch a missile in this way, you can spend  1  ki point to make a ranged attack with the weapon or piece of ammunition you just caught, as part of the same reaction.
        You make this attack with proficiency, regardless of your weapon proficiencies, and the missile counts as a monk weapon for the attack.
    </string>


    <string name="monkSlowFallTitle">
        Slow Fall
    </string>
    <string name="monkSlowFall">
        Beginning at 4th level, you can use your reaction when you fall to reduce any falling damage you take by an amount equal to five times your monk level.

    </string>


    <string name="monkStunningStrikeTitle">
        Stunning Strike
    </string>
    <string name="monkStunningStrike">
        Starting at 5th level, you can interfere with the flow of ki in an opponent’s body. 
        When you hit another creature with a melee weapon attack, you can spend 1 ki point to 
        attempt a stunning strike. The target must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or 
        be stunned until the end of your next turn.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkKiEmpoweredStrikesTitle">
        Ki-Empowered Strikes
    </string>
    <string name="monkKiEmpoweredStrikes">
        Starting at 6th level, your unarmed strikes count as magical for the purpose of overcoming resistance and immunity to nonmagical attacks and damage.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkEvasionTitle">
        Evasion
    </string>
    <string name="monkEvasion">
        At 7th level, your instinctive agility lets you dodge out of the way of certain area effects,
        such as a blue dragon’s lightning breath or a fireball spell. When you are subjected to an effect
        that allows you to make a Dexterity saving throw to take only half damage, you instead take no damage
        if you succeed on the saving throw, and only half damage if you fail.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkStillnessOfMindTitle">
        StillnessOfMind
    </string>
    <string name="monkStillnessOfMind">
        Starting at 7th level, you can use your action to end one effect on yourself that is causing you to be charmed or frightened.
    </string>


    <string name="monkPurityOfBodyTitle">
        Purity of Body
    </string>
    <string name="monkPurityOfBody">
        At 10th level, your mastery of the ki flowing through you makes you immune to disease and poison.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkTongueOfTheSunAndMoonTitle">
        Tongue of the Sun and Moon
    </string>
    <string name="monkTongueOfTheSunAndMoon">
        Starting at 13th level, you learn to touch the ki of other minds so 
        that you understand all spoken languages. Moreover, any creature that can understand a language can understand what you say.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkDiamondSoulTitle">
        Diamond Soul
    </string>
    <string name="monkDiamondSoul">
        Beginning at  14th level, your mastery of ki grants you proficiency in all saving throws.
        \n\n
        Additionally, whenever you make a saving throw and fail, you can spend 1  ki point to reroll it and take the second result.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkTimelessBodyTitle">
        Timeless Body
    </string>
    <string name="monkTimelessBody">
        At  15th level, your ki sustains you so that you suffer none of the frailty of old age, and you cant 
        be aged magically. You can still die of old age, however. In addition, you no longer need food or water.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkEmptyBodyTitle">
        Empty Body
    </string>
    <string name="monkEmptyBody">
        Beginning at 18th level, you can use your action to spend 4 ki points to become invisible for 1  minute.
        During that time, you also have resistance to all damage but force damage.
        \n\n
        Additionally, you can spend 8 ki points to cast the astral projection spell, without needing
        material components. When you do so, you can’t take any other creatures with you.
    </string>

    <string name="monkPerfectSelfTitle">
        Perfect Self
    </string>
    <string name="monkPerfectSelf">
        At 20th level, when you roll for initiative and have no ki points remaining, you regain 4 ki points.
    </string>

    //------------------------------------------------CLASS SCHOOLS------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="monkMonasticTraditions">
        Three traditions of monastic pursuit are com m on in the monasteries scattered across the multiverse.
        Most monasteries practice one tradition exclusively, but a few honor the three traditions and instruct
        each monk according to his or her aptitude and interest. All three traditions rely on the same basic techniques,
        diverging as the student grows more adept. Thus, a monk need choose a tradition only upon reaching 3rd level.
        \n\n
        W hen you reach 3rd level, you commit yourself to a monastic tradition: 
        the Way of the Open Hand, the Way of Shadow, or the Way of the Four Elements, 
        all detailed at the end of the class description. Your tradition grants you features at 3rd level and again at 6th,  11th, and  17th level.
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfTheOpenHandTitle">
        Way of the Open Hand
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfTheOpenHand">
        Monks of the Way of the Open Hand are the ultimate masters of martial arts combat, whether armed or unarmed. They learn techniques to push and trip their 
        opponents, manipulate ki to heal damage to their bodies, and practice advanced meditation that can protect them from harm.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkWayOfTheOpenHandOpenHandTechniqueTitle">
        Open Hand Technique
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfTheOpenHandOpenHandTechnique">
        Starting when you choose this tradition at 3rd level, you can manipulate your enemy’s ki when you harness your own.
        Whenever you hit a creature with one of the attacks granted by your Flurry of Blows, you can im pose one of the following effects on that target:
        \n\n
         •It must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw or be knocked prone.
        \n
        •It must make a Strength saving throw. If it fails, you can push it up to  15 feet away from you.
        \n
        •It can’t take reactions until the end of your next turn
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkWayOfTheOpenHandWholenessOfBodyTitle">
        Wholeness of Body
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfTheOpenHandWholenessOfBody">
        At 6th level, you gain the ability to heal yourself. As an action, you can regain hit points equal to three times 
        your monk level. You must finish a long rest before you can use this feature again.
    </string>
    
    <string name="monkWayOfTheOpenHandTranquilityTitle">
        Tranquility
    </string>



    <string name="monkWayOfTheOpenHandQuiveringPalmTitle">
        Quivering Palm
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfTheOpenHandQuiveringPalm">
        At 17th level, you gain the ability to set up lethal vibrations in someone’s body.
        When you hit a creature with an unarmed strike, you can spend 3 ki points to start these
        imperceptible vibrations, which last for a number of days equal to your monk level.
        The vibrations are harmless unless you use your action to end them.To do so, you and the
        target must be on the same plane of existence. When you use this action, the creature must
        make a Constitution saving throw. If it fails, it is reduced to 0 hit points. If it succeeds,
        it takes  10d10 necrotic damage.
        \n\n
        You can have only one creature under the effect of this feature at a time. You can choose to end the vibrations harmlessly without using an action.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="monkWayOfShadowTitle">
        Way of Shadow
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfShadow">
        Monks of the Way of Shadow follow a tradition that values stealth and subterfuge. 
        These monks might be called ninjas or shadowdancers, and they serve as spies and assassins. 
        Sometimes the members of a ninja monastery are family members, forming a clan sworn to secrecy 
        about their arts and missions. Other monasteries are more like thieves’ guilds, hiring out their services to nobles, 
        rich merchants, or anyone else who can pay their fees. Regardless of their methods, the heads of these monasteries 
        expect the unquestioning obedience of their students.
    </string>
    
    <string name="monkWayOfShadowsShadowArtsTitle">
        Shadow Arts
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfShadowShadowArts">
        Starting when you choose this tradition at 3rd level, you can use your ki to duplicate the effects of certain spells. 
        As an action, you can spend 2 ki points to cast darkness, darkvision, pass without trace, or 
        silence, without providing material components. Additionally, you gain the minor illusion cantrip if you don’t already know it.
    </string>

    
    <string name="monkWayOfShadowsShadowStepTitle">
        Shadow Step
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfShadowShadowStep">
        At 6th level, you gain the ability to step from one shadow into another. 
        When you are in dim light or darkness, as a bonus action you can teleport 
        up to 60 feet to an unoccupied space you can see that is also in dim light or 
        darkness. You then have advantage on the first melee attack you make before the end of the turn.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkWayOfShadowShadowCloakTitle">
        Shadow Cloak
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfShadowCloakOfShadows">
        By 11th level, you have learned to becom e one with the shadows. When you are in an area of dim light or darkness, 
        you can use your action to become invisible. You remain invisible until you make an attack, cast a spell, or are in an area of bright light.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkWayOfShadowOpportunistTitle">
        Opportunist
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfShadowOpportunist">
        At  17th level, you can exploit a creatures momentary distraction when it is hit by an attack.
        Whenever a creature within 5 feet of you is hit by an attack made by a creature other than you,
        you can use your reaction to make a melee attack against that creature.
    </string>


    <string name="monkWayOfTheFourElementsTitle">
        Way of the Four Elements
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfTheFourElements">
        You follow a monastic tradition that teaches you to harness the elements.
        When you focus your ki, you can align yourself with the forces of creation and
        bend the four elements to your will, using them as an extension of your body. Some members
        of this tradition dedicate themselves to a single element, but others weave the elements together.
        \n\n
        Many monks of this tradition tattoo their bodies with representations of their ki powers,
        commonly imagined as coiling dragons, but also as phoenixes, fish, plants, mountains, and cresting waves
    </string>


    <string name="monkWayOfTheFourElementsDiscipleOfTheElementTitle">
        Disciple of the Element
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfTheFourElementsDiscipleOfTheElement">
        When you choose this tradition at 3rd level, you learn magical disciplines that harness the power of the four elements. A discipline requires you to spend ki points each time you use it.
        \n\n
        You know the Elemental Attunement discipline and one other elemental discipline of your choice, which are detailed in the “Elemental Disciplines”
        section below. You learn one additional elemental discipline of your choice at 6th,  11th, and  17th level.
        \n\n
        Whenever you learn a new elemental discipline, you can also replace one elemental discipline that you already know with a different discipline.
        \n\n
        <b>Casting Elemental Spells</b>
        \n
        Some elemental disciplines allow you to cast spells. See chapter 10 for the general
        rules of spellcasting. To cast one of these spells, you use its casting time and other
        rules, but you don’t need to provide material components for it.
        \n\n
        Once you reach 5th level in this class, you can spend additional ki points to increase the level of an elemental discipline spell 
        that you cast, provided that the spell has an enhanced effect at a higher level, as burning hands does. 
        The spell's level increases by 1  for each additional ki point you spend. For example, if you are a 
        5th-level monk and use Sweeping Cinder Strike to cast burning hands, you can spend 3 ki points to cast it as a 
        2nd-level spell (the discipline’s base cost of 2 ki points plus 1)
        \n\n
        The maximum number of ki points you can spend to cast a spell in this way (including its base ki point cost and any additional
        ki points you spend to increase its level) is determined by your monk level, as shown in the Spells and Ki Points table.
        \n\n
        <b>Spells and Ki</b>
        \n
        \n
        <b>Monk Levels \t\t\t Maximum Ki for a Spell</b>
        \n
        5th-8th \t\t\t 3
        \n
        9th-12th \t\t\t 4
        \n
        13th-16th \t\t\t 5
        \n
        17th-20th \t\t\t 6
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="monkWayOfFourElementsElementalDisciplinesTitle">
        Elemental Disciplines
    </string>
    <string name="monkWayOfFourElementsElementalDisciplines">
        The elemental disciplines are presented in alphabetical order. If a discipline requires a level, you must be that level in this class to learn the discipline.
        \n\n
        <b>Breath of Winter (17th Level Required)</b>
        \n
        You can spend 6 ki points to cast cone of cold.
        \n\n
        <b>Clench of the North Wind (6th Level Required)</b>
        \n
        You can spend 3 ki points to cast hold person.
        \n\n
        <b>Elemental Attunement</b>
        \n
        You can use your action to briefly control elemental forces nearby, causing one of the following effects of your choice:
        \n\n
        • Create a harmless, instantaneous sensory effect related to air, earth, fire, or
        water, such as a shower of sparks, a puff of wind, a spray of light mist, or a gentle rumbling of stone.
        \n• Instantaneously light or snuff out a candle, a torch, or a small campfire.
        \n• Chill or warm up to  1  pound of nonliving material for up to  1  hour.
        \n• Cause earth, fire, water, or mist that can fit within a 1-foot cube to shape itself into a crude form you designate for 1  minute.
        \n\n
        <b>Eternal Mountain Defense (11th Level Required).</b>
        \n
        You can spend 5 ki points to cast stoneskin, targeting yourself.
        \n\n
        <b>Fangs of the Fire Snake</b>
        \n
        W hen you use the Attack action on your turn, you can spend 1  ki point to cause tendrils of
        flame to stretch out from your fists and feet. Your reach with your unarmed strikes increases by
        10 feet for that action, as well as the rest of the turn.A hit with such an attack deals fire damage
        instead of bludgeoning damage, and if you spend  1  ki point when the attack hits, it also deals an extra  1d10 fire damage.
        \n\n
        <b>Fist of Four Thunders</b>
        \n
        You can spend 2 ki points to cast thunderwave.
        \n\n
        <b>Fist of Unbroken Air</b>
        \n
        You can create a blast of com pressed air that strikes like a mighty fist. As an action, you can spend 2 ki points
        and choose a creature within 30 feet of you. That creature must make a Strength saving throw. On a failed save,
        the creature takes 3d10 bludgeoning damage, plus an extra  1d10 bludgeoning damage for each additional ki point you
        spend, and you can push the creature up to 20 feet away from you and knock it prone. On a successful save, the creature
        takes half as much damage, and you don’t push it or knock it prone.
        \n\n
        <b>Flames of the Phoenix (11th Level Required)</b>
        \n
        You can spend 4 ki points to cast fireball
        \n\n
        <b>Gong of the Summit (6th Level Required)</b>
        \n
        ou can spend 3 ki points to cast shatter.
        \n\n
        <b>Mist Stance (11th Level Required)</b>
        \n
        You can spend 4 ki points to cast gaseous form, targeting yourself.
        \n\n
        <b>Ride the Wind (11th Level Required)</b>
        \n
        You can spend4  ki points to cast fly, targeting yourself.
        \n\n
        <b>River of Hungry Flame (17th Level Required)</b>
        \n
        You can spend 5 ki points to cast wall of fire.
        \n\n
        <b>Rush of the Gale Spirits</b>
        \n
        You can spend 2 ki points to cast gust of wind.
        \n\n
        <b>Shape the Flowing River</b>
        \n
        As an action, you can spend  1  ki point to choose an area of ice or water no larger than
        30 feet on a side within  120 feet of you. You can change water to ice within the area and
        vice versa, and you can reshape ice in the area in any manner you choose. You can raise or
        lower the ice’s elevation, create or fill in a trench, erect or flatten a wall, or form a pillar.
        The extent of any such changes can’t exceed half the area’s largest dimension. For example, if you
        affect a 30-foot square, you can create a pillar up to  15 feet high, raise or lower the square’s
        elevation by up to  15 feet, dig a trench up to 15 feet deep, and so on. You can’t shape the ice
        to trap or injure a creature in the area.
        \n\n
        <b>Sweeping Cinder Strike</b>
        \n
        You can spend 2 ki points to cast burning hands.
        \n\n
        <b>Water Whip</b>
        \n
        You can spend 2 ki points as a bonus action to create a whip of water that shoves and pulls a
        creature to unbalance it. A creature that you can see that is within 30 feet of you must make a
        Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, the creature takes 3d10 bludgeoning damage, plus an extra
        1d10 bludgeoning damage for each additional ki point you spend, and you can either knock it prone or
        pull it up to 25 feet closer to you. On a successful save, the creature takes half as much damage,
        and you don’t pull it or knock it prone.
        \n\n
        <b>Wave of Rolling Earth (17th Level Required)</b>
        \n
        You can spend 6 ki points to cast wall of stone.
    </string>
    
    
    
</resources>