<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="paladin_introduction">
        Clad in plate armor that gleams in the sunlight despite
        the dust and grime of long travel, a human lays down
        her sword and shield and places her hands on a mortally
        wounded man. Divine radiance shines from her hands,
        the man’s wounds knit closed, and his eyes open wide
        with amazement.

        \n\nA dwarf crouches behind an outcrop, his black cloak
        making him nearly invisible in the night, and watches
        an orc warband celebrating its recent victory. Silently,
        he stalks into their midst and whispers an oath, and two
        orcs are dead before they even realize he is there.
        Silver hair shining in a shaft of light that seems to
        illuminate only him , an elf laughs with exultation. His
        spear flashes like his eyes as he jabs again and again
        at a twisted giant, until at last his light overcomes its
        hideous darkness.

        \n\nWhatever their origin and their mission, paladins are
        united by their oaths to stand against the forces of evil.
        Whether sworn before a god’s altar and the witness of
        a priest, in a sa cred glade before nature spirits and fey
        beings, or in a moment of desperation and grief with the
        dead as the only witness, a paladin’s oath is a powerful
        bond. It is a source of power that turns a devout warrior
        into a blessed champion.

    </string>

    <string name="creating_paladin_string">
        The most important aspect of a paladin character is
        the nature of his or her holy quest. Although the class
        features related to your oath don`t appear until you
        reach 3rd level, plan ahead for that choice by reading
        the oath descriptions at the end of the class. Are you a
        devoted servant of good, loyal to the gods of justice and
        honor, a holy knight in shining armor venturing forth
        to smite evil? Are you a glorious champion of the light,
        cherishing everything beautiful that stands against the
        shadow, a knight whose oath descends from traditions
        older than many of the gods? Or are you an embittered
        loner sworn to take vengeance on those who have done
        great evil, sent as an angel of death by the gods or driven
        by your need for revenge?

        \n\nHow did you experience your call to
        serve as a paladin? Did you hear a whisper
        from an unseen god or angel while you were at
        prayer? Did another paladin sense the potential within
        you and decide to train you as a squire? Or did some
        terrible event—the destruction of your home, perhaps—
        drive you to your quests? Perhaps you stumbled into
        a sacred grove or a hidden elven enclave and found
        yourself called to protect all such refuges of goodness
        and beauty. Or you might have known from your earliest
        memories that the paladin’s life was your calling, almost
        as if you had been sent into the world with that purpose
        stamped on your soul.

        \n\nAs guardians against the forces of wickedness,
        paladins are rarely of any evil alignment. Most of them
        walk the paths of charity and justice. Consider how your
        alignment colors the way you pursue your holy quest
        and the manner in which you con duct yourself before
        gods and mortals. Your oath and alignment might be
        in harmony, or your oath might represent standards of
        behavior that you have not yet attained.

    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="paladin_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Divine Sense
        \nLay on Hands
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Fighting Style,
        \nSpellcasting,
        \nDivine Smite
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        Divine Health,
        \nSacred Oath
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_5th_lvl_abilities">
        Extra Attack
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Aura of Protection
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_7th_lvl_abilities">
        Sacred Oath Feature
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_9th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Aura of Courage
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_11th_lvl_abilities">
        Improved Divine Smite
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_13th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Cleansing Touch
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_15th_lvl_abilities">
        Sacred Oath Feature
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_17th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Aura Improvements
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Sacred Oath Feature
    </string>


    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="paladinFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a paladin, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="paladinHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d10 per paladin lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 10 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d10(or 6) + Constitution Modifier per paladin level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="paladinProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> All armors, Shields
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Simple Weapons, Martial Weapons
        \n<b>Tools:</b> None
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Wisdom, Charisma
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose two from Athletics, Insight, Intimidation, Medicine, Persuation, Religion
    </string>

    <string name="paladinEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background:
        \n\n- (a) a martial weapon and shield or (b) two martial weapons
        \n- (a) five javelins or (b) any simple melee weapon
        \n- (s) a priests pack or (b) an explorers pack
        \n- chain mail and a holy symbol
    </string>



    //------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
</resources>