<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="paladin_introduction">
        Clad in plate armor that gleams in the sunlight despite
        the dust and grime of long travel, a human lays down
        her sword and shield and places her hands on a mortally
        wounded man. Divine radiance shines from her hands,
        the man’s wounds knit closed, and his eyes open wide
        with amazement.

        \n\nA dwarf crouches behind an outcrop, his black cloak
        making him nearly invisible in the night, and watches
        an orc warband celebrating its recent victory. Silently,
        he stalks into their midst and whispers an oath, and two
        orcs are dead before they even realize he is there.
        Silver hair shining in a shaft of light that seems to
        illuminate only him , an elf laughs with exultation. His
        spear flashes like his eyes as he jabs again and again
        at a twisted giant, until at last his light overcomes its
        hideous darkness.

        \n\nWhatever their origin and their mission, paladins are
        united by their oaths to stand against the forces of evil.
        Whether sworn before a god’s altar and the witness of
        a priest, in a sa cred glade before nature spirits and fey
        beings, or in a moment of desperation and grief with the
        dead as the only witness, a paladin’s oath is a powerful
        bond. It is a source of power that turns a devout warrior
        into a blessed champion.

    </string>

    <string name="creating_paladin_string">
        The most important aspect of a paladin character is
        the nature of his or her holy quest. Although the class
        features related to your oath don`t appear until you
        reach 3rd level, plan ahead for that choice by reading
        the oath descriptions at the end of the class. Are you a
        devoted servant of good, loyal to the gods of justice and
        honor, a holy knight in shining armor venturing forth
        to smite evil? Are you a glorious champion of the light,
        cherishing everything beautiful that stands against the
        shadow, a knight whose oath descends from traditions
        older than many of the gods? Or are you an embittered
        loner sworn to take vengeance on those who have done
        great evil, sent as an angel of death by the gods or driven
        by your need for revenge?

        \n\nHow did you experience your call to
        serve as a paladin? Did you hear a whisper
        from an unseen god or angel while you were at
        prayer? Did another paladin sense the potential within
        you and decide to train you as a squire? Or did some
        terrible event—the destruction of your home, perhaps—
        drive you to your quests? Perhaps you stumbled into
        a sacred grove or a hidden elven enclave and found
        yourself called to protect all such refuges of goodness
        and beauty. Or you might have known from your earliest
        memories that the paladin’s life was your calling, almost
        as if you had been sent into the world with that purpose
        stamped on your soul.

        \n\nAs guardians against the forces of wickedness,
        paladins are rarely of any evil alignment. Most of them
        walk the paths of charity and justice. Consider how your
        alignment colors the way you pursue your holy quest
        and the manner in which you con duct yourself before
        gods and mortals. Your oath and alignment might be
        in harmony, or your oath might represent standards of
        behavior that you have not yet attained.

    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="paladin_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Divine Sense
        \nLay on Hands
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Fighting Style,
        \nSpellcasting,
        \nDivine Smite
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        Divine Health,
        \nSacred Oath
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_5th_lvl_abilities">
        Extra Attack
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Aura of Protection
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_7th_lvl_abilities">
        Sacred Oath Feature
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_9th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Aura of Courage
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_11th_lvl_abilities">
        Improved Divine Smite
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_13th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Cleansing Touch
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_15th_lvl_abilities">
        Sacred Oath Feature
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_17th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Aura Improvements
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="paladin_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Sacred Oath Feature
    </string>


    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="paladinFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a paladin, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="paladinHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d10 per paladin lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 10 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d10(or 6) + Constitution Modifier per paladin level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="paladinProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> All armors, Shields
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Simple Weapons, Martial Weapons
        \n<b>Tools:</b> None
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Wisdom, Charisma
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose two from Athletics, Insight, Intimidation, Medicine, Persuation, Religion
    </string>

    <string name="paladinEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background:
        \n\n- (a) a martial weapon and shield or (b) two martial weapons
        \n- (a) five javelins or (b) any simple melee weapon
        \n- (s) a priests pack or (b) an explorers pack
        \n- chain mail and a holy symbol
    </string>



    //--------------------------------------------------ABILITIES----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="paladinDivineSenseTitle">
        Divine Sense
    </string>
    <string name="paladinDivineSense">
        The presence of strong evil registers on your senses like a noxious odor,
        and powerful good rings like heavenly music in your ears. As an action, you can
        open your awareness to detect such forces. Until the end of your next turn, you
        know the location of any celestial, fiend, or undead within 60 feet of you that is
        not behind total cover. You know the type (celestial, fiend, or undead) of any being
        whose presence you sense, but not its identity (the vampire Count Strahd von Zarovich, for instance).
        Within the same radius, you also detect the presence of any place or object that has been consecrated
        or desecrated, as with the hallow spell.
        \n\n
        You can use this feature a number of times equal to: 1 + your Charisma modifier. When you finish a long rest, you regain all expended uses.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinLayOnHandsTitle">
        Lay on Hands
    </string>
    <string name="paladinLayOnHands">
        Your blessed touch can heal wounds. You have a pool of healing power that replenishes when you take a long rest.
        With that pool, you can restore a total number of hit points equal to your paladin level x 5.
        \n\n
        As an action, you can touch a creature and draw power from the pool to restore a number of hit points to
        that creature, up to the maximum amount remaining in your pool.
        \n\n
        Alternatively, you can expend 5 hit points from your pool of healing to cure the target of one disease or
        neutralize one poison affecting it. You can cure multiple
        diseases and neutralize multiple poisons with a single use of Lay on Hands, expending hit points separately for each one.
        \n\n
        This feature has no effect on undead and constructs.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinFightingStyleTitle">
        Fighting Style
    </string>
    <string name="paladinFightingStyle">
        At 2nd level, you adopt a style of fighting as your specialty. Choose one of the following options.
        You can’t take a Fighting Style option more than once, even if you later get to choose again.
        \n\n
        <b>Defense</b>
        \n
        While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1  bonus to AC.
        \n\n
        <b>Dueling</b>
        \n
        When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.
        \n\n
        <b>Great Weapon Fighting</b>
        \n
        When you roll a 1  or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands,
        you can reroll the die and must use the new roll. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.
        \n\n
        <b>Protection</b>
        \n
        When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use
        your reaction to im pose disadvantage on the attack roll.You must be wielding a shield.
    </string>


    <string name="paladinDivineSmiteTitle">
        Divine Smite
    </string>
    <string name="paladinDivineSmite">
        Starting at 2nd level, when you hit a creature with a melee weapon attack, 
        you can expend one paladin spell slot to deal radiant damage to the target, 
        in addition to the w eapon’s damage. The extra damage is 2d8 for a 1st-level spell 
        slot, plus  1d8 for each spell level higher than  1st, to a maximum of 5d8. The damage 
        increases by 1d8 if the target is an undead or a fiend.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinDivineHealthTitle">
        Divine Health
    </string>
    <string name="paladinDivineHealth">
        By 3rd level, the divine magic flowing through you makes you immune to disease.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinAuraOfProtectionTitle">
        Aura of Protection
    </string>
    <string name="paladinAuraOfProtection">
        Starting at 6th level, whenever you or a friendly creature within  10 feet of you must make a saving throw,
        the creature gains a bonus to the saving throw equal to your Charisma modifier (with a minimum bonus of +1).
        You must be conscious to grant this bonus.
        \n\n
        At 18th level, the range of this aura increases to 30 feet.
    </string>

    <string name="paladinAuraOfCourageTitle">
        Aura of Courage
    </string>
    <string name="paladinAuraOfCourage">
        Starting at  10th level, you and friendly creatures within  10 feet of you can’t be frightened while you are conscious.
        \n\n
        At 18th level, the range of this aura increases to 30 feet.
    </string>
    
    <string name="paladinImprovedDivineSmiteTitle">
        Improved Divine Smite
    </string>
    <string name="paladinImprovedDivineSmite">
        By 11th level, you are so suffused with righteous might that all your melee weapon strikes 
        carry divine power with them. W henever you hit a creature with a melee weapon, the creature 
        takes an extra  1d8 radiant damage. If you also use your Divine Smite with an attack, you 
        add this damage to the extra damage of your Divine Smite.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinCleansingTouchTitle">
        Cleansing Touch
    </string>
    <string name="paladinCleansingTouch">
        Beginning at 14th level, you can use your action to end one spell on yourself or on one willing creature that you touch.
        \n\n
        You can use this feature a number of times equal to your Charisma modifier (a minimum of once). You regain expended uses when you finish a long rest.
    </string>

    //--------------------------------------------------CLASS SCHOOLS----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="paladinSacredOathsTitle">
        Sacred Oaths
    </string>
    <string name="paladinSacredOaths">
        Becoming a paladin involves taking vows that commit the paladin to the cause of righteousness, an active path of fighting wickedness.
        The final oath, taken when he or she reaches 3rd level, is the culmination of all the paladin’s training. Som e characters with this
        class don’t consider themselves true paladins until they have reached 3rd level and made this oath. For others, the actual swearing of
        the oath is a formality, an official stamp on what has always been true in the paladin’s heart.
        \n\n
        When you reach 3rd level, you swear the oath that binds you as a paladin forever.
        Up to this time you have been in a preparatory stage, committed to the path but not yet sworn to it.
        Now you choose the Oath of Devotion, the Oath of the Ancients, or the Oath of Vengeance, all detailed
        at the end of the class description.Your choice grants you features at 3rd level and again at 7th,
        15th, and 20th level. Those features include oath spells and the Channel Divinity feature.
        \n\n
        <b>Oath Spells</b>
        \n
        Each oath has a list of associated spells. You gain access to these spells at the levels specified in the oath description.
        Once you gain access to an oath spell, you always have it prepared. Oath spells don’t count against the number of spells you can prepare each day.
        \n
        If you gain an oath spell that doesn’t appear on the paladin spell list, the spell is nonetheless a paladin spell for you.
        \n\n
        <b>Channel Divinity</b>
        \n
        Your oath allows you to channel divine energy to fuel magical effects. Each Channel Divinity option provided by your oath explains how to use it.
        \n
        When you use your Channel Divinity, you choose which option to use. You must then finish a short or long rest to use your Channel Divinity again.
        \n
        Some Channel Divinity effects require saving throws. W hen you use such an effect from this class, the DC equals your paladin spell save DC.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinOathOfDeviotionTitle">
        Oath of Devotion
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfDeviotion">
        The Oath of Devotion binds a paladin to the loftiest ideals of justice, virtue, and order.
        Sometimes called cavaliers, white knights, or holy warriors, these paladins meet the ideal of the knight in shining armor,
        acting with honor in pursuit of justice and the greater good. They hold themselves to the highest
        standards of conduct, and some, for better or worse, hold the rest of the world to the same standards.
        Many who swear this oath are devoted to gods of law and good and use their gods’ tenets as the measure of
        their devotion. They hold angels—the perfect servants of good—as their ideals, and incorporate images of angelic
        wings into their helmets or coats of arms.
    </string>



    <string name="paladinOathOfDeviotionOathSpellsTitle">
        Oath Spells
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfDeviotionOathSpells">
        Oath of Devotion Spells
        \n\n
        <b>Paladin Level \t\t\t Spells</b>\n
        3rd \t\t\t protection from evil and good, sanctuary\n
        5th \t\t\t lesser restoration, zone of truth\n
        9th \t\t\t beacon of hope, dispel magic\n
        13th \t\t\t freedom of movement, guardian of faith\n
        17th \t\t\t commune, flame strike\n
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinOathOfDeviotionChannelDivinityTitle">
        Channel Divinity
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfDeviotionChannelDivinity">
        When you take this oath at 3rd level, you gain the following two Channel Divinity options.
        \n\n
        <b>Sacred Weapon</b>
        \n
        As an action, you can imbue one weapon that you are holding with positive energy,
        using your Channel Divinity. For 1  minute, you add your Charisma modifier to attack
        rolls made with that weapon (with a minimum bonus of +1). The weapon also emits bright
        light in a 20-foot radius and dim light 20 feet beyond that. If the weapon is not already magical,
        it becomes magical for the duration.
        \nYou can end this effect on your turn as part of any other action. If you are no longer
        holding or carrying this weapon, or if you fall unconscious, this effect ends.
        \n\n
        <b>Turn the Unholy</b>
        \n
        As an action, you present your holy symbol and speak a prayer censuring fiends and undead,
        using your Channel Divinity. Each fiend or undead that can see or hear you within 30 feet of you must make a Wisdom saving throw.
        If the creature fails its saving throw, it is turned for  1  minute or until it takes damage.
        \nA turned creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can,
        and it can’t willingly move to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can’t take reactions. 
        For its action, it can use only the Dash action or try to escape from an effect that prevents 
        it from moving. If there’s nowhere to move, the creature can use the Dodge action.
    </string>

    
    <string name="paladinOathOfDevotionAuraOfDevotionTitle">
        Aura of Devotion
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfDevotionAuraofDevotion">
        Starting at 7th level, you and friendly creatures within 10 feet of you can’t be charmed while you are conscious. 
        \n\n
        At 18th level, the range of this aura increases to 30 feet.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinOathOfDevotionPurityOfSpiritTitle">
        Purity of Spirit
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfDevotionPurityOfSpirit">
        Beginning at  15th level, you are always under the effects of a protection from evil and good spell.
    </string>
    
    <string name="paladinOathOfDevotionHolyNimbusTitle">
        Holy Nimbus
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfDevotionHolyNimbus">
        At 20th level, as an action, you can emanate an aura of sunlight. For 1
        minute, bright light shines from you in a 30-foot radius, and dim light shines 30 feet beyond that.
        \n\n
        Whenever an enemy creature starts its turn in the bright light, the creature takes  10 radiant damage.
        \n\n
        In addition, for the duration, you have advantage on saving throws against spells cast by fiends or undead.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a long rest.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncientsTitle">
        Oath of the Ancients
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncients">
        The Oath of the Ancients is as old as the race of elves and the rituals of the druids. Sometim es called fey knights,
        green knights, or horned knights, paladins who swear this oath cast their lot with the side of the light in the cosmic
        struggle against darkness because they love the beautiful and life-giving things of the world, not necessarily because they
        believe in principles of honor, courage, and justice.
        They adorn their armor and clothing with images of growing things—leaves, antlers, or flowers—to reflect their commitment
        to preserving life and light in the world.
    </string>


    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncientsSpellsTitle">
        Oath Spells
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncientsSpells">
        Oath of the Ancients Spells
        \n\n
        <b>Paladin Level \t\t\t Spells</b>\n
        3rd \t\t\t ensnaring strike, speak with animals\n
        5th \t\t\t moonbeam, misty step\n
        9th \t\t\t plant growth, protection from energy\n
        13th \t\t\t ice storm, stoneskin\n
        17th \t\t\t commune with nature, tree stride\n
    </string>


    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncientsChannelDivinityTitle">
        Channel Divinity
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncientsChannelDivinity">
        When you take this oath at 3rd level, you gain the following two Channel Divinity options.
        \n\n
        <b>Natures Wrath</b>
        \n
        You can use your Channel Divinity to invoke primeval forces to ensnare a foe.
        As an action, you can cause spectral vines to spring up and reach for a creature within
        10 feet of you that you can see.The creature must succeed on a Strength or Dexterity saving
        throw (its choice) or be restrained. While restrained by the vines, the creature repeats the
        saving throw at the end of each of its turns. On a success, it frees itself and the vines vanish.
        \n\n
        <b>Turn the Faithless</b>
        \n
        You can use your Channel Divinity to utter ancient words that are painful for fey and fiends to hear.
        As an action, you present your holy symbol, and each fey or fiend within 30 feet of you that can hear
        you must make a Wisdom  saving throw. On a failed save, the creature is turned for 1  minute or until it takes damage.
        \nA turned creature must spend its turns trying to move as far away from you as it can, and it can’t willingly move
        to a space within 30 feet of you. It also can’t take reactions. For its action, it can use only the Dash action or
        try to escape from an effect that prevents it from moving. If there’s nowhere to move, the creature can use the Dodge action.
        \nIf the creature’s true form is concealed by an illusion, shapeshifting, or other effect, that form is revealed while it is turned.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncientsAuraOfWardingTitle">
        Aura of Warding
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncientsAuraOfWarding">
        Beginning at 7th level, ancient magic lies so heavily upon you that it forms an
        eldritch ward. You and friendly creatures within  10 feet of you have resistance to damage from spells.
        \n\n
        At 18th level, the range of this aura increases to 30 feet.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncientsUndyingSentinelTitle">
        Undying Sentinel
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncientsUndyingSentinel">
        Starting at 15th level, when you are reduced to 0 hit points and are not killed outright, you can
        choose to drop to  1 hit point instead. Once you use this ability, you can’t use it again until you finish a long rest.
        \n\n
        Additionally, you suffer none of the drawbacks of old age, and you can’t be aged magically.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncientsElderChampionTitle">
        Elder Champion
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfTheAncientsElderChampion">
        At 20th level, you can assume the form of an ancient force of nature, taking on an appearance you choose.For example,
        your skin might turn green or take on a bark-like texture, your hair might becom e leafy or m oss- like, or you might sprout antlers or a lion-like mane.
        \n\n
        Using your action, you undergo a transformation.For 1 minute, you gain the following benefits:
        \n
        •\tAt the start of each of your turns, you regain  10 hit points.
        •\tWhenever you cast a paladin spell that has a casting time of 1  action, you can cast it using a bonus action instead.
        •\tEnemy creatures within  10 feet of you have disadvan­tage on saving throws against your paladin spells and Channel Divinity options.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a long rest.
    </string>


    <string name="paladinOathOfVengenceTitle">
        Oath of Vengence
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfVengence">
        he Oath of Vengeance is a solemn commitment to punish those who have committed a grievous sin. When evil forces
        slaughter helpless villagers, when an entire people turns against the will of the gods, when a thieves’ guild
        \grows too violent and powerful, when a dragon rampages through the countryside—at times like these, paladins
        arise and swear an Oath of Vengeance to set right that which has gone wrong. To these paladins— sometimes called
        avengers or dark knights—their own purity is not as important as delivering justice.
    </string>


    <string name="paladinOathOfVengenceSpellsTitle">
        Oath Spells
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfVengenceSpells">
        Oath of the Ancients Spells
        \n\n
        <b>Paladin Level \t\t\t Spells</b>\n
        3rd \t\t\t bane, hunters mark\n
        5th \t\t\t hold person, misty step\n
        9th \t\t\t haste, protection from energy\n
        13th \t\t\t banishment, dimension door\n
        17th \t\t\t hold monster, scrying\n
    </string>


    <string name="paladinOathOfVengenceChannelDivinityTitle">
        Channel Divinity
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfVengenceChannelDivinity">
        When you take this oath at 3rd level, you gain the following two Channel Divinity options.
        \n\n
        <b>Abjure Enemy</b>
        \n
        As an action, you present your holy symbol and speak a prayer of denunciation,
        using your Channel Divinity. Choose one creature within 60 feet of you that you can see.
        That creature must make a Wisdom  saving throw, unless it is immune to being frightened. Fiends and undead have disadvantage on this saving throw.
        \nOn a failed save, the creature is frightened for 1 minute or until it takes any damage.
        While frightened, the creature’s speed is 0, and it can’t benefit from any bonus to its speed.
        \nOn a successful save, the creature’s speed is halved for  1  minute or until the creature takes any damage.
        \n\n
        <b>Vow of Enmity</b>
        \n
        As a bonus action, you can utter a vow of enmity against a creature you can see within  10 feet of you, using your Channel Divinity. 
        You gain advantage on attack rolls against the creature for 1  minute or until it drops to 0 hit points or falls unconscious.
    </string>



    <string name="paladinOathOFVengenceRelentlessAvengerTitle">
        Relentless Avenger
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOFVengenceRelentlessAvenger">
        By 7th level, your supernatural focus helps you close off a foe’s retreat. When you hit a creature with an opportunity attack, 
        you can move up to half your speed immediately after the attack and as part of the same reaction. 
        This movement doesn’t provoke opportunity attacks.
    </string>
    
    <string name="paladinOathOfVengenceSoulOfVengeanceTitle">
        Soul of Vengeance
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfVengenceSoulOfVengeance">
        Starting at  15th level, the authority with which you speak your Vow of Enmity
        gives you greater power over your foe. W hen a creature under the effect of your
        Vow of Enmity makes an attack, you can use your reaction to make a melee weapon attack against that creature if it is within range.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="paladinOathOfVengenaceAvengingAngelTitle">
        Avenging Angel
    </string>
    <string name="paladinOathOfVengenaceAvengingAngel">
        At 20th level, you can assume the form of an angelic avenger. Using your action, you undergo a transformation. For 1  hour, you gain the following benefits:
        \n
        •\tWings sprout from your back and grant you a flying speed of 60 feet.\n
        •\tYou emanate an aura of menace in a 30-foot radius. The first time any enemy creature enters the aura or starts its turn there during a battle,
        the creature must succeed on a Wisdom  saving throw or become frightened of you for 1  minute or until it takes any damage.
        Attack rolls against the frightened creature have advantage.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a long rest.
    </string>

</resources>