<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="ranger_introduction">
        Rough and wild looking,
        a human stalks alone
        through the shadows of
        trees, hunting the orcs he
        knows are planning a raid
        on a nearby farm. Clutching
        a shortsword in each hand,
        he becomes a whirlwind of
        steel, cutting down one enemy
        after another.

        \n\nAfter tumbling away from a cone of
        freezing air, an elf finds her feet and draws
        back her bow to loose an arrow at the white
        dragon. Shrugging off the wave of fear that emanates
        from the dragon like the cold of its breath, she sends
        one arrow after another to find the gaps between the
        dragon’s thick scales.

        \n\nHolding his hand high, a half-elf whistles to the hawk
        that circles high above him, calling the bird back to his
        side. Whispering instructions in Elvish, he points to
        the owlbear he’s been tracking and sends the hawk to
        distract the creature while he readies his bow.

        \n\nFar from the bustle of cities and towns, past the
        hedges that shelter the most distant farms from the
        terrors of the wild, amid the dense-packed trees of
        trackless forests and across wide and empty plains,
        rangers keep their unending watch.

    </string>

    <string name="creating_renger_string">
        As you create your ranger character, consider the nature
        of the training that gave you your particular capabilities.
        Did you train with a single mentor, wandering the wilds
        together until you mastered the ranger’s ways? Did you
        leave your apprenticeship, or was your mentor slain—
        perhaps by the same kind of monster that became your
        favored enemy? Or perhaps you learned your skills as
        part of a band of rangers affiliated with a druidic circle,
        trained in mystic paths as well as wilderness lore. You
        might be self-taught, a recluse who learned combat
        skills, tracking, and even a magical connection to nature
        through the necessity of surviving in the wilds.

        \n\nWhat’s the source of your particular hatred of a
        certain kind of enemy? Did a monster kill someone
        you loved or destroy your home village? Or did you see
        too much of the destruction these monsters cause and
        com mit yourself to reining in their depredations? Is
        your adventuring career a continuation of your work
        in protecting the borderlands, or a significant change?

        \n\nWhat made you join up with a band of adventurers?
        Do you find it challenging to teach new allies the ways
        of the wild, or do you welcome the relief from solitude
        that they offer?
    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="ranger_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Favored Enemy,
        \nNatural Explorer
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Fighting Style,
        \nSpellcasting
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        Ranger Archetype,
        \nPrimal Awareness
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_5th_lvl_abilities">
        Extra Attack
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Favored Enemy Improvement,
        \nNatural Explorer Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_7th_lvl_abilities">
        Ranger Archetype Feature
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement,
        \nHide in Plain Sight
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_9th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Natural Explorer Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_11th_lvl_abilities">
        Ranger Archetype Feature
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_13th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Favored Enemy Improvement,
        \nVanish
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_15th_lvl_abilities">
        Ranger Archetype Feature
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_17th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Feral Senses
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Foe Slayer
    </string>

    //---------------------------------------------------------Spell Table---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="ranger_table2_label">
        Spells Table
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_label">
        Spells Known
    </string>


    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_1_values">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_2_values">
        2
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_3to4_values">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_5to6_values">
        4
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_7to8_values">
        5
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_9to10_values">
       6
    </string>


    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_11to12_values">
        7
    </string>


    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_13to14_values">
        8
    </string>


    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_15to16_values">
        9
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_17to18_values">
       10
    </string>

    <string name="ranger_table2_value2_19to20_values">
        11
    </string>




    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="rangerFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a ranger, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="rangerHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d10 per ranger lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 10 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d10(or 6) + Constitution Modifier per ranger level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="rangerProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> Light armor, medium armor, shields
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Simple weapons, martial weapons
        \n<b>Tools:</b> None
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Strength, Dexterity
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose three from Animal Handling, Athletics, Insight, Investigation, Nature, Perception, Stealth, Survival
    </string>

    <string name="rangerEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background:
        \n\n- (a) two shortswords or (b) two simple melee weapon
        \n- (a) a dungeoners pack or (b) an explorers pack
        \n- A longbow with 20 arrows
    </string>



    //--------------------------------------------------------ABILITIES----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    
    <string name="rangerFavoredEnemyTitle">
        Favored Enemy
    </string>
    <string name="rangerFavoredEnemy">
        Beginning at  1st level, you have significant experience studying, tracking, hunting, and even talking to a certain type of enemy.
        \n\n
        Choose a type of favored enemy: aberrations, beasts, celestials, constructs, dragons, elementals, fey, fiends,
        giants, monstrosities, oozes, plants, or undead. Alternatively, you can select two races of humanoid (such as gnolls and orcs) as favored enemies.
        \n\n
        You have advantage on W isdom  (Survival) checks to track your favored enemies, as well as on Intelligence checks to recall information about them.
        \n\n
        When you gain this feature, you also learn one language of your choice that is spoken by your favored enemies, if they speak one at all.
        \n\n
        You choose one additional favored enemy, as well as an associated language, at 6th and  14th level. As you gain levels, your choices 
        should reflect the types of monsters you have encountered on your adventures.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rangerNaturalExplorerTitle">
        Natural Explorer
    </string>
    <string name="rangerNaturalExplorer">
        You are particularly familiar with one type of natural environment and are adept at traveling and surviving in such regions.
        Choose one type of favored terrain: arctic, coast, desert, forest, grassland, mountain, swamp, or the Underdark. W hen you make
        an Intelligence or Wisdom  check related to your favored terrain, your proficiency bonus is doubled if you are using a skill that you’re proficient in.
        \n\n
        While traveling for an hour or more in your favored terrain, you gain the following benefits:
        \n
        •\tDifficult terrain doesn’t slow your group’s travel.
        \n
        •\tYour group can’t become lost except by magical means.
        \n
        •\tEven when you are engaged in another activity while traveling (such as foraging, navigating, or tracking), you remain alert to danger.
        \n
        •\tIf you are traveling alone, you can move stealthily at a normal pace.
        \n
        •\tWhen you forage, you find twice as much food as you normally would.
        \n
        •\tWhile tracking other creatures, you also learn their exact number, their sizes, and how long ago they passed through the area.
        \n\n
        You choose additional favored terrain types at 6th and  10th level.
    </string>



    <string name="rangerFightingStyleTitle">
        Fighting Style
    </string>
    <string name="rangerFightingStyle">
        At 2nd level, you adopt a particular style of fighting as your specialty.
        Choose one of the following options. You can’t take a Fighting Style option more than once,
        even if you later get to choose again.
        \n\n
        <b>Archery</b>
        \nYou gain a +2 bonus to attack rolls you make with ranged weapons.
        \n\n
        <b>Defense</b>
        \n
        While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.
        \n\n
        <b>Dueling</b>
        \n
        When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.
        \n\n
        <b>Two-Weapon Fighting</b>
        \n
        When you engage in two-weapon fighting, you can add your ability modifier to the damage of the second attack.
    </string>


    <string name="rangerPrimevalAwarenessTitle">
        Primeval Awareness
    </string>
    <string name="rangerPrimevalAwareness">
        Beginning at 3rd level, you can use your action and expend one ranger spell slot to focus your awareness
        on the region around you. For 1  minute per level of the spell slot you expend, you can sense whether the
        following types of creatures are present within  1  mile of you (or within up to 6 miles if you are in your favored terrain):
        aberrations, celestials, dragons, elementals, fey, fiends, and undead. This feature doesn’t reveal the creatures’ location or number.
    </string>


    <string name="rangerLandsStrideTitle">
        Lands Stride
    </string>
    <string name="rangerLandsStride">
        Starting at 8th level, moving through nonmagical difficult terrain costs you no extra movement.
        You can also pass through nonmagical plants without being slowed by them and without taking damage from them if they have thorns, spines, or a similar hazard.
        \n\n
        In addition, you have advantage on saving throws against plants that are magically created or manipulated to impede movement, such those created by the entangle spell.
    </string>
    
    <string name="rangerHideInPlainSightTitle">
        Hide in Plain Side
    </string>
    <string name="rangerHideInPlainSight">
        Starting at  10th level, you can spend 1  minute creating camouflage for yourself.
        You must have access to fresh mud, dirt, plants, soot, and other naturally occurring materials with which to create your camouflage.
        \n\n
        Once you are camouflaged in this way, you can try to hide by pressing yourself up against a solid surface, such as a tree or wall,
        that is at least as tall and wide as you are. You gain a +10 bonus to Dexterity (Stealth) checks as long as you remain there
        without moving or taking actions. Once you move or take an action or a reaction, you must camouflage yourself again to gain this benefit.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rangerVanishTitle">
        Vanish
    </string>
    <string name="rangerVanish">
        Starting at  14th level, you can use the Hide action as a bonus action on your turn. 
        Also, you can’t be tracked by nonmagical means, unless you choose to leave a trail.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rangerFeralSensesTitle">
        Feral Senses
    </string>
    <string name="rangerFeralSenses">
        At 18th level, you gain preternatural senses that help you fight creatures you can’t see.
        When you attack a creature you can’t see, your inability to see it doesn’t impose disadvantage on your attack rolls against it.
        \n\n
        You are also aware of the location of any invisible creature within 30 feet of you, 
        provided that the creature isn’t hidden from you and you aren’t blinded or deafened.
    </string>
    
    <string name="rangerFoeSlayerTitle">
        Foe Slayer
    </string>
    <string name="rangerFoeSlayer">
        At 20th level, you become an unparalleled hunter of your enemies. Once on each of your turns, you can add your
        Wisdom  modifier to the attack roll or the damage roll of an attack you make against one of your favored enemies.
        You can choose to use this feature before or after the roll, but before any effects of the roll are applied.
    </string>





    <string name="rangerRangerArchetypesTitle">
        Ranger Archetype
    </string>
    <string name="rangerRangerArchetype">
        The ideal of the ranger has two classic expressions: the Hunter and the Beast Master.
        \n\n
        At 3rd level, you choose an archetype that you strive to emulate: Hunter or Beast Master, 
        both detailed at the end of the class description. Your choice grants you features at 3rd level and again at 7th,  11th, and  15th level.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rangerHunterTitle">
        Hunter
    </string>
    <string name="rangerHunter">
        Emulating the Hunter archetype means accepting your place as a bulwark between civilization 
        and the terrors of the wilderness. As you walk the Hunter’s path, you learn specialized techniques 
        for fighting the threats you face, from rampaging ogres and hordes of orcs to towering giants and terrifying dragons.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rangerHunterHuntersPreyTitle">
        Hunters Prey
    </string>
    <string name="rangerHunterHuntersPrey">
        At 3rd level, you gain one of the following features of your choice.
        \n\n
        <b>Colossus Slayer</b>
        \n
        Your tenacity can wear down the most potent foes. W hen you hit a creature with a weapon attack,
        the creature takes an extra  1d8 damage if it’s below its hit point maximum. You can deal this extra damage only once per turn.
        \n\n
        <b>Giant Killer</b>
        \n
        W hen a Large or larger creature within5  feet of you hits or misses
        you with an attack, you can use your reaction to attack that creature
        immediately after its attack, provided that you can see the creature.
        \n\n
        <b>Horde Breaker</b>
        \n
        Once on each of your turns when you make a weapon attack, you can make another attack
        with the same weapon against a different creature that is within 5 feet of the original target and within range of your weapon.
    </string>


    <string name="rangerHunterDefensiveTacticsTitle">
        Defensive Tactics
    </string>
    <string name="rangerHunterDefensiveTactics">
        At 7th level, you gain one of the following features of your choice.
        \n\n
        <b>Escape the Horde</b>
        \n
        Opportunity attacks against you are made with disadvantage.
        \n\n
        <b>Multiattack Defense</b>
        \n
        When a creature hits you with an attack, you gain a +4 bonus to AC against all subsequent attacks made by that creature for the rest of the turn.
        \n\n
        <b>Steel Will</b>
        \n
        You have advantage on saving throws against being frightened.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rangerHunterMultiattackTitle">
        Multiattack
    </string>
    <string name="rangerHunterMultiattack">
        At 11th level, you gain one of the following features of your choice.
        \n\n
        <b>Volley</b>
        \n
        You can use your action to make a ranged attack against any number of creatures within 10
        feet of a point you can see within your weapon’s range. You must have ammunition for each target,
        as normal, and you make a separate attack roll for each target.
        \n\n
        <b>Whirlwind Attack</b>
        \n
        You can use your action to make a melee attack against any number of creatures within 5 feet of you, with a separate attack roll for each target.
    </string>


    <string name="rangerHunterSuperiorHunterDefenseTitle">
        Superior Hunter Defense
    </string>
    <string name="rangerHunterSuperiorHunterDefense">
        At 15th level, you gain one of the following features of your choice.
        \n\n
        <b>Evasion</b>
        \n
        You can nimbly dodge out of the way of certain area effects, such as a red dragon’s fiery breath or a lightning bolt spell.
        When you are subjected to an effect that allows you to make a Dexterity saving throw to take only half damage, you instead take no damage
        if you succeed on the saving throw, and only half damage if you fail.
        \n\n
        <b>Stand Against The Tide</b>
        \n
        When a hostile creature misses you with a melee attack, you can use your reaction to force that creature to repeat the
        same attack against another creature (other than itself) of your choice.
        \n\n
        <b>Uncanny Dodge</b>
        \n
        When an attacker that you can see hits you with an attack, you can use your reaction to halve the attack’s damage against you.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rangerBeastMasterTitle">
        Beast Master
    </string>
    <string name="rangerBeastMaster">
        The Beast Master archetype em bodies a friendship between the civilized races and the beasts of the world. 
        United in focus, beast and ranger work as one to fight the monstrous foes that threaten civilization and the wilderness alike. 
        Emulating the Beast Master archetype means committing yourself to this ideal, working in partnership with an animal as its companion and friend.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rangerBeastMasterRangersCompanionTitle">
        Rangers Comapnion
    </string>
    <string name="rangerBeastMasterRangersCompanion">
        At 3rd level, you gain a beast companion that accompanies you on your adventures and is trained to fight
        alongside you. Choose a beast that is no larger than Medium and that has a challenge rating of
        1/4 or lower (appendix D presents statistics for the hawk, mastiff, and panther as examples).
        Add your proficiency bonus to the beast’s AC, attack rolls, and damage rolls, as well as to any saving
        throws and skills it is proficient in. Its hit point maximum equals its normal maximum or four times your ranger level, whichever is higher.
        \n\n
        The beast obeys your commands as best as it can. It takes its turn on your initiative, though it doesn’t take an action
        unless you command it to. On your turn, you can verbally command the beast where to move (no action required by you).
        You can use your action to verbally command it to take the Attack, Dash, Disengage, Dodge, or Help action. Once you have the
        Extra Attack feature, you can make one weapon attack yourself when you command the beast to take the Attack action.
        \n\n
        While traveling through your favored terrain with only the beast, you can move stealthily at a normal pace.
        \n\n
        If the beast dies, you can obtain another one by spending 8 hours magically bonding with another beast that isn’t hostile to you, 
        either the same type of beast as before or a different one
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rangerBeastMasterExceptionalTrainingTitle">
        Exceptional Training
    </string>
    <string name="rangerBeastMasterExceptionalTraining">
        Beginning at 7th level, on any of your turns when your beast companion doesn’t attack, you
        can use a bonus action to command the beast to take the Dash, Disengage, Dodge, or Help action on its turn.
    </string>



    <string name="rangerBeastMasterBestialFuryTitle">
        Bestial Fury
    </string>
    <string name="rangerBeastMasterBestialFury">
        Starting at 11th level, your beast companion can make two attacks when you command it to use the Attack action.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="rangerBeastMasterShareSpellsTitle">
        Share Spells
    </string>
    <string name="rangerBeastMasterShareSpells">
        Beginning at  15th level, when you cast a spell targeting yourself, you can also affect your
        beast companion with the spell if the beast is within 30 feet of you.
    </string>
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
    
</resources>