<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="rogue_introduction">
        Signaling for her companions to wait, a halfling creeps
        forward through the dungeon hall. She presses an ear
        to the door, then pulls out a set of tools and picks the
        lock in the blink of an eye. Then she disappears into
        the shadows as her fighter friend moves forward to kick
        the door open.

        \n\nA human lurks in the shadows of an alley while his
        accomplice prepares for her part in the ambush. When
        their target — a notorious slaver — passes the alleyway,
        the accomplice cries out, the slaver comes to investigate,
        and the assassin’s blade cuts his throat before he can
        make a sound.

        \n\nSuppressing a giggle, a gnome waggles her fingers
        and magically lifts the key ring from the guard’s belt.
        In a moment, the keys are in her hand, the cell door is
        open, and she and her companions are free to make
        their escape.

        \n\nRogues rely on skill, stealth, and their foes’
        vulnerabilities to get the upper hand in any situation.
        They have a knack for finding the solution to just about
        any problem , demonstrating a resourcefulness and
        versatility that is the cornerstone of any successful
        adventuring party.

    </string>

    <string name="creating_rogue_string">
        As you create your rogue character, consider the
        character’s relationship to the law. Do you have a
        criminal past—or present? Are you on the run from the
        law or from an angry thieves’ guild master? Or did you
        leave your guild in search of bigger risks and bigger
        rewards? Is it greed that drives you in your adventures,
        or some other desire or ideal?

        \n\nWhat was the trigger that led you away from your
        previous life? Did a great con or heist gone terribly
        wrong cause you to reevaluate your career? Maybe
        you were lucky and a successful robbery gave you the
        coin you needed to escape the squalor of your life.
        Did wanderlust finally call you away from your home?
        Perhaps you suddenly found yourself cut off from your
        family or your mentor, and you had to find a new means
        of support. Or maybe you made a new friend—another
        member of your adventuring party — who showed you
        new possibilities for earning a living and employing
        your particular talents.

    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="rogue_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Experise,
        \nSneak Attack,
        \Thieves' Cant
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Cunning Action
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        Roguish Archetype
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_5th_lvl_abilities">
        Uncanny Dodge
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Expertise
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_7th_lvl_abilities">
        Evasion
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_9th_lvl_abilities">
        Roguish Archetype Feature
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_11th_lvl_abilities">
        Reliable Talent
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_13th_lvl_abilities">
        Roguish Archetype Feature
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Blindsense
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_15th_lvl_abilities">
        Slippery Mind
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_17th_lvl_abilities">
        Roguish Archetype Feature
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Elusive
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Stroke of Luck
    </string>

    //---------------------------------------------------------Spell Table---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="rogue_table2_label">
        Rogue Table
    </string>



    <string name="rogue_table2_value2_1to2_values">
        1d6
    </string>


    <string name="rogue_table2_value2_3to4_values">
        2d6
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_table2_value2_5to6_values">
        3d6
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_table2_value2_7to8_values">
        4d6
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_table2_value2_9to10_values">
       5d6
    </string>


    <string name="rogue_table2_value2_11to12_values">
        6d6
    </string>


    <string name="rogue_table2_value2_13to14_values">
        7d6
    </string>


    <string name="rogue_table2_value2_15to16_values">
        8d6
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_table2_value2_17to18_values">
       9d6
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_table2_value2_19to20_values">
        10d6
    </string>

    <string name="rogue_table2_value2_label">
        Sneak Attack
    </string>

    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="rogueFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a rogue, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="rogueHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d8 per rogue lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 8 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d8(or 5) + Constitution Modifier per rogue level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="rogueProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> Light armor
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Simple weapons, hand crossbows, longswords, rapiers, shortswords
        \n<b>Tools:</b> Thieves tools
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Dexterity, Intelligence
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose four from Acrobatics, Athletics, Deception, Insight, Intimidation, Investigation, Perception, Performance, Persuation, Sleight of Hand, Stealth
    </string>

    <string name="rogueEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background:
        \n\n- (a) a rapier (b) a shortsword
        \n- (a) a shortbow with 20 arrows or (b) a shortsword
        \n- (a) a burglars pack, (b) a dungeoners pack or (c) an explorers pack
        \n- Leather Armor, two daggers and thieves tools
    </string>



    //------------------------------------------------ABILITIES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="rogueExpertiseTitle">
        Expertise
    </string>
    <string name="rogueExpertise">
        At 1st level, choose two of your skill proficiencies, or one of your skill proficiencies and
        your proficiency with thieves’ tools. Your proficiency bonus is doubled for any ability check
        you make that uses either of the chosen proficiencies.
        \n\n
        At 6th level, you can choose two more of your proficiencies (in skills or with thieves’ tools) to gain this benefit
    </string>

    <string name="rogueSneakAttackTitle">
        Sneak Attack
    </string>
    <string name="rogueSneakAttack">
        Beginning at 1st level, you know how to strike subtly and exploit a foe’s distraction.
        Once per turn, you can deal an extra 1d6 damage to one creature you hit with an attack
        if you have advantage on the attack roll. The attack must use a finesse or a ranged weapon.
        \n\n
        You don’t need advantage on the attack roll if another enemy of the target is within 5
        feet of it, that enemy isn’t incapacitated, and you don’t have disadvantage on the attack roll.
        \n\n
        The amount of the extra damage increases as you gain levels in this class, as shown in the Sneak Attack column of the Rogue table.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueThievesCantTitle">
        Thieves Cant
    </string>
    <string name="rogueThievesCant">
        During your rogue training you learned thieves’ cant,
        a secret mix of dialect, jargon, and code that allows you to hide
        messages in seemingly normal conversation. Only another creature that knows
        thieves’ cant understands such messages. It takes four times longer to
        convey such a message than it does to speak the same idea plainly.
        \n\n
        In addition, you understand a set of secret signs and symbols used to convey short, simple messages, 
        such as whether an area is dangerous or the territory of a thieves’ guild, whether loot is nearby, or 
        whether the people in an area are easy marks or will provide a safe house for thieves on the run.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueCunningActionTitle">
        Cunning Action
    </string>
    <string name="rogueCunningAction">
        Starting at 2nd level, your quick thinking and agility allow you to move and act quickly.
        You can take a bonus action on each of your turns in combat. This action can be used only to take the Dash, Disengage, or Hide action.
    </string>


    <string name="rogueUncannyDodgeTitle">
        Uncanny Dodge
    </string>
    <string name="rogueUncannyDodge">
        Starting at 5th level, when an attacker that you can see hits you with an attack, you can use your reaction to halve the attack’s damage against you.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueEvasionTitle">
        Evasion
    </string>
    <string name="rogueEvasion">
        Beginning at 7th level, you can nimbly dodge out of the way of certain area effects, such as a red dragon’s 
        fiery breath or an ice storm spell. When you are subjected to an effect that allows you to make a Dexterity 
        saving throw to take only half damage, you instead take no damage if you succeed on the saving throw, and only half damage if you fail.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="rogueReliableTalentTitle">
        Reliable Talent
    </string>
    <string name="rogueReliableTalent">
        By 11th level, you have refined your chosen skills until they approach perfection. 
        Whenever you make an ability check that lets you add your proficiency bonus, you can treat a d20 roll of 9 or lower as a  10.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueBlindSenseTitle">
        Blind Sense
    </string>
    <string name="rogueBlindSense">
        Starting at  14th level, if you are able to hear, you are aware of the location of any hidden or invisible creature within  10 feet of you.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="rogueSlipperyMindTitle">
        Slippery Mind
    </string>
    <string name="rogueSlipperyMind">
        Starting at  14th level, if you are able to hear, you are aware of the location of any hidden or invisible creature within  10 feet of you.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueElusiveTitle">
        Elusive
    </string>
    <string name="rogueElusive">
        Beginning at  18th level, you are so evasive that attackers rarely gain the upper hand against you. No attack roll has advantage against you while you aren’t incapacitated.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueStrokeOfLuckTitle">
        Stroke of Luck
    </string>
    <string name="rogueStrokeOfLuck">
        At 20th level, you have an uncanny knack for succeeding when you need to. If your attack misses
        a target within range, you can turn the miss into a hit. Alternatively, if you fail an ability check, you can treat the d20 roll as a 20.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a short or long rest.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="rogueRoguishArchetypesTitle">
        Roguish Archetypes
    </string>
    <string name="rogueRoguishArchetypes">
        Rogues have many features in common, including their emphasis on perfecting their skills,
        their precise and deadly approach to combat, and their increasingly quick reflexes.
        But different rogues steer those talents in varying directions, em bodied by the rogue archetypes.
        Your choice of archetype is a reflection of your focus— not necessarily an indication of your chosen profession, but a description of your preferred techniques.
        \n\n
        At 3rd level, you choose an archetype that you emulate in the exercise of your rogue abilities: Thief, Assassin, or Arcane Trickster, all detailed at the end of 
        the class description. Your archetype choice grants you features at 3rd level and then again at 9th,  13th, and 17th level.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueThiefTitle">
        Thief
    </string>
    <string name="rogueThief">
        You hone your skills in the larcenous arts. Burglars, bandits, 
        cutpurses, and other criminals typically follow this archetype, but so do rogues who 
        prefer to think of themselves as professional treasure seekers, explorers, delvers, and 
        investigators. In addition to improving your agility and stealth, you learn skills useful for delving 
        into ancient ruins, reading unfamiliar languages, and using magic items you normally couldn’t employ.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueThiefFastHandsTitle">
        Fast Hands
    </string>
    <string name="rogueThiefFastHands">
        Starting at 3rd level, you can use the bonus action granted by your Cunning Action to make a 
        Dexterity (Sleight of Hand) check, use your thieves’ tools to disarm a trap or open a lock, or take the Use an Object action.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueThiefSecondStoryWorkTitle">
        Second-Story Work
    </string>
    <string name="rogueThiefSecondStoryWork">
        When you choose this archetype at 3rd level, you gain the ability to climb faster than normal; climbing no longer costs you extra movement.
        \n\n
        In addition, when you make a running jump, the distance you cover increases by a number of feet equal to your Dexterity modifier.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueThiefSupremeSneakTitle">
        Supreme Sneak
    </string>
    <string name="rogueThiefSupremeSneak">
        Starting at 9th level, you have advantage on a Dexterity (Stealth) check if you move no more than half your speed on the same turn.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueThiefUseMagicDeviceTitle">
        Use Magic Device
    </string>
    <string name="rogueThiefUseMagicDevice">
        By 13th level, you have learned enough about the workings of magic that you can improvise the use 
        of items even when they are not intended for you. You ignore all class, race, and level requirements on the use of magic items.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueThiefThiefsReflexTitle">
        Thiefs Reflex
    </string>
    <string name="rogueThiefThiefsReflex">
        When you reach 17th level, you have become adept at laying ambushes and quickly escaping danger.
        You can take two turns during the first round of any combat. You take your first turn at your normal initiative and your
        second turn at your initiative minus  10. You can’t use this feature when you are surprised.
    </string>



    <string name="rogueAssassinTitle">
        Assassin
    </string>
    <string name="rogueAssassin">
        You focus your training on the grim art of death. Those who adhere to this archetype are diverse: 
        hired killers, spies, bounty hunters, and even specially anointed priests trained to exterminate the 
        enemies of their deity. Stealth, poison, and disguise help you eliminate your foes with deadly efficiency.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="rogueAssassinBonusProficiencyTitle">
        Bonus Proficiency
    </string>
    <string name="rogueAssassinBonusProficiency">
        When you choose this archetype at 3rd level, you gain proficiency with the disguise kit and the poisoner’s kit.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueAssassinAssassinateTitle">
        Assassinate
    </string>
    <string name="rogueAssassinAssassinate">
        Starting at 3rd level, you are at your deadliest when you get the drop on your enemies. You have advantage on attack rolls 
        against any creature that hasn’t taken a turn in the combat yet. In addition, any hit you score against a creature that is surprised is a critical hit.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="rogueAssassinInfiltrationExpertiseTitle">
        Infiltration Expertise
    </string>
    <string name="rogueAssassinInfiltrationExpertise">
        Starting at 9th level, you can unfailingly create false identities for yourself.
        You must spend seven days and 25 gp to establish the history, profession, and affiliations
        for an identity. You can’t establish an identity that belongs to someone else. For example,
        you might acquire appropriate clothing, letters of introduction, and official- looking certification
        to establish yourself as a member of a trading house from a remote city so you can insinuate yourself into the company of other wealthy merchants.
        \n\n
        Thereafter, if you adopt the new identity as a disguise, other creatures believe you to be that person until given an obvious reason not to.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueAssassinImpostorTitle">
        Impostor
    </string>
    <string name="rogueAssassinImpostor">
        At  13th level, you gain the ability to unerringly mimic another person’s speech, writing, and behavior.You must spend at
        least three hours studying these three components of the person’s behavior, listening to speech, examining handwriting, and observing mannerisms.
        \n\n
        Your ruse is indiscernible to the casual observer. If a wary creature suspects something is amiss, 
        you have advantage on any Charisma (Deception) check you make to avoid detection.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueAssassinDeathStrikeTitle">
        Death Strike
    </string>
    <string name="rogueAssassinDeathStrike">
        Starting at  17th level, you becom e a master of instant death. When you attack and hit a creature that is surprised, it must make a Constitution 
        saving throw (DC 8 + your Dexterity modifier + your proficiency bonus). On a failed save, double the damage of your attack against the creature.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueArcaneTricksterTitle">
        Arcane Trickster
    </string>
    <string name="rogueArcaneTrickster">
        Some rogues enhance their fine-honed skills of stealth and agility with magic, learning tricks of enchantment and illusion. 
        These rogues include pickpockets and burglars, but also pranksters, mischief-makers, and a significant number of adventurers.
    </string>

    
    <string name="rogueArcaneTricksterMageHandLegerdemainTitle">
        Mage Hand Legerdemain
    </string>
    <string name="rogueArcaneTricksterMageHandLegerdemain">
        Starting at 3rd level, when you cast mage hand, you can make the spectral hand invisible, and you can perform the following additional tasks with it:
        \n
        •\tYou can stow one object the hand is holding in a container worn or carried by another creature.
        \n
        •\tYou can retrieve an object in a container worn or carried by another creature.
        \n
        •\tYou can use thieves’ tools to pick locks and disarm traps at range.
        \n\n
        You can perform one of these tasks without being noticed by a creature if you succeed on a
        Dexterity (Sleight of Hand) check contested by the creature’s Wisdom  (Perception) check.
        \n\n
        In addition, you can use the bonus action granted by your Cunning Action to control the hand.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="rogueArcaneTricksterMagicalAmbushTitle">
        Magical Ambush
    </string>
    <string name="rogueArcaneTricksterMagicalAmbush">
        Starting at 9th level, if you are hidden from a creature when you cast a spell on it, 
        the creature has disadvantage on any saving throw it makes against the spell this turn.
    </string>


    <string name="rogueArcaneTricksterVersatileTricksterTitle">
        Versatile Trickster
    </string>
    <string name="rogueArcaneTricksterVersatileTrickster">
        At  13th level, you gain the ability to distract targets with your mage hand. As a bonus action on your turn, you can designate a creature 
        within 5 feet of the spectral hand created by the spell. Doing so gives you advantage on attack rolls against that creature until the end of the turn.
    </string>

    
    
    <string name="rogueArcaneTricksterSpellThiefTitle">
        Spell Thief
    </string>
    <string name="rogueArcaneTricksterSpellThief">
        At 17th level, you gain the ability to magically steal the knowledge of how to cast a spell from another spellcaster.
        \n\n
        Immediately after a creature casts a spell that targets you or includes you in its area of effect, you can use your
        reaction to force the creature to make a saving throw with its spellcasting ability modifier. The DC equals your
        spell save DC. On a failed save, you negate the spell’s effect against you, and you steal the knowledge of the spell
        if it is at least  1st level and of a level you can cast (it doesn’t need to be a wizard spell). For the next 8 hours,
        you know the spell and can cast it using your spell slots. The creature can’t cast that spell until the 8 hours have passed.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a long rest.
    </string>


    
    
    
    
</resources>