<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="sorcerer_introduction">
        Golden eyes flashing, a human
        stretches out her hand and unleashes
        the dragonfire that burns in her veins.
        As an in ferno rages around her foes,
        leathery wings spread from her back and
        she takes to the air.

        \n\nLong hair whipped by a conjured wind,
        a half-elf spreads his arms wide and throws
        his head back. Lifting him momentarily off
        the ground, a wave of magic surges up in him,
        through him , and out from him in a mighty blast
        of lightning.

        \n\nCrouching behind a stalagmite, a halfling points a
        finger at a charging troglodyte. A blast of fire springs
        from her finger to strike the creature. She ducks back
        behind the rock formation with a grin, unaware that her
        wild magic has turned her skin bright blue.

        \n\nSorcerers carry a magical birthright conferred
        upon them by an exotic bloodline, some other worldly
        influence, or exposure to unknown cosmic forces.
        One can’t study sorcery as one learns a language, any
        more than one can learn to live a legendary life. No one
        chooses sorcery; the power chooses the sorcerer.
    </string>

    <string name="create_sorcerer_string">
        The most important question to consider when creating
        your sorcerer is the origin of your power. As a starting
        character, you will choose an origin that ties to a draconic
        bloodline or the influence of wild magic, but the exact
        source of your power is up to you to decide. Is it a family
        curse, passed down to you from distant ancestors? Or
        did some extraordinary event leave you blessed with
        inherent magic but perhaps scarred as well?

        \n\nHow do you feel about the magical power coursing
        through you? Do you embrace it, try to master it, or
        revel in its unpredictable nature? Is it a blessing or
        a curse? Did you seek it out, or did it find you? Did
        you have the option to refuse it, and do you wish you
        had? What do you intend to do with it? Perhaps you
        feel like you’ve been given this power for some lofty
        purpose. Or you might decide that the power gives you
        the right to do what you want, to take what you want
        from those who lack such power. Perhaps your power
        links you to a powerful individual in the world — the fey
        creature that blessed you at birth, the dragon who put
        a drop of its blood into your veins, the lich who created
        you as an experiment, or the deity who chose you to
        carry this power.

    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="sorcerer_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Spellcasting,
        \nSorcerous Origin
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Font of Magic
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        Metamagic
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_5th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Sorcerous Origin Feature
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_7th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_9th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Metamagic
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_11th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_13th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Sorcerous Origin Feature
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_15th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_17th_lvl_abilities">
        Metamagic
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Sorcerous Origin Feature
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Sorcerous Restoration
    </string>

    //---------------------------------------------------------Spell Table---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="sorcerer_table2_label">
        Spells Table
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_label">
        Sorcerery \nPoints
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value3_label">
        Cantrip \nKnown
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_label">
        Spells Known
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_1">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_2">
       2
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_3">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_4">
        4
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_5">
        5
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_6">
        6
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_7">
       7
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_8">
       8
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_9">
        9
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_10">
        10
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_11">
        11
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_12">
        12
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_13">
        13
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_14">
        14
    </string>
    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_15">
        15
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_16">
        16
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_17">
        17
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_18">
        18
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_19">
        19
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value2_20">
        20
    </string>






    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value3_1to3_values">
        4
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value3_4to9_values">
        5
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value3_10to20_values">
        6
    </string>




    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_1values">
        2
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_2values">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_3values">
        4
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_4values">
        5
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_5values">
        6
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_6values">
        7
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_7values">
        8
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_8values">
        9
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_9values">
        10
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_10values">
        11
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_11to12values">
        12
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_13to14values">
        13
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_15to16values">
        14
    </string>

    <string name="sorcerer_table2_value4_17to20values">
        15
    </string>


    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="sorcererFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a sorcerer, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="sorcererHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d6 per sorcerer lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 6 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d6(or 4) + Constitution Modifier per sorcerer level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="sorcererProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> None
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Daggers, darts, slings, quarterstaffs, light crossbows
        \n<b>Tools:</b> None
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Constitution, Charisma
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose two from Arcana, Deception, Insight, Intimidation, Persuation, Religion
    </string>

    <string name="sorcererEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background:
        \n\n- (a) light crossbow with 20 bolts or (b) any simple weapon
        \n- (a) a component puch or (b) an arcane focus
        \n- (a) a dungeoners pack or (b) an explorers pack
        \n- Two daggers
    </string>



    //------------------------------------------ABILITIES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="sorcererFontOfMagicTitle">
        Font of Magic
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererFontOfMagic">
        At 2nd level, you tap into a deep wellspring of magic within yourself. 
        This wellspring is represented by sorcery points, which allow you to create a variety of magical effects.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="sorcererSorceryPointsTitle">
        Sorcery Points
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererSorceryPoints">
        ou have 2 sorcery points, and you gain more as you reach higher levels, 
        as shown in the Sorcery Points column of the Sorcerer table. You can never 
        have more sorcery points than shown on the table for your level. 
        You regain all spent sorcery points when you finish a long rest.
    </string>
    

    <string name="sorcererFlexibleCastingTitle">
        Flexible Casting
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererFlexibleCasting">
        You can use your sorcery points to gain additional spell slots,
        or sacrifice spell slots to gain additional sorcery points. You learn other ways to use your sorcery points as you reach higher levels.
        \n\n
        <b>Creating Spell Slots</b>
        \n
        ou can transform unexpended sorcery points into one spell slot as a bonus action on your turn. The Creating Spell
        Slots table shows the cost of creating a spell slot of a given level. You can create spell slots no higher in level than 5th.
        \n\n
        <b>Spell Slot Lvl \t\t\t Sorcery Point Cost</b>
        \n
        1st \t\t\t 2
        \n
        2nd \t\t\t 3
        \n
        3rd \t\t\t 5
        \n
        4th \t\t\t 6
        \n
        5th \t\t\t 7
        \n\n
        <b>Converting a Spell Slot to Sorcery Points</b>
        \n
        As a bonus action on your turn, you can expend one spell slot and gain a number of sorcery points equal to the slot’s level.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="sorcererMetamagicTitle">
        Metamagic
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererMetamagic">
        At 3rd level, you gain the ability to twist your spells to suit your needs.
        You gain two of the following Metamagic options of your choice. You gain another one at 10th and  17th level.
        \n
        You can use only one Metamagic option on a spell when you cast it, unless otherwise noted.

    </string>



    <string name="sorcererCarefuillSpellTitle">
        Careful Spell
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererCarefullSpell">
        When you cast a spell that forces other creatures to make a saving throw,
        you can protect som e of those creatures from the spell’s full force. To do so,
        you spend 1 sorcery point and choose a number of those creatures up to your Charisma
        modifier (minimum of one creature). A chosen creature automatically succeeds on its saving throw against the spell.
    </string>


    
    <string name="sorcererDistantSpellTitle">
        Distant Spell
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererDistantSpell">
        When you cast a spell that has a range of 5 feet or greater, you can spend  1  sorcery point to double the range of the spell.
        \n\n
        When you cast a spell that has a range of touch, you can spend  1  sorcery point to make the range of the spell 30 feet.
    </string>


    <string name="sorcererEmpoweredSpellTitle">
        Empowered Magic
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererEmpoweredSpell">
        When you roll damage for a spell, you can spend  1 sorcery point to reroll a number of the damage
        dice up to your Charisma modifier (minimum of one). You must use the new rolls.
        \n\n
        You can use Empowered Spell even if you have already used a different Metamagic option during the casting of the spell.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="sorcererExtendedSpellTitle">
        Extended Spell
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererExtendedSpell">
        When you cast a spell that has a duration of 1  minute or longer, you can spend  1  sorcery point to double its duration, to a maximum duration of 24 hours.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="sorcererHeightenedSpellTitle">
        Heightened Spell
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererHeightenedSpell">
        When you cast a spell that forces a creature to make a saving throw to resist its effects, 
        \you can spend 3 sorcery points to give one target of the spell disadvantage on its first saving throw made against the spell.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="sorcererQuickenedSpellTitle">
        Quickened Spell
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererQuickenedSpell">
        When you cast a spell that has a casting time of 1  action, you can spend 2 sorcery points to change the casting time to  1  bonus action for this casting.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="sorcererSubtleSpellTitle">
        Subtle Spell
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererSubtleSpell">
        When you cast a spell, you can spend  1  sorcery point to cast it without any somatic or verbal components.
    </string>
    
    <string name="sorcererTwindedSpellTitle">
        Twinned Spell
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererTwindedSpell">
        When you cast a spell that targets only one creature and doesn’t have a range of self, you can spend a number of sorcery
        points equal to the spell’s level to target a second creature in range with the same spell (1  sorcery point if the spell is a cantrip).
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="sorcererSorcerousRestorationTitle">
        Sorcerous Restoration
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererSorcerousRestoration">
        At 20th level, you regain 4 expended sorcery points whenever you finish a short rest.
    </string>
    

    <string name="sorcererSorcerousOriginTitle">
        Sorcerous Origin
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererSorcerousOrigin">
        Different sorcerers claim different origins for their innate magic.
        Although many variations exist, most of these origins fall into two categories: a draconic bloodline and wild magic.
        \n\n
        Choose a sorcerous origin, which describes the source of your innate magical power: Draconic Bloodline or Wild Magic,
        both detailed at the end of the class description.
        \n\n
        Your choice grants you features when you choose it at 1st level and again at 6th,  14th, and 18th level.
    </string>


    
    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodlineTitle">
        Draconic Bloodline
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodline">
        Your innate magic com es from draconic magic that was mingled with your blood or that of your ancestors.
        Most often, sorcerers with this origin trace their descent back to a mighty sorcerer of ancient times
        who made a bargain with a dragon or who might even have claimed a dragon parent. Som e of these bloodlines are
        well established in the world, but most are obscure. Any given sorcerer could be the first of a new bloodline,
        as a result of a pact or som e other exceptional circumstance.
    </string>
    


    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodlineDragonAncestorTitle">
        Dragon Ancestor
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodlineDragonAncestor">
        At  1st level, you choose one type of dragon as your ancestor. The damage type associated with each dragon is used by features you gain later.
        \n\n
        <b>Dragon \t\t\t Damage Type</b>
        \n
        Black \t\t\t\t\t Acid
        \n
        Blue \t\t\t\t\t\t Lightning
        \n
        Brass \t\t\t\t\t Fire
        \n
        Bronze \t\t\t Lightning
        \n
        Copper \t\t\t Acid
        \n
        Gold \t\t\t\t\t Fire
        \n
        Green \t\t\t\t Poison
        \n
        Red \t\t\t\t\t\t Fire
        \n
        Silver \t\t\t\t\t Cold
        \n
        White \t\t\t\t\t Cold
        \n\n
        You can speak, read, and write Draconic. Additionally, whenever you
        make a Charisma check when interacting with dragons, your proficiency bonus is doubled if it applies to the check.
    </string>
    

    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodlineDraconicResilenceTitle">
        Draconic Resilience
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodlineDraconicResilence">
        As magic flows through your body, it causes physical traits of your dragon ancestors to emerge.
        At 1st level, your hit point maximum increases by 1  and increases by 1  again whenever you gain a level in this class.
        \n\n
        Additionally, parts of your skin are covered by a thin sheen of dragon-like scales. When you aren’t wearing armor, your AC equals  13 + your Dexterity modifier.
    </string>



    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodlineElementalAffinityTitle">
        Elemental Affinity
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodlineElementalAffinity">
        Starting at 6th level, when you cast a spell that deals damage of the type associated with your draconic ancestry,
        add your Charisma modifier to that damage.At the same time, you can spend  1  sorcery point to gain resistance to that damage type for 1  hour.
    </string>


    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodlineDragonWingsTitle">
        Dragon Wings
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodlineDragonWings">
        At 14th level, you gain the ability to sprout a pair of dragon wings from your back, gaining a flying speed equal to your current speed.
        You can create these wings as a bonus action on your turn. They last until you dismiss them as a bonus action on your turn.
        \n\n
        You can’t manifest your wings while wearing armor unless the armor is made to accommodate them, and clothing not made to accommodate your wings might be destroyed when you manifest them.
    </string>

    
    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodlineDraconicPresenceTitle">
        Draconic Presence
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererDraconicBloodlineDraconicPresence">
        Beginning at  18th level, you can channel the dread presence of your dragon ancestor, causing those 
        around you to becom e awestruck or frightened. As an action, you can spend 5 sorcery points to 
        draw on this power and exude an aura of awe or fear (your choice) to a distance of 60 feet. 
        For  1  minute or until you lose your concentration (as if you were casting a concentration spell), 
        each hostile creature that starts its turn in this aura must succeed on a W isdom  saving throw or be 
        charmed (if you chose awe) or frightened (if you chose fear) until the aura ends. A creature that 
        succeeds on this saving throw is immune to your aura for 24 hours.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="sorcererWildMagicTitle">
        Wild Magic
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererWildMagic">
        Your innate magic com es from the wild forces of chaos that underlie the order of creation. 
        You might have endured exposure to som e form of raw magic, perhaps through a planar portal 
        leading to Limbo, the Elemental Planes, or the mysterious Far Realm. Perhaps you were blessed 
        by a powerful fey creature or marked by a demon. Or your magic could be a fluke of your birth, 
        with no apparent cause or reason. However it came to be, this chaotic magic churns within you, waiting for any outlet.
    </string>
    

    <string name="sorcererWildMagicWildMagicSurgeTitle">
        Wild Magic Surge
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererWildMagicWildMagicSurge">
        tarting when you choose this origin at  1st level, your spellcasting can unleash surges of untamed magic.
        Immediately after you cast a sorcerer spell of 1st level or higher, the DM can have you roll a d20. If you roll
        a 1, roll on the Wild Magic Surge table to create a random magical effect.
    </string>
    
    <string name="sorcererWildMagicTidesOfChaosTitle">
        Tides Of Chaos
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererWildMagicTidesOfChaos">
        Starting at  1st level, you can manipulate the forces of chance and chaos to gain
        advantage on one attack roll, ability check, or saving throw. Once you do so, you must finish a long rest before you can use this feature again.
        \n\n
        Any time before you regain the use of this feature, the DM can have you roll on the Wild Magic Surge table 
        immediately after you cast a sorcerer spell of 1st level or higher. You then regain the use of this feature.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="sorcererWildMagicBendLuckTitle">
        Bend Luck
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererWildMagicBendLuck">
        Starting at 6th level, you have the ability to twist fate using your wild magic.
        When another creature you can see makes an attack roll, an ability check, or a saving throw,
        you can use your reaction and spend 2 sorcery points to roll  1d4 and apply the number rolled as a bonus or penalty (your choice) to the creature’s roll.
        You can do so after the creature rolls but before any effects of the roll occur.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="sorcererWildMagicControlledChaosTitle">
        Controlled Chaos
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererWildMagicControlledChaos">
        At 14th level, you gain a modicum of control over the surges of your wild magic. 
        Whenever you roll on the Wild Magic Surge table, you can roll twice and use either number.
    </string>


    <string name="sorcererWildMagicSpellBombardmentTitle">
        Spell Bombardment
    </string>
    <string name="sorcererWildMagicSpellBombardment">
        Beginning at  18th level, the harmful energy of your spells intensifies. When you roll damage for a spell and roll the highest number possible on any of the dice,
        choose one of those dice, roll it again and add that roll to the damage. You can use the feature only once per turn.
    </string>
    
    

    <string name="WildMagicSurge0_2">
        Roll on this table at the start of each of your turns for the next minute, ignoring this result on subsequent rolls.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge3_4">
        For the next minute, you can see any invisible creature if you have line of sight to it.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge5_4">
        A modron chosen and controlled  by the DM  appears in an unoccupied space within  5 feet o f you, then disappears  1  minute later
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge7_4">
        You cast fireballas a 3rd-level spell centered on yourself.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge9_4">
        You cast m agic missileas a 5th-level spell.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge11_4">
        Roll a d10. Your height changes by a number of inches equal to the roll.  If the roll is odd, you shrink. If the roll is even, you grow.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge13_4">
        You cast confusioncentered on yourself.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge15_4">
        For the next minute, you regain 5 hit points at the start of each o f your turns.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge17_4">
        You grow a long beard made of feathers that remains until you sneeze, at which  point the feathers explode out from your face.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge19_4">
        You cast greasecentered on yourself.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge21_4">
        Creatures have disadvantage on saving throws against the next spell you cast in the next minute that involves a saving throw.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge23_4">
        Your skin turns a vibrant shade of blue. A remove cursespell can end this effect.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge25_4">
        An eye appears on your forehead for the next minute. During that time, you have advantage on Wisdom (Perception)  checks that rely on sight.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge27_4">
        For the next minute, all your spells with a casting time of 1  action have a casting time of 1  bonus action.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge29_4">
        You teleport up to 60 feet to an unoccupied space of your choice that you can  see.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge31_4">
        You are transported to the Astral  Plane until the end of your next turn, after which time you
        return to the space you  previously occupied or the nearest unoccupied space if that space is occupied.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge33_4">
        Maximize the damage of the next damaging spell you cast within the next minute.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge35_4">
        Roll a d10. Your age changes by a number of years equal to the roll.  If the roll is odd, you get younger (minimum  1  year old).  If the roll is even, you get older.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge37_4">
        1d6 flumphs controlled by the DM appear in unoccupied spaces within 60 feet o f you and are frightened of you. They vanish after 1  minute.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge39_4">
        You regain 2d10 hit points.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge41_4">
        You turn into a potted plant until the start of your next turn.
        While a plant, you are incapacitated and have vulnerability to all damage.
        If you drop to 0 hit points, your pot breaks, and your form  reverts.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge43_4">
        For the next minute, you can teleport up to 20 feet as a bonus action on each o f your turns.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge45_4">
        You cast levitateon yourself.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge47_4">
         unicorn controlled by the DM  appears in a space within  5 feet o f you, then disappears 1  minute later.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge49_4">
        You can’t speak for the next minute. Whenever you try, pink bubbles float out of your mouth.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge51_4">
        A spectral shield hovers  near you for the next minute, granting you a +2 bonus to AC and immunity to m agicmissile.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge53_4">
        You are immune to being intoxicated  by alcohol for the next 5d6 days.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge55_4">
        Your hair falls out but grows back within 24 hours.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge57_4">
        For the next minute, any flammable object you touch that isn’t being worn or carried by another creature bursts into flame.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge59_4">
        You regain your lowest-level expended spell  slot.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge61_4">
        For the next minute, you  must shout when you speak.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge63_4">
        You cast fog cloudcentered on yourself.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge65_4">
        Up to three creatures you choose within 30 feet of you take 4d10 lightning damage.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge67_4">
        You are frightened  by the nearest creature until the end of your next turn.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge69_4">
        Each creature within 30 feet of you  becomes invisible for the next minute. The invisibility ends on a creature when it attacks or casts a spell.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge71_4">
        You gain  resistance to all damage for the next minute.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge73_4">
        A random creature within 60 feet of you becomes poisoned for 1d4 hours.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge75_4">
        You glow with  bright light in a 30-foot radius for the next minute. Any creature that ends its turn within  5 feet o f you is blinded until the end of its next turn.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge77_4">
        You cast polym orphon yourself.  If you fail the saving throw, you turn into a sheep for the spell’s duration.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge79_4">
        Illusory butterflies and flower petals flutter in the air within  10 feet of you for the next minute.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge81_4">
        You can take one additional action  immediately.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge83_4">
        Each creature within 30 feet of you takes  1d10 necrotic damage. You  regain hit points equal to the sum of the necrotic damage dealt.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge85_4">
        You cast mirror image.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge87_4">
        You cast flyon a random creature within 60 feet of you
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge89_4">
        You become invisible for the next minute.  During that time, other creatures can’t hear you. The invisibility ends if you attack or cast a spell.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge91_4">
        If you die within the next minute, you immediately come back to life as if by the reincarnatespell.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge93_4">
        Your size increases by one size category for the next minute.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge95_4">
        You and all creatures within 30 feet o f you gain vulnerability to piercing damage for the next minute.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge97_4">
        Yu are surrounded  by faint, ethereal  music for the next minute.
    </string>
    <string name="WildMagicSurge99_4">
        You regain all expended sorcery points.
    </string>



</resources>