<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="warlock_introduction">

        With a pseudodragon curled on his shoulder, a young
        elf in golden robes smiles warmly, weaving a magical
        charm into his honeyed words and bending the palace
        sentinel to his will.

        \n\nAs flames spring to life in her hands, a wizened
        human whispers the secret name of her demonic patron,
        infusing her spell with fiendish magic.

        \n\nShifting his gaze between a battered tome and the
        od dalignment of the stars overhead, a wild - eyed tiefling
        chants the mystic ritual that will open a doorway to a
        distant world.

        \n\nWarlocks are seekers of the knowledge that lies
        hidden in the fabric of the multiverse. Through pacts
        made with mysterious beings of supernatural power,
        warlocks unlock magical effects both subtle and
        spectacular. Drawing on the ancient know ledge of
        beings such as fey nobles, demons, devils, hags, and
        alien entities of the Far Realm, warlock s piece together
        arcane secrets to bolster their own power.


    </string>

    <string name="creating_warlock_string">
        As you make your warlock character, spend some time
        thinking about your patron and the obligations that
        your pact imposes upon you. What led you to make the
        pact, and how did you make contact with your patron?
        Were you seduced into summoning a devil, or did you
        seek out the ritual that would allow you to make contact
        with an alien elder god? Did you search for your patron,
        or did your patron find and choose you? Do you chafe
        under the obligations of your pact or serve joyfully in
        anticipation of the rewards promised to you?

        \n\nWork with your DM to determine how big a part your
        pact will play in your character’s adventuring career.
        Your patron’s demands might drive you into adventures,
        or they might consist entirely of small favors you can do
        between adventures.

        \n\nWhat kind of relationship do you have with your
        patron? Is it friendly, antagonistic, uneasy, or romantic?
        How important does your patron consider you to be?
        What part do you play in your patron’s plans? Do you
        know other servants of your patron?

        \n\nHow does your patron communicate with you? If
        you have a familiar, it might occasionally speak with
        your patron’s voice. Some warlocks find messages
        from their patrons etched on trees, mingled among tea
        leaves, or adrift in the clouds — messages that only the
        warlock can see. Other warlocks converse with their
        patrons in dreams or waking visions, or deal only with
        intermediaries.

    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="warlock_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Otherworldly Patron,
        \nPact Magic
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Eldricht Invocation
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_3rd_lvl_abilities">
        Pact Boon
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_5th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Otherworldly Patron Feature
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_7th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_9th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Otherworldly Patron Feature
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_11th_lvl_abilities">
        Mystic Arcanum (6th lvl)
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_13th_lvl_abilities">
        Mystic Arcanum (7th lvl)
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Otherworldly Patron Feature
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_15th_lvl_abilities">
        Mystic Arcanum (8th lvl)
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_17th_lvl_abilities">
        Mystic Arcanum (9th lvl)
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_18th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Eldricht Master
    </string>

    //---------------------------------------------------------Spell Table---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="warlock_table2_label">
        Spells Table
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value2_label">
        Invocations \nKnown
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value3_label">
        Cantrip \nKnown
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_label">
        Spells Known
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value2_1">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value2_2to4">
       2
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value2_5to6">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value2_7to8">
        4
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value2_9to11">
        5
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value2_12to14">
        6
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value2_15to17">
       7
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value2_18to20">
       8
    </string>





    <string name="warlock_table2_value3_1to3_values">
        2
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value3_4to9_values">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value3_10to20_values">
        4
    </string>




    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_1values">
        2
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_2values">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_3values">
        4
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_4values">
        5
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_5values">
        6
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_6values">
        7
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_7values">
        8
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_8values">
        9
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_9to10_values">
        10
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_11to12values">
        11
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_13to14values">
        12
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_15to16values">
        13
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_17to18values">
        14
    </string>

    <string name="warlock_table2_value4_19to20values">
        15
    </string>


    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="warlockFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a warlock, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="warlockHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d8 per warlock lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 8 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d8(or 5) + Constitution Modifier per warlock level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="warlockProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> Light Armor
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Simple weapons
        \n<b>Tools:</b> None
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Wisdom, Charisma
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose two from Arcana, Deception, History, Intimidation, Investigation , Nature, Religion
    </string>

    <string name="warlockEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background:
        \n\n- (a) a light crossbow with 20 bolts or (b) any simple weapon
        \n- (a) a component pouch or (b) an arcane focus
        \n- (a) a scholars pack or (b) a dungeoners pack
        \n- Leather armor, any simple weapon, two daggers
    </string>



    //-------------------------------------------ABILITIES-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="warlockEldrichtInvocationTitle">
        Eldricht Invocation
    </string>
    <string name="warlockEldrichtInvocation">
        In your study of occult lore, you have unearthed eldritch invocations, fragments of forbidden knowledge that imbue you with an abiding magical ability.
        \n\n
        At 2nd level, you gain two eldritch invocations of your choice. Your invocation options are detailed at the end of the class description.
        When you gain certain warlock levels, you gain additional invocations of your choice, as shown in the Invocations Known column of the Warlock table.
        \n\n
        Additionally, when you gain a level in this class, you can choose one of the invocations you know and replace it with another invocation that you could learn at that level.
    </string>
    

    <string name="warlockPactBoonTitle">
        Pact Boon
    </string>
    <string name="warlockPactBoon">
        At 3rd level, your otherworldly patron bestows a gift upon you for your loyal service. You gain one of the following features of your choice.
    </string>


    <string name="warlockPactOfTheChainTitle">
        Pact of the Chain
    </string>
    <string name="warlockPactOfTheChain">
        You learn the find familiar spell and can cast it as a ritual. The spell doesn’t count against your number of spells known.
        \n\n
        When you cast the spell, you can choose one of the normal forms for your familiar or one of the following special forms: imp, pseudodragon, quasit, or sprite.
        \n\n
        Additionally, when you take the Attack action, you can forgo one of your own attacks to allow your familiar to make one attack of its own.
    </string>
    

    <string name="Title">
        Pact of the Blade
    </string>
    <string name="warlockPactOfTheBlade">
        You can use your action to create a pact weapon in your empty hand. You can choose the form that this
        melee weapon takes each time you create it (see chapter 5 for weapon options). You are proficient with it while you wield it.
        This weapon counts as magical for the purpose of overcoming resistance and immunity to nonmagical attacks and damage.
        \n\n
        Your pact weapon disappears if it is more than 5 feet away from you for 1  minute or more.
        It also disappears if you use this feature again, if you dismiss the weapon (no action required), or if you die.
        \n\n
        You can transform one magic weapon into your pact weapon by performing a special ritual while you hold the weapon. 
        You perform the ritual over the course of 1  hour, which can be done during a short rest.You can then dismiss the weapon, 
        shunting it into an extradimensional space, and it appears whenever you create your pact weapon thereafter. 
        You can’t affect an artifact or a sentient weapon in this way. The weapon ceases being your pact weapon if you die, 
        if you perform the  1-hour ritual on a different weapon, or if you use a  1-hour ritual to break your bond to it. 
        The weapon appears at your feet if it is in the extradimensional space when the bond breaks.
    </string>

    
    <string name="warlockPactofTheTomeTitle">
        Pact of the Tome
    </string>
    <string name="warlockPactofTheTome">
        Your patron gives you a grimoire called a Book of Shadows. W hen you gain this feature, choose three
        cantrips from any class’s spell list. While the book is on your person, you can cast those cantrips at will.
        They don’t count against your number of cantrips known.
        \n\n
        If you lose your Book of Shadows, you can perform a  1-hour ceremony to receive a replacement from your patron.
        This ceremony can be performed during a short or long rest, and it destroys the previous book. The book turns to ash when you die.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="warlockMysticArcanumTitle">
        Mystic Arcanum
    </string>
    <string name="warlockMysticArcanum">
        At  11th level, your patron bestows upon you a magical secret called an arcanum. Choose one 6th-level spell from the warlock spell list as this arcanum.
        \n\n
        You can cast your arcanum spell once without expending a spell slot. You must finish a long rest before you can do so again.
        \n\n
        At higher levels, you gain more warlock spells of your choice that can be cast in this way: one 7th-level spell at  13th level, one 8th-level spell at 15th level, 
        and one 9th-level spell at 17th level. You regain all uses of your Mystic Arcanum when you finish a long rest.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="warlockEldritchMasterTitle">
        Eldritch Master
    </string>
    <string name="warlockEldritchMaster">
        At 20th level, you can draw on your inner reserve of mystical power while entreating your patron to regain expended 
        spell slots. You can spend  1  minute entreating your patron for aid to regain all your expended spell slots from your 
        Pact Magic feature. Once you regain spell slots with this feature, you must finish a long rest before you can do so again.
    </string>
    

    <string name="warlockOtherwordlyPatronsTitle">
        Otherwordly Patrons
    </string>
    <string name="warlockOtherwordlyPatrons">
        The beings that serve as patrons for warlocks are mighty inhabitants of other planes of existence—not gods, but almost godlike in
        their power. Various patrons give their warlocks access to different powers and invocations, and expect significant favors in return.
        \n\n
        om e patrons collect warlocks, doling out mystic knowledge relatively freely or boasting of their ability to bind mortals to their will.
        Other patrons bestow their power only grudgingly, and might make a pact with only one warlock. Warlocks who serve the same patron might
        view each other as allies, siblings, or rivals.
        \n\n
        At 1st level, you have struck a bargain with an otherworldly being of your choice: the Archfey, the Fiend, or the Great Old One, 
        each of which is detailed at the end of the class description. Your choice grants you features at 1st level and again at 6th,  10th, and 14th level.
    </string>
    

    <string name="warlockArchfeyTitle">
        The Archfey
    </string>
    <string name="warlockArchfey">
        Your patron is a lord or lady of the fey, a creature of legend who holds secrets that were forgotten before the mortal races were born.
        This being’s motivations are often inscrutable, and som etim es whimsical, and might involve a striving for greater magical power or the
        settling of age-old grudges. Beings of this sort include the Prince of Frost; the Queen of Air and Darkness, ruler of the Gloaming Court;
        Titania of the Summer Court; her consort Oberon, the Green Lord; Hyrsam, the Prince of Fools; and ancient hags.
    </string>


    <string name="warlockArchfeyExpendedSpelllistTitle">
        Extended Spell List
    </string>
    <string name="warlockArchfeyExpendedSpelllist">
        The Archfey lets you choose from an expanded list of spells when you learn a warlock spell. The following spells are added to the warlock spell list for you.
        \n\n
        <b>Spell Level \t\t\t Spells</b>
        \n
        1st \t\t\t faerie fire, sleep
        \n
        2nd \t\t\t calm emotions, phantasmal force
        \n
        3rd \t\t\t blink, plant growth
        \n
        4th \t\t\t dominate beast, greater invisibility
        \n
        5th \t\t\t dominate person, seeming
    </string>



    <string name="warlockArchfeyFeyPresenceTitle">
        Fey Presence
    </string>
    <string name="warlockArchfeyFeyPresence">
        Starting at  1st level, your patron bestows upon you the ability to project the beguiling and fearsome
        presence of the fey. As an action, you can cause each creature in a 10-foot cube originating from you
        to make a Wisdom saving throw against your warlock spell save DC. The creatures that fail their saving
        throws are all charmed or frightened by you (your choice) until the end of your next turn.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a short or long rest.
    </string>
    

    <string name="warlockArchfeyMistyEscapeTitle">
        Misty Escape
    </string>
    <string name="warlockArchfeyMistyEscape">
        Starting at 6th level, you can vanish in a puff of mist in response to harm. W hen you take damage, you can use your reaction to turn invisible and teleport up
        to 60 feet to an unoccupied space you can see. You remain invisible until the start of your next turn or until you attack or cast a spell.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can't use it again until you finish a short or long rest.
    </string>

    
    <string name="walockArchfeyBeguilingDefensesTitle">
        Beguiling Defenses
    </string>
    <string name="walockArchfeyBeguilingDefenses">
        Beginning at 10th level, your patron teaches you how to turn the mind-affecting magic of your enemies against them. 
        You are immune to being charmed, and when another creature attempts to charm you, you can use your reaction to attempt to 
        turn the charm back on that creature. The creature must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw against your warlock spell save DC or 
        be charmed by you for 1  minute or until the creature takes any damage.
    </string>

    
    <string name="warlockArchfeyDarkDeliriumTitle">
        Dark Delirium
    </string>
    <string name="warlockArchfeyDarkDelirium">
        tarting at 14th level, you can plunge a creature into an illusory realm. As an action, choose a creature that you can see 
        within 60 feet of you. It must make a W isdom  saving throw against your warlock spell save DC. 
        On a failed save, it is charmed or frightened by you (your choice) for 1  minute or until your concentration is 
        broken (as if you are concentrating on a spell). This effect ends early if the creature takes any damage.
        \n\n
        Until this illusion ends, the creature thinks it is lost in a misty realm, the appearance of which you choose. The creature can see and hear only itself, you, and the illusion.
        \n\n
        You must finish a short or long rest before you can use this feature again.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="warlockFiendTitle">
        The Fiend
    </string>
    <string name="warlockFiend">
        You have made a pact with a fiend from the lower planes of existence, a being w hose aims are evil, even if 
        you strive against those aims. Such beings desire the corruption or destruction of all things, ultimately including you. 
        Fiends powerful enough to forge a pact include demon lords such as Demogorgon, Orcus, Fraz’Urb-luu, and Baphomet; archdevils 
        such as Asmodeus, Dispater, Mephistopheles, and Belial; pit fiends and balors that are especially mighty; and ultroloths and other lords of the yugoloths.
    </string>
    

    <string name="warlockFiendExpandedSpellListTitle">
        Expanded Spell List
    </string>
    <string name="warlockFiendExpandedSpellList">
        The Fiend lets you choose from an expanded list of spells when you learn a warlock spell. The following spells are added to the warlock spell list for you.
        \n\n
        <b>Spell Level \t\t\t Spells</b>
        \n
        1st \t\t\t burning hands, command
        \n
        2nd \t\t\t blindness/deafness, scorching ray
        \n
        3rd \t\t\t fireball, stinking cloud
        \n
        4th \t\t\t fire shield, wall of fire
        \n
        5th \t\t\t flame strike, hallow
    </string>
    

    <string name="warlockFiendDarkOnesBlessingTitle">
        Dark Ones Blessing
    </string>
    <string name="warlockFiendDarkOnesBlessing">
        Starting at 1st level, when you reduce a hostile creature to 0 hit points,
        you gain temporary hit points equal to your Charisma modifier + your warlock level (minimum of 1).
    </string>

    
    <string name="warlockFiendDarkOnesOwnLuckTitle">
        Dark Ones Own Luck
    </string>
    <string name="warlockFiendDarkOnesOwnLuck">
        Starting at 6th level, you can call on your patron to alter fate in your favor. W hen you make an ability
        check or a saving throw, you can use this feature to add a d10 to your roll. You can do so after seeing the
        initial roll but before any of the roll’s effects occur.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a short or long rest.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="warlockFiendFiendishReplenishTitle">
        Fiendish Replenish
    </string>
    <string name="warlockFiendFiendishReplenish">
        Starting at  10th level, you can choose one damage type when you finish a short or long rest. 
        You gain resistance to that damage type until you choose a different one with this feature. Damage from magical weapons or silver weapons ignores this resistance.
    </string>
    
    
    
    <string name="warlockFiendHurlThroughTItle">
        Hurl Through Hell
    </string>
    <string name="warlockFiendHurlThrough">
        Starting at 14th level, when you hit a creature with an attack, you can use this feature to instantly transport the target through the lower planes.
        The creature disappears and hurtles through a nightmare landscape.
        \n\n
        At the end of your next turn, the target returns to the space it previously occupied, or the nearest unoccupied space.
        If the target is not a fiend, it takes  10d10 psychic damage as it reels from its horrific experience.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a long rest.
    </string>
    
    
    <string name="warlockGreatOldOneTitle">
        The Great Old One
    </string>
    <string name="warlockGreatOldOne">
        Your patron is a mysterious entity whose nature is utterly foreign to the fabric of reality. It might com e from the Far Realm, 
        the space beyond reality, or it could be one of the elder gods known only in legends. Its motives are incomprehensible to mortals, 
        and its knowledge so immense and ancient that even the greatest libraries pale in comparison to the vast secrets it holds. The Great 
        Old One might be unaware of your existence or entirely indifferent to you, but the secrets you have learned allow you to draw your magic from it.
        \n\n
        Entities of this type include Ghaunadar, called That Which Lurks; Tharizdun, the Chained God; Dendar, the Night Serpent; Zargon,
        the Returner; Great Cthulhu; and other unfathomable beings.
    </string>
    
    <string name="warlockGreatOldOneExpendedSpellListTitle">
        Expanded Spell List
    </string>
    <string name="warlockGreatOldOneExpendedSpellList">
        The Great Old One lets you choose from an expanded list of spells when you learn a warlock spell. The following spells are added to the warlock spell list for you.
        \n\n
        <b>Spell Level \t\t\t Spells</b>
        \n
        1st \t\t\t dissonant whisper, Tashas hideous laughter
        \n
        2nd \t\t\t detect thoughts, phantasmal force
        \n
        3rd \t\t\t clairvoyance, sending
        \n
        4th \t\t\t dominate beast, Evards black tentacles
        \n\n
        5th dominate person, telekinesis
    </string>
    


    <string name="warlockGreatOldOneAwakenedMindTitle">
        Awakened Mind
    </string>
    <string name="warlockGreatOldOneAwakenedMind">
        Starting at  1st level, your alien knowledge gives you the ability to touch the minds of other creatures. 
        You can communicate telepathically with any creature you can see within 30 feet of you. You don’t need to share a 
        language with the creature for it to understand your telepathic utterances, but the creature must be able to understand at least one language.
    </string>
    

    <string name="warlockGreatOldOneEntropicWardTitle">
        Entropic Ward
    </string>
    <string name="warlockGreatOldOneEntropicWard">
        At 6th level, you learn to magically ward yourself against attack and to turn an enemy’s
        failed strike into good luck for yourself. W hen a creature makes an attack roll against you,
        you can use your reaction to im pose disadvantage on that roll. If the attack misses you, your next
        attack roll against the creature has advantage if you make it before the end of your next turn.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a short or long rest.
    </string>
    

    <string name="warlockGreatOldOneThoughtShieldTitle">
        Thought Shield
    </string>
    <string name="warlockGreatOldOneThoughtShield">
        Starting at 10th level, your thoughts can’t be read by telepathy or other m eans unless you allow it. You also have resistance to psychic damage, 
        and whenever a creature deals psychic damage to you, that creature takes the same amount of damage that you do.
    </string>
    
    <string name="warlockGreatOldOneGreatThrallTitle">
        Great Thrall
    </string>
    <string name="warlockGreatOldOneGreatThrall">
        At  14th level, you gain the ability to infect a humanoid’s mind with the alien magic of your patron.
        You can use your action to touch an incapacitated humanoid. That creature is then charmed by you until a remove
        cursespell is cast on it, the charmed condition is removed from it, or you use this feature again.
        \n\n
        You can communicate telepathically with the charmed creature as long as the two of you are on the same plane of existence.
    </string>

    
    
    
    
</resources>