<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="wizard_introduction">
        Clad in the silver robes that denote her station, an
        elf closes her eyes to shut out the distractions of the
        battlefield and begins her quiet chant. Fingers weaving
        in front of her, she completes her spell and launches a
        tiny bead of fire toward the enemy ranks, where it erupts
        into a conflagration that engulfs the soldiers.

        \n\nChecking and rechecking his work, a human scribes
        an intricate magic circle in chalk on the bare stone
        floor, then sprinkles powdered iron along every line and
        graceful curve. When the circle is complete, he drones a
        long incantation. A hole opens in space inside the circle,
        bringing a whiff of brimstone from the otherworldly
        plane beyond.

        \n\nCrouching on the floor in a dungeon intersection, a
        gnome tosses a handful of sm all bones in scribed with
        mystic symbols, muttering a few words of power over
        them. Closing his eyes to see the visions more clearly,
        he nods slowly, then opens his eyes and points down the
        passage to his left.

        \n\nWizards are supreme magic-users, defined and united
        as a class by the spells they cast. Drawing on the subtle
        weave of magic that permeates the cosmos, wizards cast
        spells of explosive fire, arcing lightning, subtle deception,
        and brute-force mind control. Their magic conjures
        monsters from other planes of existence, glimpses the
        future, or turns slain foes into zombies. Their mightiest
        spells change one substance into another, call meteors
        down from the sky, or open portals to other worlds.


    </string>

    <string name="creating_wizard_string">
        Creating a wizard character demands a backstory
        dominated by at least one extraordinary event. How
        did your character first come into contact with magic?
        How did you discover you had an aptitude for it? Do
        you have a natural talent, or did you simply study
        hard and practice incessantly? Did you encounter a
        magical creature or an ancient tome that taught you the
        basics of magic?

        \n\nWhat drew you forth from your life of study? Did your
        first taste of magical knowledge leave you hungry for
        more? Have you received word of a secret repository
        of knowledge not yet plundered by any other wizard?
        Perhaps you’re simply eager to put your new found
        magical skills to the test in the face of danger.

    </string>

    //-----------------------------------------------------------Abilities per Lvl-------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//


    <string name="wizard_1st_lvl_abilities">
        Spellcasting,
        \nArcane Recovery
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_2nd_lvl_abilities">
        Arcane Tradition
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_3rd_lvl_abilities">
       -
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_4th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_5th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_6th_lvl_abilities">
        Arcane Tradition Feature
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_7th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_8th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement,
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_9th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_10th_lvl_abilities">
        Arcane Tradition Feature
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_11th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_12th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_13th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_14th_lvl_abilities">
        Arcane Tradition Feature
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_15th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_16th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_17th_lvl_abilities">
        -
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_18th_lvl_abilities">
        Spell Mastery
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_19th_lvl_abilities">
        Ability Score Improvement
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_20th_lvl_abilities">
        Signature Spell
    </string>

    //---------------------------------------------------------Spell Table---------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//
    <string name="wizard_table2_label">
        Spells Table
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_table2_value2_label">
        Cantrips Known
    </string>


    <string name="wizard_table2_value2_1to3_values">
        3
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_table2_value2_4to9_values">
        4
    </string>

    <string name="wizard_table2_value2_10to20_values">
        5
    </string>

    //------------------------------------------------CLASS FEATURES------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="wizardFeaturesTitleDescription">
        As a wizard, you gain the following class features.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardHp">
        <b>Hit Dice:</b> 1d6 per wizard lvl
        \n<b>HP at 1st lvl:</b> 6 + Constitution Modifier
        \n<b>HP on higher levels:</b> 1d6(or 4) + Constitution Modifier per wizard level after 1st
    </string>

    <string name="wizardProfitiencysDescription">
        <b>Armor:</b> None
        \n<b>Weapons:</b> Daggers, darts, slings, quarterstaffs, light crossbows
        \n<b>Tools:</b> None
        \n
        \n<b>Saving Throws:</b> Intelligence, Wisdom
        \n<b>Skills: </b> Choose two from Arcana, History, Insight, Investigation, Medicine, Religion
    </string>

    <string name="wizardEquipment">
         You start with the following equipment in addition to the equipment granted by your background:
        \n\n- (a) a quarterstaff or (b) a dagger
        \n- (a) a component pouch or (b) an arcane focus
        \n- (a) a scholars pack or (b) an explorers pack
        \n- A spellbook
    </string>



    //-------------------------------------------ABILITIES-----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------//

    <string name="wizardArcaneRecoveryTitle">
        Arcane Recovery
    </string>

    <string name="wizardArcaneRecovery">
        You have learned to regain som e of your magical energy by studying your spellbook.
        Once per day when you finish a short rest, you can choose expended spell slots to recover.
        The spell slots can have a combined level that is equal to or less than half your wizard level (rounded up),
        and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher.
        \n\n
        For example, if you’re a 4th-level wizard, you can recover up to two levels worth of spell slots. You can recover either a 2nd-level spell slot or two  1st-level spell slots.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSpellMasteryTitle">
        SpellMastery
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSpellMastery">
        At 18th level, you have achieved such mastery over certain spells that you can cast them at will.
        Choose a 1st-level wizard spell and a 2nd-level wizard spell that are in your spellbook. You can cast those spells at their
        lowest level without expending a spell slot when you have them prepared. If you want to cast either spell at a higher level, you must expend a spell slot as normal.
        \n\n
        By spending 8 hours in study, you can exchange one or both of the spells you chose for different spells of the same levels.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSignatureSpellsTitle">
        Signature Spells
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSignatureSpells">
        When you reach 20th level, you gain mastery over two powerful spells and can cast them with little effort. Choose two 3rd-level wizard spells in your spellbook as your
        signature spells. You always have these spells prepared, they don’t count against the number of spells you have prepared, and you can
        cast each of them once at 3rd level without expending a spell slot. W hen you do so, you can’t do so again until you finish a short or long rest.
        \n\n
        If you want to cast either spell at a higher level, you must expend a spell slot as normal.
    </string>



    <string name="wizardArcaneTraditionsTitle">
       Arcane Traditions
    </string>
    <string name="wizardArcaneTraditions">
        The study of wizardry is ancient, stretching back to
        the earliest mortal discoveries of magic. It is firmly established in the worlds of DnD, with various traditions dedicated to its complex study.
        \n\n
        The most com m on arcane traditions in the multiverse revolve around the schools of magic. Wizards through the ages have cataloged thousands of
        spells, grouping them into eight categories called schools, as described in chapter  10. In som e places, these traditions are literally schools;
        a wizard might study at the School of Illusion while another studies across town at the School of Enchantment. In other institutions, the
        schools are more like academic departments, with rival faculties competing for students and funding. Even wizards who train apprentices
        in the solitude of their own towers use the division of magic into schools as a learning device, since the spells of each school require mastery
        of different techniques.
        \n\n
        When you reach 2nd level, you choose an arcane tradition, shaping your practice of magic through one of eight schools: Abjuration, Conjuration,
        Divination, Enchantment, Evocation, Illusion, Necromancy, or Transmutation, all detailed at the end of the class description.
        \n\n
        Your choice grants you features at 2nd level and again at 6th,  10th, and  14th level.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolofAbjurationTitle">
        School of Abjuration
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolofAbjuration">
        he School of Abjuration emphasizes magic that blocks, banishes, or protects.
        Detractors of this school say that its tradition is about denial, negation rather than positive assertion.
        You understand, however, that ending harmful effects, protecting the weak, and banishing evil influences is
        anything but a philosophical void. It is a proud and respected vocation.
        \n\n
        Called abjurers, members of this school are sought when baleful spirits require exorcism, when important locations must be 
        guarded against magical spying, and when portals to other planes of existence must be closed.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfAbjurationAbjurantServantTitle">
        Abjurant Savant
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfAbjurationAbjurantServant">
        Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy an abjuration spell into your spellbook is halved.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfAbjurationArcaneWardTitle">
       Arcane Ward
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfAbjurationArcaneWard">
        Starting at 2nd level, you can weave magic around yourself for protection. When you cast an abjuration spell of 1st level or
        higher, you can simultaneously use a strand of the spell’s magic to create a magical ward on yourself that lasts until you finish a
        long rest. The ward has hit points equal to twice your wizard level + your Intelligence modifier. Whenever you take damage, the ward
        takes the damage instead. If this damage reduces the ward to 0 hit points, you take any remaining damage.
        \n\n
        W hile the ward has 0 hit points, it can’t absorb damage, but its magic remains. Whenever you cast an abjuration spell of 1st level
        or higher, the ward regains a number of hit points equal to twice the level of the spell.
        \n\n
        Once you create the ward, you can't create it again until you finish a long rest.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfAbjurationProjectWardTitle">
       Project Ward
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfAbjurationProjectWard">
        Starting at 6th level, when a creature that you can see within 30 feet of you takes damage, you can use your reaction to cause your 
        Arcane Ward to absorb that damage. If this damage reduces the ward to 0 hit points, the warded creature takes any remaining damage.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfAbjurationImprovedAbjurationTitle">
        Improved Abjuration
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfAbjurationImprovedAbjuration">
        Beginning at 10th level, when you cast an abjuration spell that requires you to make an ability check as a part of casting that 
        spell (as in counterspell and dispel magic), you add your proficiency bonus to that ability check.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfAbjurationSpellResistanceTitle">
        Spell Resistance
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfAbjurationSpellResistance">
        Starting at 14th level, you have advantage on saving throws against spells.
        \n\n
        Furthermore, you have resistance against the damage of spells.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfConjurationTitle">
        School of Conjuration
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfConjuration">
        As a conjurer, you favor spells that produce objects and creatures out of thin air. 
        You can conjure billowing clouds of killing fog or summon creatures from elsewhere to fight on your behalf. 
        As your mastery grows, you learn spells of transportation and can teleport yourself across vast distances, even to other planes of existence, in an instant.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfConjurationConjurationServantTitle">
        Conjuration Savant
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfConjurationConjurationServant">
        Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy a conjuration spell into your spellbook is halved.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchooldOfConjurationMinorConjurationTitle">
        Minor Conjuration
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchooldOfConjurationMinorConjuration">
        Starting at 2nd level when you select this school, you can use your action to conjure up an inanimate object in your hand or on the ground in an unoccupied space that you can see within  10 feet of you.
        This object can be no larger than 3 feet on a side and weigh no more than 10 pounds, and its form must be that of a nonmagical object that you have seen. The object is visibly magical, radiating dim light out to 5 feet.
        \n\n
        The object disappears after  1  hour, when you use this feature again, or if it takes any damage.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfConjurationBenignTranspositionTitle">
        Benign Transposition
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfConjurationBenignTransposition">
        Starting at 6th level, you can use your action to teleport up to 30 feet to an unoccupied space that you can see.
        Alternatively, you can choose a space within range that is occupied by a Small or Medium creature. If that creature is willing, you both teleport, swapping places.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a long rest or you cast a conjuration spell of 1st level or higher.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfConjurationFocusedConjurationTitle">
        Focused Conjuration
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfConjurationFocusedConjuration">
        Beginning at  10th level, while you are concentrating on a conjuration spell, your concentration can’t be broken as a result of taking damage.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfConjurationDurableSummonsTitle">
        Durable SUmmons
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfConjurationDurableSummons">
        Starting at  14th level, any creature that you summon or create with a conjuration spell has 30 temporary hit points.
    </string>



    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivinationTitle">
        School of Divination
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivination">
        The counsel of a diviner is sought by royalty and com m oners alike, for all seek a clearer understanding of the past, present, and future.
        As a diviner, you strive to part the veils of space, time, and consciousness so that you can see clearly. You work to master spells of discernment,
        remote viewing, supernatural knowledge, and foresight.
    </string>



    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivinationDivinationSavantTitle">
        BDivination Savant.
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivinationDivinationSavant">
        Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy a divination spell into your spellbook is halved.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivinationPortendTitle">
        Portend
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivinationPortend">
        Starting at 2nd level when you choose this school, glimpses of the future begin to press in on your awareness. When you finish a long rest, 
        roll two d20s and record the numbers rolled. You can replace any attack roll, saving throw, or ability check made by you or a 
        creature that you can see with one of these foretelling rolls. You must choose to do so before the roll, and you can replace a roll in this way only once per turn.
        \n\n
        Each foretelling roll can be used only once. W hen you finish a long rest, you lose any unused foretelling rolls
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivinationExpertDivinationTitle">
        Expert Divination
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivinationExpertDivination">
        Beginning at 6th level, casting divination spells com es so easily to you that it expends only a fraction of your 
        spellcasting efforts. When you cast a divination spell of 2nd level or higher using a spell slot, you regain one expended spell slot. 
        The slot you regain must be of a level lower than the spell you cast and can’t be higher than 5th level.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivinationTheThirdEyeTitle">
        The Third Eye
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivinationTheThirdEye">
        Starting at  10th level, you can use your action to increase your powers of perception. When you do so, choose one of the following benefits,
        which lasts until you are incapacitated or you take a short or long rest. You can’t use the feature again until you finish a rest.
        \n\n
        <b>Darkvision</b>
        \n
        You gain darkvision out to a range of 60 feet, as described in chapter 8.
        \n\n
        <b>Ethereal Sight</b>
        \n
        You can see into the Ethereal Plane within 60 feet of you.
        \n\n
        <b>Greater Comprehension</b>
        \n
        You can read any language.
        \n\n
        <b>See invisibility</b>
        \n
        You can see invisible creatures and objects within  10 feet of you that are within line of sight.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivinationGreaterPortentTitle">
        Greater Portent
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfDivinationGreaterPortent">
        Starting at 14th level, the visions in your dreams intensify and 
        paint a more accurate picture in your mind of what is to come. You roll three d20s for your Portent feature, rather than two.
    </string>



    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantmentTitle">
        School of Enchantment
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantment">
        As a member of the School of Enchantment, you have honed your ability to 
        magically entrance and beguile other people and monsters. Som e enchanters are peacemakers w ho bewitch the 
        violent to lay down their arms and charm the cruel into showing mercy. Others are tyrants who magically bind the unwilling into their service. 
        Most enchanters fall somewhere in between.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantmentEnchantedSavantTitle">
        Enchanted Savant
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantmentEnchantedSavant">
        Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy an enchantment spell into your spellbook is halved.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantmentHypnoticGazeTitle">
        Hypnotic Gaze
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantmentHypnoticGaze">
        Starting at 2nd level when you choose this school, your soft words and enchanting gaze can magically enthrall another creature. As an action,
        choose one creature that you can see within 5 feet of you. If the target can see or hear you, it must succeed on a Wisdom
        saving throw against your wizard spell save DC or be charmed by you until the end of your next turn. The charmed creature’s speed
        drops to 0, and the creature is incapacitated and visibly dazed.
        \n\n
        On subsequent turns, you can use your action to maintain this effect, extending its duration until the end of your next turn. However, the effect ends
        if you move more than 5 feet away from the creature, if the creature can neither see nor hear you, or if the creature takes damage.
        \n\n
        Once the effect ends, or if the creature succeeds on its initial saving throw against this effect,
        you can’t use this feature on that creature again until you finish a long rest.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantmentInstinctiveCharmTitle">
        Instinctive Charm
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantmentInstinctiveCharm">
        Beginning at 6th level, when a creature you can see within 30 feet of you makes an attack roll against you, you can use your reaction to divert the
        attack, provided that another creature is within the attack’s range. The attacker must make a W isdom  saving throw against your wizard spell save DC.
        On a failed save, the attacker must target the creature that is closest to it, not including you or itself. If multiple creatures are closest, the attacker
        chooses which one to target. On a successful save, you can’t use this feature on the attacker again until you finish a long rest.
        \n\n
        You must choose to use this feature before knowing whether the attack hits or misses. Creatures that can’t be charmed are immune to this effect.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantmentSplitEnchantmentTitle">
      Split Enchantment
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantmentSplitEnchantment">
        Starting at 10th level, when you cast an enchantment spell of 1st level or higher that targets only one creature, you can have it target a second creature.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantmentAlterMemoriesTitle">
      Alter Memories
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEnchantmentAlterMemories">
        At  14th level, you gain the ability to make a creature unaware of your magical influence on it. W hen you cast an enchantment
        spell to charm one or more creatures, you can alter one creature’s understanding so that it remains unaware of being charmed.
        \n\n
        Additionally, once before the spell expires, you can use your action to try to make the chosen creature forget som e of the time it spent charmed. 
        The creature must succeed on an Intelligence saving throw against your wizard spell save DC or lose a number of hours of its 
        memories equal to  1 + your Charisma modifier (minimum 1). You can make the creature forget less time, and the amount of time can’t exceed the 
        duration of your enchantment spell.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocationTitle">
        School of Evocation
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocation">
        ou focus your study on magic that creates powerful elemental effects such as bitter cold, searing flame, rolling thunder, crackling lightning, 
        and burning acid. Som e evokers find employment in military forces, serving as artillery to blast enemy armies from afar. Others use their spectacular 
        power to protect the weak, while som e seek their own gain as bandits, adventurers, or aspiring tyrants.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocationEvocationSavantTitle">
        Evocation Savant
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocationEvocationSavant">
        Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy an evocation spell into your spellbook is halved.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocationSculptSpellsTitle">
        Sculpt Spells
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocationSculptSpells">
        Beginning at 2nd level, you can create pockets of relative safety within the effects of your evocation spells. 
        When you cast an evocation spell that affects other creatures that you can see, you can choose a number of them equal to  
        1 + the spell’s level. The chosen creatures automatically succeed on their saving throws against the spell, and they take no 
        damage if they would normally take half damage on a successful save.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocationPotentCantripTitle">
        Potent Cantrip
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocationPotentCantrip">
        Starting at 6th level, your damaging cantrips affect even creatures that avoid the brunt of the effect. When a creature succeeds on a saving throw against your cantrip, 
        the creature takes half the cantrip’s damage (if any) but suffers no additional effect from the cantrip.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocationEmpoweredEvocationTitle">
       Empowered Evocation
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocationEmpoweredEvocation">
        Beginning at  10th level, you can add your Intelligence modifier to the damage roll of any wizard evocation spell you cast.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocationOverchannelTitle">
       Overchannel
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfEvocationOverchannel">
        Starting at 14th level, you can increase the power of your simpler spells. W hen you cast a wizard spell of 5th level or lower that deals damage,
        you can deal maximum damage with that spell.
        \n\n
        The first time you do so, you suffer no adverse effect. If you use this feature again before you finish a long rest, you take 2d12 necrotic
        damage for each level of the spell, immediately after you cast it. Each time you use this feature again before finishing a long rest, the necrotic
        damage per spell level increases by 1d12. This damage ignores resistance and immunity.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfIllusionTitle">
        School Of Illusion
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfIllusion">
        You focus your studies on magic that dazzles the senses, befuddles the mind, and tricks even the wisest folk. Your magic is subtle,
        but the illusions crafted by your keen mind make the impossible seem real. Som e illusionists—including many gnome w izards—are benign
        tricksters who use their spells to entertain. Others are more sinister masters of deception, using their illusions to frighten and fool others for
        their personal gain.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSWchoolOfIllusionIllusionSavantTitle">
        Illusion Savant
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSWchoolOfIllusionIllusionSavant">
        Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy an illusion spell into your spellbook is halved.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfIllusionImprovedMinorIllusionTitle">
        Improved Minor Illusion
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfIllusionImprovedMinorIllusion">
        When you choose this school at 2nd level, you learn the minor illusion cantrip. If you already know this cantrip, you learn a different wizard cantrip of your choice.
        The cantrip doesn’t count against your number of cantrips known.
        \n\n
        When you cast minor illusion, you can create both a sound and an image with a single casting of the spell.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfIllusionMalleableIllusionTitle">
        Malleable Illusion
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfIllusionMalleableIllusion">
        Starting at 6th level, when you cast an illusion spell that has a duration of 1  minute or longer, you can use your action to change the nature of that 
        illusion (using the spell’s normal parameters for the illusion), provided that you can see the illusion.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardChoolOfIllusionIllusorySelfTitle">
       Illusory Self
    </string>
    <string name="wizardChoolOfIllusionIllusorySelf">
        Beginning at  10th level, you can create an illusory duplicate of yourself as an instant, almost instinctual
        reaction to danger. When a creature makes an attack roll against you, you can use your reaction to interpose the illusory duplicate between
        the attacker and yourself. The attack automatically misses you, then the illusion dissipates.
        \n\n
        Once you use this feature, you can’t use it again until you finish a short or long rest.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfIllusionIllusoryRealityTitle">
      Illusory Reality
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfIllusionIllusoryReality">
        By 14th level, you have learned the secret of weaving shadow magic into your illusions to give them a semi-reality.
        When you cast an illusion spell of 1st level or higher, you can choose one inanimate, nonmagical object that is part of the
        illusion and make that object real. You can do this on your turn as a bonus action while the spell is ongoing. The object remains real for 1  minute.
        For example, you can create an illusion of a bridge over a chasm and then make it real long enough for your allies to cross.
        \n\n
        The object can’t deal damage or otherwise directly harm anyone.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancyTitle">
        School of Necromancy
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancy">
        The School of Necromancy explores the cosm ic forces of life, death, and undeath. As you focus your studies in this tradition, you
        learn to manipulate the energy that animates all living things. As you progress, you learn to sap the life force from a creature as your
        magic destroys its body, transforming that vital energy into magical power you can manipulate.
        \n\n
        Most people see necromancers as menacing, or even villainous, due to the close association with death.Not all necromancers are evil, but the forces they manipulate are considered taboo by many societies.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancyNecromancySavantTitle">
       Necromancy Savant
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancyNecromancySavant">
        Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy a necromancy spell into your spellbook is halved.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancyGrimHarvestTitle">
Grim Harvest

    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancyGrimHarvest">
        At 2nd level, you gain the ability to reap life energy from creatures you kill with your spells. Once per turn when you kill one or more creatures with a
        spell of 1st level or higher, you regain hit points equal to twice the spell’s level, or three times its level if the spell belongs to the School of Necromancy.
        You don’t gain this benefit for killing constructs or undead.

    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancyUndeadThrallsTitle">
       Undead Thralls
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancyUndeadThralls">
        At 6th level, you add the animate dead spell to your spellbook if it is not there already. W hen you cast animate dead, you can target one additional corpse or pile of bones, creating another zombie or skeleton, as appropriate.
        \n\n
        Whenever you create an undead using a necromancy spell, it has additional benefits:
        \n
        •\tThe creature’s hit point maximum is increased by an amount equal to your wizard level.
        \n
        •\tThe creature adds your proficiency bonus to its weapon damage rolls.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancyInuredToUndeadTitle">
        Inured to Undead
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancyInuredToUndead">
        Beginning at 10th level, you have resistance to necrotic damage, and your hit point maximum cant be reduced. You have spent so much time dealing with undead 
        and the forces that animate them that you have becom e inured to som e of their worst effects.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancyCommandUndeadTitle">
       Command Undead
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfNecromancyCommandUndead">
        Starting at 14th level, you can use magic to bring undead under your control, even those created by other wizards.
        As an action, you can choose one undead that you can see within 60 feet of you. That creature must make a Charisma saving throw against your
        wizard spell save DC. If it succeeds, you can’t use this feature on it again. If it fails, it becomes friendly to you and obeys your commands
        until you use this feature again.
        \n\n
        Intelligent undead are harder to control in this way.If the target has an Intelligence of 8 or higher, it has advantage on the saving throw. 
        If it fails the saving throw and has an Intelligence of 12 or higher, it can repeat the saving throw at the end of every hour until it succeeds and breaks free.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutationTitle">
    School of Transmutation
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutation">
        You are a student of spells that modify energy and matter. To you, the world is not a fixed thing, but eminently mutable, and you delight in
        being an agent of change.You wield the raw stuff of creation and learn to alter both physical forms and mental qualities.
        Your magic gives you the tools to becom e a smith on reality’s forge.
        \n\n
        Some transmuters are tinkerers and pranksters, turning people into toads and transforming copper into silver for fun and occasional profit.
        Others pursue their magical studies with deadly seriousness, seeking the power of the gods to make and destroy worlds.
        
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutaiotnTransmutationSavantTitle">
        Transmutation Savant
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutaiotnTransmutationSavant">
        Beginning when you select this school at 2nd level, the gold and time you must spend to copy a transmutation spell into your spellbook is halved.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutationMinorAlchemyTitle">
        Minor Alchemy
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutationMinorAlchemy">
        Starting at 2nd level when you select this school, you can temporarily alter the physical properties of one nonmagical object,
        changing it from one substance into another. You perform a special alchemical procedure on one object com posed entirely of wood, stone
        (but not a gemstone), iron, copper, or silver, transforming it into a different one of those materials. For each  10 minutes
        you spend performing the procedure, you can transform up to  1  cubic foot of material. After 1  hour, or until you lose your concentration
        (as if you were concentrating on a spell), the material reverts to its original substance.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutationTransmutersStoneTitle">
      Transmuter Stone
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutationTransmutersStone">
        Starting at 6th level, you can spend 8 hours creating a transmuter’s stone that stores transmutation magic. You can benefit from the stone yourself or
        give it to another creature. A creature gains a benefit of your choice as long as the stone is in the creature’s possession. W hen you create the stone,
        choose the benefit from the following options:
        \n\n
        •\tDarkvision out to a range of 60 feet, as described in chapter 8
        \n
        •\tAn increase to speed of 10 feet while the creature is unencumbered
        \n
        •\tProficiency in Constitution saving throws
        \n
        •\tResistance to acid, cold, fire, lightning, or thunder damage (your choice whenever you choose this benefit)
        \n\n
        Each time you cast a transmutation spell of 1st level or higher, you can change the effect of your stone if the stone is on your person.
        \n\n
        If you create a new transmuter’s stone, the previous one ceases to function.
    </string>

    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutationShapeChangerTitle">
       Shape Changer
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutationShapeChanger">
        At  10th level, you add the polymorph spell to your spellbook, if it is not there already. You can cast polymorph without
        expending a spell slot. W hen you do so, you can target only yourself and transform into a beast w hose challenge rating is 1  or lower.
        \n\n
        Once you cast polymorph in this way, you can’t do so again until you finish a short or long rest, though you can still cast it 
        normally using an available spell slot.
    </string>


    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutationMasterTransmuterTitle">
       Master Transmuter
    </string>
    <string name="wizardSchoolOfTransmutationMasterTransmuter">
        Starting at 14th level, you can use your action to consum e the reserve of transmutation magic stored within your transmuter’s
        stone in a single burst. When you do so, choose one of the following effects. Your transmuter’s stone is destroyed and
        can’t be remade until you finish a long rest.
        \n\n
        <b>Major Transformation</b>\n
        You can transmute one nonmagical object—no larger than a 5-foot cube—into another nonmagical object of similar size and mass and of equal or lesser value.
        You must spend 10 minutes handling the object to transform it.
        \n\n
        <b>Panacea</b>\n
        You remove all curses, diseases, and poisons affecting a creature that you touch with the transmuter’s stone. The creature also regains all its hit points.
        \n\n
        <b>Restore Life</b>\n
        You cast the raise dead spell on a creature you touch with the transmuter’s stone, without expending a spell slot or needing to have the spell in your spellbook.
        \n\n
        <b>Restore Youth</b>\n
        You touch the transmuter’s stone to a willing creature, and that creature’s apparent age is reduced by 3d10 years, to a minimum of 13 years. This effect doesn’t extend the creature’s lifespan.
    </string>
    
</resources>
